<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2023-01-08T00:24:09.840Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2023-01-08T00:24:09.840Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SMS Delivery Failures to Algar Telecom (CTBC) Network in Brazil]]></title>
        <id>https://status.twilio.com/incidents/34c8hqw2r9pw</id>
        <link href="https://status.twilio.com/incidents/34c8hqw2r9pw"/>
        <updated>2023-01-08T00:02:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jan  7, 16:02 PST
Update - We still continue to experience SMS delivery failures to Algar Telecom (CTBC) Network in Brazil from a subset of short-codes. Our engineers are working with our carrier partner to resolve this issue. We expect to provide another update in 8 hours or as soon as more information becomes available.
Jan  7, 12:01 PST
Update - We continue experiencing SMS delivery failures to Algar Telecom (CTBC) Network in Brazil from a subset of short-codes. Our engineers are working with our carrier partner to resolve the issue. We expect to provide another update in 4 hours or as soon as more information becomes available.
Jan  7, 09:58 PST
Update - We continue to experience SMS delivery failures to Algar Telecom (CTBC) Network in Brazil from a subset of short-codes. Our engineers are working with our carrier partner to resolve the issue. We expect to provide another update in 2 hours or as soon as more information becomes available.
Jan  7, 08:58 PST
Investigating - We are experiencing SMS delivery failures to Algar Telecom (CTBC) Network in Brazil from a subset of short-codes. Our engineers are working with our carrier partner to resolve the issue. We expect to provide another update in 1 hour or as soon as more information becomes available.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Twilio Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident with Actions]]></title>
        <id>https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/ffwkvn9j77d1</id>
        <link href="https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/ffwkvn9j77d1"/>
        <updated>2023-01-07T23:30:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jan  7, 23:30 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Jan  7, 23:25 UTC
Update - We are investigating reports of timeouts with Actions. We will continue to keep users updated on progress towards mitigation.
Jan  7, 22:50 UTC
Investigating - We are investigating reports of degraded performance for Actions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GitHub Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Singapore SMS Carrier Maintenance - StarHub]]></title>
        <id>https://status.twilio.com/incidents/6fvfxj2kqllz</id>
        <link href="https://status.twilio.com/incidents/6fvfxj2kqllz"/>
        <updated>2023-01-07T22:00:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jan  7, 14:00 PST
Completed - The scheduled maintenance has been completed.
Jan  7, 08:00 PST
In progress - Scheduled maintenance is currently in progress. We will provide updates as necessary.
Jan  2, 17:08 PST
Scheduled - The StarHub network in Singapore is conducting a planned maintenance from 07 January 2023 at 08:00 PST until 07 January 2023 at 14:00 PST. During the maintenance window, there could be intermittent delays delivering SMS to and from StarHub Singapore handsets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Twilio Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SMS Delivery Delays to Jawwal Network In Palestine]]></title>
        <id>https://status.twilio.com/incidents/jlhxs2s0bfj7</id>
        <link href="https://status.twilio.com/incidents/jlhxs2s0bfj7"/>
        <updated>2023-01-07T18:05:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jan  7, 10:05 PST
Update - We continue experiencing SMS delivery delays when sending messages to Jawwal Network in Palestine. Our engineers are working with our carrier partner to resolve the issue. We will provide another update in 16 hours or as soon as more information becomes available.
Jan  7, 02:06 PST
Update - We are continuing to experience SMS delivery delays when sending messages to Jawwal Network In Palestine. Our engineers are working with our carrier partner to resolve the issue. We will provide another update in 8 hours or as soon as more information becomes available.
Jan  6, 23:35 PST
Update - We are continuing to experience SMS delivery delays when sending messages to Jawwal Network In Palestine. Our engineers are working with our carrier partner to resolve the issue. We will provide another update in 4 hours or as soon as more information becomes available.
Jan  6, 21:35 PST
Update - We are continuing to experience SMS delivery delays when sending messages to Jawwal Network In Palestine. Our engineers are working with our carrier partner to resolve the issue. We will provide another update in 2 hours or as soon as more information becomes available.
Jan  6, 20:35 PST
Investigating - We are experiencing SMS delivery delays when sending messages to Jawwal Network In Palestine. Our engineers are working with our carrier partner to resolve the issue. We will provide another update in 1 hour or as soon as more information becomes available.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Twilio Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Inbound Call Failures to a Subset of Twilio Phone Numbers in Estonia]]></title>
        <id>https://status.twilio.com/incidents/5x1g1qyp65kr</id>
        <link href="https://status.twilio.com/incidents/5x1g1qyp65kr"/>
        <updated>2023-01-07T14:42:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jan  7, 06:42 PST
Resolved - The issue affecting inbound calls to Twilio phone numbers in Estonia has been resolved, and the service is functioning normally at this time.
Jan  7, 04:39 PST
Monitoring - We have started seeing recovery in a subset of call failures to Twilio phone numbers in Estonia. We will continue to monitor to ensure a full recovery. We expect to provide another update in 2 hours or as soon as more information becomes available.
Jan  7, 01:24 PST
Update - We are continuing to observe a subset of call failures to Twilio phone numbers in Estonia. We are currently working with our carrier partner to resolve the issue. We expect to provide another update in 16 hours or as soon as more information becomes available.
Jan  6, 17:34 PST
Update - We are continuing to observe a subset of call failures to Twilio phone numbers in Estonia. We are currently working with our carrier partner to resolve the issue. We expect to provide another update in 8 hours or as soon as more information becomes available.
Jan  6, 13:34 PST
Update - We are continuing to observe a subset of call failures to Twilio phone numbers in Estonia. We are currently working with our carrier partner to resolve the issue. We expect to provide another update in 4 hours or as soon as more information becomes available.
Jan  6, 11:33 PST
Update - We continue observing a subset of call failures to Twilio phone numbers Estonia. We are currently working with our carrier partner to resolve the issue. We expect to provide another update in 2 Hours or as soon as more information becomes available.
Jan  6, 10:45 PST
Investigating - We are observing a subset of call failures to Twilio phone numbers in Estonia. We are currently working with our carrier partner to resolve the issue. We expect to provide another update in 1 hours or as soon as more information becomes available.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Twilio Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SMS Delivery Report Delays when sending to STC Network In Saudi Arabia]]></title>
        <id>https://status.twilio.com/incidents/d0kjshfqh612</id>
        <link href="https://status.twilio.com/incidents/d0kjshfqh612"/>
        <updated>2023-01-07T08:12:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jan  7, 00:12 PST
Resolved - We are no longer experiencing  delays in receiving message delivery reports when sending to STC Network In Saudi Arabia.. This incident has been resolved.
Jan  6, 22:24 PST
Monitoring - We are observing recovery in delivery report delays when sending to STC Network In Saudi Arabia. We will continue monitoring the service to ensure a full recovery. We will provide another update in 2 hours or as soon as more information becomes available.
Jan  6, 20:24 PST
Update - We continue to experience delays in receiving message delivery reports when sending to STC Network In Saudi Arabia. Our engineers are working with our carrier partner to resolve the issue. We expect to provide another update in 2 hours or as soon as more information becomes available.
Jan  6, 19:24 PST
Investigating - We are experiencing delays in receiving message delivery reports when sending to STC Network In Saudi Arabia. Our engineers are working with our carrier partner to resolve the issue. We expect to provide another update in 1 hour or as soon as more information becomes available.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Twilio Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SMS Delivery Delays to Telefonica Colombia]]></title>
        <id>https://status.twilio.com/incidents/431761t25kt0</id>
        <link href="https://status.twilio.com/incidents/431761t25kt0"/>
        <updated>2023-01-07T00:48:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jan  6, 16:48 PST
Resolved - We are no longer experiencing SMS delivery delays when sending messages to Telefonica network in Colombia. This incident has been resolved.
Jan  6, 14:45 PST
Monitoring - We are observing recovery in SMS delivery delays when sending messages to Telefonica network in Colombia. We will continue monitoring the service to ensure a full recovery. We will provide another update in 2 hours or as soon as more information becomes available.
Jan  6, 11:28 PST
Update - We are still experiencing SMS delivery delays to Telefonica network in Colombia. Our engineers are working with our carrier partner to resolve the issue. We will provide another update in 4 hours or as soon as more information becomes available.
Jan  6, 09:41 PST
Update - We continue experiencing SMS delivery delays to Telefonica network in Colombia. Our engineers are working with our carrier partner to resolve the issue. We will provide another update in 2 hours or as soon as more information becomes available.
Jan  6, 08:44 PST
Update - We are experiencing SMS delivery delays to Telefonica network in Colombia. Our engineers are working with our carrier partner to resolve the issue. We will provide another update in 1 hour or as soon as more information becomes available.
Jan  6, 08:31 PST
Investigating - Our monitoring systems have detected a potential issue with delays delivering SMS to Telefonica in Colombia. Our engineering team has been alerted and is actively investigating. We will update as soon as we have more information.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Twilio Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multilingual Inbound SMS are Parsed Incorrectly, Corrupting the Text]]></title>
        <id>https://status.twilio.com/incidents/mwl35sx2v87d</id>
        <link href="https://status.twilio.com/incidents/mwl35sx2v87d"/>
        <updated>2023-01-06T12:31:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jan  6, 04:31 PST
Resolved - We are seeing complete recovery from the issue with multilingual inbound sms being parsed incorrectly, corrupting the text and the service is functioning normally at this time.
Jan  6, 02:31 PST
Monitoring - We are seeing recovery from the issue with multilingual inbound sms being parsed incorrectly, corrupting the text and are monitoring closely for any changes. We will provide another update in 2 hours or as soon as more information becomes available.
Jan  5, 23:05 PST
Update - Our engineers are continuing to investigate an issue with multilingual inbound sms being parsed incorrectly, corrupting the text. Our engineering team is actively investigating. We will update in 16 hours or as soon as we have more information.
Jan  5, 15:12 PST
Update - Our engineers …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Twilio Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Switzerland SMS Carrier Maintenance - Sunrise]]></title>
        <id>https://status.twilio.com/incidents/x462rfz5khb0</id>
        <link href="https://status.twilio.com/incidents/x462rfz5khb0"/>
        <updated>2023-01-06T01:00:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jan  5, 17:00 PST
Completed - The scheduled maintenance has been completed.
Jan  5, 15:00 PST
In progress - Scheduled maintenance is currently in progress. We will provide updates as necessary.
Jan  3, 11:19 PST
Scheduled - The Sunrise network in Switzerland is conducting an emergency maintenance from 05 January 2023 at 15:00 PST until 05 January 2023  at 17:00 PST. During the maintenance window, there could be intermittent delays delivering SMS to and from Sunrise Switzerland handsets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Twilio Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SMS Delivery Delays to Trimob Network]]></title>
        <id>https://status.twilio.com/incidents/d7zr2ffpwnfh</id>
        <link href="https://status.twilio.com/incidents/d7zr2ffpwnfh"/>
        <updated>2023-01-05T22:50:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jan  5, 14:50 PST
Resolved - We are no longer experiencing SMS delivery delays when sending messages to Trimob network in Ukraine. This incident has been resolved.
Jan  5, 12:52 PST
Monitoring - We are observing recovery in SMS delivery delays when sending messages to Trimob network in Ukraine. We will continue monitoring the service to ensure a full recovery. We will provide another update in 2 hours or as soon as more information becomes available.
Jan  5, 10:04 PST
Update - We are continuing to experience SMS delivery delays when sending messages to Trimob network in Ukraine. Our engineers are working with our carrier partner to resolve the issue. We will provide another update in 4 hours or as soon as more information becomes available.
Jan  5, 08:06 PST
Update - We are continuing to experience SMS delivery delays when sending messages to Trimob network in Ukraine. Our engineers are working with our carrier partner to resolve the issue. We will provide another update in 2 hours or as soon as more information becomes available.
Jan  5, 07:10 PST
Investigating - We are experiencing SMS delivery delays when sending messages to Trimob network in Ukraine. Our engineers are working with our carrier partner to resolve the issue. We will provide another update in 1 hour or as soon as more information becomes available.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Twilio Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Delay in email delivery due to third-party outage]]></title>
        <id>https://status.rippling.com/incidents/mbk89dt1vc41</id>
        <link href="https://status.rippling.com/incidents/mbk89dt1vc41"/>
        <updated>2023-01-05T15:49:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jan  5, 15:49 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Jan  5, 02:25 UTC
Monitoring - A fix has been implemented and we are monitoring the results.
Jan  5, 01:45 UTC
Update - We are continuing to monitor our third-party service provider for updates. Service has not been restored by the third-party email provider. Once service is restored, the majority of emails that were not sent during the outage will be resent.
Jan  5, 01:14 UTC
Update - We are continuing to monitor our third-party service provider for updates. Service has not been restored by the third-party email provider. Once service is restored, the majority of emails that were not sent during the outage will be resent.
Jan  5, 00:38 UTC
Update - Service has not been restored by the third-party email provider. Once service is restored, the majority of emails that were not sent during the outage will be resent.
Jan  5, 00:17 UTC
Identified - A fix has been implemented by the third-party service. We are working to confirm service has been restored.
Jan  4, 23:31 UTC
Investigating - Our third-party email delivery provider has been experiencing an outage since Jan 4th, 2:10 PM PST, causing a delay in notification delivery for all Rippling emails (including password resets). We are investigating this issue with the third-party provider.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rippling Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Issues completing a MFA authenticator challenge]]></title>
        <id>https://status.rippling.com/incidents/zgg7pyzjl7tr</id>
        <link href="https://status.rippling.com/incidents/zgg7pyzjl7tr"/>
        <updated>2023-01-03T23:07:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jan  3, 23:07 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Jan  3, 21:33 UTC
Monitoring - A fix has been implemented and we are monitoring the results.
Jan  3, 20:35 UTC
Identified - The issue has been identified and a fix is being implemented.
Jan  3, 20:27 UTC
Investigating - Users asked to complete an MFA challenge are unable to advance past the page. We are investigating this issue]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rippling Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RESOLVED: We are experiencing an issue with Gmail, Google Chat, Google Voice. Our engineering team continues to investigate the issue. We will provide an update by Tuesday, 2022-12-13 10:30 US/Pacific with current details.
Users may be facing unavailability for Gmail, Google Chat and Google Voice]]></title>
        <id>https://www.google.com/appsstatus/dashboard/incidents/tLjnxF7DdVTCicccdQtj</id>
        <link href="https://www.google.com/appsstatus/dashboard/incidents/tLjnxF7DdVTCicccdQtj"/>
        <updated>2023-01-03T20:28:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p> Incident began at <strong>2022-12-13 15:34</strong> and ended at <strong>2022-12-13 18:04</strong> <span>(times are in <strong>Coordinated Universal Time (UTC)</strong>).</span></p><div class="cBIRi14aVDP__status-update-text"><p>A combined Incident Report has been published on our Google Workspace Status Dashboard for this Incident - <a href="https://www.google.com/appsstatus/dashboard/incidents/AzeVS1iCHxhtzgi8r3mc">https://www.google.com/appsstatus/dashboard/incidents/AzeVS1iCHxhtzgi8r3mc</a></p>
</div><hr><p>Affected products: Gmail</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Workspace Status Dashboard Updates</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident with Codespaces]]></title>
        <id>https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/srn4b1fjxp8h</id>
        <link href="https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/srn4b1fjxp8h"/>
        <updated>2023-01-01T18:28:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jan  1, 18:28 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Jan  1, 17:28 UTC
Update - We have identified the issue and are deploying a fix. We will update our status when the fix is fully deployed.
Jan  1, 16:44 UTC
Update - Codespaces is experiencing issues with web connectivity from GitHub.com. The desktop client can still be used to launch or connect to codespaces."
Jan  1, 16:33 UTC
Investigating - We are investigating reports of degraded performance for Codespaces.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GitHub Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident with Codespaces]]></title>
        <id>https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/1whd66ydswnx</id>
        <link href="https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/1whd66ydswnx"/>
        <updated>2022-12-31T01:47:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dec 31, 01:47 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Dec 31, 01:39 UTC
Update - We are continuing mitigation for an issue impacting some Codespaces customers. We will keep you updated on progress.
Dec 31, 01:12 UTC
Update - We are continuing to work on mitigation for an issue impacting some Codespaces customers. We will continue to keep you updated on progress.
Dec 31, 00:39 UTC
Update - We identified an issue that impacts some Codespaces customers and are working on mitigation.We will continue to keep you updated on progress.
Dec 31, 00:07 UTC
Investigating - We are investigating reports of degraded performance for Codespaces.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GitHub Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MDM Enrollment not available for new macOS computers]]></title>
        <id>https://status.rippling.com/incidents/gmll739frv3b</id>
        <link href="https://status.rippling.com/incidents/gmll739frv3b"/>
        <updated>2022-12-22T19:55:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dec 22, 19:55 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Dec 22, 18:13 UTC
Update - We are continuing to monitor for any further issues.
Dec 22, 18:13 UTC
Monitoring - A fix has been implemented and we are monitoring the results.
Dec 22, 17:35 UTC
Identified - The issue has been identified and a fix is being implemented.
Dec 22, 17:12 UTC
Investigating - We are currently investigating this issue.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rippling Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Missing Workspace section in sidebar]]></title>
        <id>https://status.notion.so/incidents/3py88r008jjg</id>
        <link href="https://status.notion.so/incidents/3py88r008jjg"/>
        <updated>2022-12-21T18:31:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dec 21, 10:31 PST
Resolved - We have implemented the fix and confirmed the issue is resolved. Workspace section and pages have been restored to the sidebar for affected users.
Dec 21, 10:06 PST
Identified - Since ~3:30pm Pacific time yesterday, some users on Free and Plus plans have been unable to see pages in the Workspace section of the sidebar. We have identified the root cause and a fix is in progress.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Notion Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident: Messages on iOS are automatically marked as read]]></title>
        <id>https://status.slack.com//2022-12/4db4ec459abdd159</id>
        <link href="https://status.slack.com//2022-12/4db4ec459abdd159"/>
        <updated>2022-12-20T14:36:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Issue summary:

From Monday December 12, 2022 at 10:27 AM PST to Monday December 19, 2022 at 1:30 PM PST, we began investigating reports of messages being marked as read when backgrounding the iOS app while in a conversation. As a result, the sidebar would not show unread messages next to the DM/Channel/Threads view. 


We have now made a change on our end that resolved the issue and released a fix on iOS app version 22.12.21. Users on the iOS app should now be able to receive messages without them being marked as read automatically.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Slack System Status</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident with Actions]]></title>
        <id>https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/cb6ljbzhktxd</id>
        <link href="https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/cb6ljbzhktxd"/>
        <updated>2022-12-20T07:58:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dec 20, 07:58 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Dec 20, 07:23 UTC
Update - We are seeing delayed workflow job status updates for Actions. We are seeing the status update events being backed up and have applied a mitigation. We continue to monitor the delay.
Dec 20, 06:55 UTC
Investigating - We are investigating reports of degraded performance for Actions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GitHub Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident with Actions]]></title>
        <id>https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/3y3y8nnbyt2d</id>
        <link href="https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/3y3y8nnbyt2d"/>
        <updated>2022-12-20T01:38:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dec 20, 01:38 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Dec 20, 01:02 UTC
Update - We have identified the issue with manual workflow invocations from the UI. A mitigation will be deployed shortly.
Dec 20, 00:09 UTC
Investigating - We are investigating reports of degraded performance for Actions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GitHub Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Partial search failres]]></title>
        <id>https://status.notion.so/incidents/vwnxl4hd436q</id>
        <link href="https://status.notion.so/incidents/vwnxl4hd436q"/>
        <updated>2022-12-19T03:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dec 18, 19:00 PST
Resolved - From approximately 5pm Pacific time yesterday to 8:30am today, Notion experienced an issue that caused some search results to fail. This issue has been resolved.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Notion Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New feature - Check-in types !]]></title>
        <id>253029</id>
        <link href="https://changelog.bookingsync.com/new-feature-check-in-types-!-253029"/>
        <updated>2022-12-16T14:02:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New!
  
At Smily, we are here to help you Save time and Book more! That's why we are always thrilled to announce new features 🎉
Over the past few years, more and more channels have allowed you to set the check-in instructions, to coordinate a smooth and seamless arrival with your guests.
The check-in types were not synchronized with Smily, preventing you from adding this critical information to your listings.
After several requests and feedback, we created a new field on the rental base where you can add your check-in type. 

This feature is now synchronized with your website and our top partners, Airbnb, Booking.com, VRBO, and Expedia.
Add your check-in types in Smily and provide your guests with a smoother check-in experience!
For more details please follow the steps in this article
We invite you to discover all these new features, and we hope it will help you manage better your bookings, save time, and book more!
Wishing you all a pleasant day!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Zahra, Product manager, PMS team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Investigating reports of degraded performance.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/d5158f5wh1ly</id>
        <link href="https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/d5158f5wh1ly"/>
        <updated>2022-12-15T20:37:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dec 15, 20:37 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Dec 15, 20:31 UTC
Update - We are working on mitigating the issues loading content from raw.github.com
Dec 15, 20:00 UTC
Update - We are investigating issues loading content from raw.github.com
Dec 15, 20:00 UTC
Investigating - We are currently investigating this issue.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GitHub Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident with API Requests]]></title>
        <id>https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/pkbqcn8dp6dy</id>
        <link href="https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/pkbqcn8dp6dy"/>
        <updated>2022-12-15T20:00:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dec 15, 20:00 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Dec 15, 19:47 UTC
Update - We are investigating issues loading content from raw.github.com
Dec 15, 19:42 UTC
Investigating - We are investigating reports of degraded performance for API Requests.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GitHub Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident: Some users having trouble playing videos]]></title>
        <id>https://status.slack.com//2022-12/ddd9879de59fd9d1</id>
        <link href="https://status.slack.com//2022-12/ddd9879de59fd9d1"/>
        <updated>2022-12-15T18:39:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Issue summary: From December 13, 2022 at 11:46 AM PST to December 14, 2022 at 7:30 AM PST some customers may have experienced issues while playing videos.


We determined this issue was caused by a recent frontend change that caused a failure to load videos via the streaming protocol HLS (Hypertext Live Streaming), for which no fallback existed. 


To resolve this issue, we introduced a fallback to HLS allowing users to play video files with a slightly degraded experience, such as longer load times. 


Additionally, we disabled a code optimization technique which fully restored HLS functionality for all users.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Slack System Status</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident: Some users not receiving 2FA codes via SMS]]></title>
        <id>https://status.slack.com//2022-12/7e95e869e43429ae</id>
        <link href="https://status.slack.com//2022-12/7e95e869e43429ae"/>
        <updated>2022-12-15T01:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Issue Summary:


On December 14, 2022 from 4:30 AM PST to 9:00 AM PST, we received reports from customers who were unable to receive SMS 2FA codes to log into Slack. 


We discovered that the Slack queue on a third party 2FA service, and associated outgoing SMS message errors, were growing at a high rate. Customers who had enabled 2FA via SMS were affected in at least India, China, US, Brazil, and Argentina. We identified that a majority of traffic was coming from bad actors, whose requests led to unusually high volume for our queue. 


We prevented these individuals from accessing Slack, while our 2FA service provider implemented a change to further mitigate strain on our queue. These actions resolved the issue for all impacted customers.


Note: This summary has been edited since its initial posting to better align with Slack's communication guidelines.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Slack System Status</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident: Trouble connecting in Slack]]></title>
        <id>https://status.slack.com//2022-12/3404420180fb4113</id>
        <link href="https://status.slack.com//2022-12/3404420180fb4113"/>
        <updated>2022-12-14T22:00:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Issue summary:

From 10:12 AM PST until 10:25 AM PST on December 14, 2022, some customers had trouble loading Slack workspaces, sending messages, and uploading files.


Prior to this issue, we began removing traffic from an isolated location within a data center region as part of a planned exercise. Upon further investigation, we identified a bug within this process. We then stopped the process, which resolved the issue for all users. Error rates were monitored for a short while prior to announcing the resolution, in order to ensure the issue was fully resolved and would not reoccur.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Slack System Status</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident with Git Operations and Pull Requests]]></title>
        <id>https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/4p7zympgsr86</id>
        <link href="https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/4p7zympgsr86"/>
        <updated>2022-12-13T18:43:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dec 13, 18:43 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Dec 13, 18:35 UTC
Update - We have identified the issue impacting pull requests and git operations and are actively working on mitigations.
Dec 13, 17:39 UTC
Investigating - We are investigating reports of degraded performance for Git Operations and Pull Requests.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GitHub Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident with Issues and Pull Requests]]></title>
        <id>https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/6p0msrcyr3qt</id>
        <link href="https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/6p0msrcyr3qt"/>
        <updated>2022-12-10T03:00:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dec 10, 03:00 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Dec 10, 02:37 UTC
Investigating - We are investigating reports of degraded performance for Issues and Pull Requests.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GitHub Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>