<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2023-06-25T00:29:55.667Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2023-06-25T00:29:55.667Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident: Users may be experiencing increased loading time or delays when switching between channels]]></title>
        <id>https://status.slack.com//2023-06/a8931305c8cbcf0e</id>
        <link href="https://status.slack.com//2023-06/a8931305c8cbcf0e"/>
        <updated>2023-06-24T00:09:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We have released a fix at this time, and customers should no longer be experiencing delays when loading channels, conversation history, or when switching between channels. Please send a note to feedback@slack.com if you continue to have any trouble.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Slack System Status</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident: Trouble with Google Calendar and Outlook Calendar App]]></title>
        <id>https://status.slack.com//2023-06/4edd40b2f4290679</id>
        <link href="https://status.slack.com//2023-06/4edd40b2f4290679"/>
        <updated>2023-06-16T12:00:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Issue summary:

From June 13, 2023 at 12:30 PM PDT until June 15, 2023 at 2:30 AM PDT, some users may have experienced issues with statuses, reminders and agendas failing to sync from their Google Calendar and Outlook Calendar apps.


These issues were due to an outage from an upstream service provider which affected many services. The provider actively worked to remediate those issues, which then fully resolved the reported failures for impacted Slack users.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Slack System Status</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident: Some users may notice slow performance throughout Slack]]></title>
        <id>https://status.slack.com//2023-06/7363f55dbcde89c1</id>
        <link href="https://status.slack.com//2023-06/7363f55dbcde89c1"/>
        <updated>2023-06-15T23:28:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Issue summary:


On June 15, 2023 from 8:10 AM PDT to around 8:20 AM PDT, some users may have experienced slow performance and errors while loading conversations, sending messages and taking other actions in Slack.


We traced the issue to a recent code change which caused connection failures. We reverted this change and all affected functionality should be restored for users. Thank you for your patience while we resolved this issue.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Slack System Status</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RESOLVED: We're aware of a problem with Admin Console affecting a subset of Google Workspace Administrators. Some Google Workspace Administrators may experience issues when performing List, Create, Update, or Delete operations for OrgUnits using the Admin Console or Directory APIs. Attempting to navigate to the admin.google.com/ac/users/]]></title>
        <id>https://www.google.com/appsstatus/dashboard/incidents/1jNfhkFKus49vEyaUQLm</id>
        <link href="https://www.google.com/appsstatus/dashboard/incidents/1jNfhkFKus49vEyaUQLm"/>
        <updated>2023-06-15T21:23:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p> Incident began at <strong>2023-06-02 19:25</strong> and ended at <strong>2023-06-03 11:57</strong> <span>(times are in <strong>Coordinated Universal Time (UTC)</strong>).</span></p><div class="cBIRi14aVDP__status-update-text"><h1>Incident Report</h1>
<h2>Summary</h2>
<p>From Friday, 2 June 2023 to Saturday, 3 June 2023, some Google Workspace Administrators experienced issues performing List, Create, Update, or Delete operations for users and organizational units (OU) when using the Admin Console or Directory APIs. The total outage duration was 16 hours and 32 minutes. We have conducted an internal investigation and are taking steps to improve our service.</p>
<h2>Root Cause</h2>
<p>The Google Workspace Admin Console and Directory APIs use a backend service to authorize requests to create/update/delete/read user and OU resources. A workflow synchronizes user and OU resources to that backend authorization service.</p>
<p>On Friday, 2 June 2023 at 12:25 PDT, engineers rolled out a configuration change that inadvertently caused the workflow to stop synchronizing resources to the authorization service. Because the authorization service was not aware of the new resources (those created during the outage), it was unable to authorize requests and returned a 403 Unauthorized error. The incorrect configuration went undetected before being deployed to production because the automatic pre-submit checks had been suppressed because engineers incorrectly believed the change was safe.</p>
<h2>Remediation and Prevention</h2>
<p>Google engineers were alerted to the outage via a support case on 2 June 2023 at 19:33 PDT and immediately started an investigation. Engineers identified that the roll out of the configuration change aligned with the start of 403 Unauthorized errors and initiated a rollback on 3 June 2023 at 00:14 PDT. The rollback completed at 00:57 PDT, mitigating the issue for new users and OU resources created after that time. Engineers performed a backfill to synchronize the impacted users and OU resources that were created after the start of the issue, fully mitigating the issue at 04:57 PDT.</p>
<p>Google is committed preventing a repeat of this issue in the future and is completing the following actions:</p>
<ul>
<li>We will be updating the pre-submit checks for workflow configuration changes to better identify potential issues before rolling out to production.</li>
<li>We will be adding a requirement to have a designated reviewer approve workflow configuration changes to ensure that automated presubmit checks are being run before rolling out to production.</li>
</ul>
<h2>Detailed Description of Impact</h2>
<p>From 2 June 2023 at 12:25 PDT to 3 June 2023 at 04:57, Google Workspace Administrators may have experienced 403 Unauthorized errors when attempting to perform actions for user and OU resources via Admin Console or Directory APIs. This issue affected Create, Fetch, Update, Delete and other related operations for user and OU resources created between 2 June 2023 at 12:25 PDT and 3 June 2023 at 00:57 PDT.</p>
</div><hr><p>Affected products: Admin Console</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Workspace Status Dashboard Updates</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident: Trouble with workflows, loading channels and accessing Slack]]></title>
        <id>https://status.slack.com//2023-06/20df18536cc9524b</id>
        <link href="https://status.slack.com//2023-06/20df18536cc9524b"/>
        <updated>2023-06-15T18:31:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Issue Summary:

From June 14, 2023 at 3:44 PM PDT until June 15, 2023 at 4:30 AM PDT, some customers may have been unable to send messages, join Huddles, run workflows, and access Slack.


A recent code change caused some resources on our backend web hosting service to be temporarily exhausted. Due to this, users experienced errors when joining Huddles, sending messages, and may have had their connection to Slack reset. We identified the issue and reverted the change restoring full functionality to these features.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Slack System Status</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident: Trouble with workflows and clips transcripts]]></title>
        <id>https://status.slack.com//2023-06/a0c185e5ad5eac55</id>
        <link href="https://status.slack.com//2023-06/a0c185e5ad5eac55"/>
        <updated>2023-06-14T03:06:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Issue summary: 

On June 13, 2023 from 11:55 AM PDT to around 3:47 PM PDT, some users may have experienced failure with clips transcribing and transcoding, execution of workflows with custom functions, new deployments of apps with hosted functions, and some delay when using canvases in Slack. 


These issues were due to an outage from an upstream service provider which affected many services. The provider actively worked to remediate those issues, which then fully resolved the reported failures for impacted Slack users.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Slack System Status</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident: Small number of users might be experiencing connectivity issues]]></title>
        <id>https://status.slack.com//2023-06/1bd97a73cb7874f1</id>
        <link href="https://status.slack.com//2023-06/1bd97a73cb7874f1"/>
        <updated>2023-06-12T14:56:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On June 11, 2023 from 10:57 AM PDT to 12:10 PM PDT, some users may have experienced difficulties when trying to access Slack due to a database issue.


The underlying cause has since been determined and remediation steps were applied. This resolved the above for all impacted users.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Slack System Status</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident: Some files may not be unfurling as expected]]></title>
        <id>https://status.slack.com//2023-06/6cb0bb4f227a82e8</id>
        <link href="https://status.slack.com//2023-06/6cb0bb4f227a82e8"/>
        <updated>2023-06-06T11:15:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Thank you for your patience while our team investigated this. All new file uploads are now expected to generate thumbnails for affected users and the issue has been resolved. Please note that previous attempts won't be retried, however new files should function as normal.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Slack System Status</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident: Issues with Workflow Builder]]></title>
        <id>https://status.slack.com//2023-06/f7c5d1e455e95466</id>
        <link href="https://status.slack.com//2023-06/f7c5d1e455e95466"/>
        <updated>2023-06-05T09:01:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Issue summary:


On June 02, 2023 from 3:28 PM PDT to around 5:29 PM PDT, some customers may have experienced large empty spaces in the Workflow Builder UI and issues with publishing/adding or editing steps in a workflow. 


We traced the issue to a recent code change which caused the channel selector to appear out of view, resulting in the inability to take certain actions while editing a workflow. 


We reverted the change which solved the issue for all customers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Slack System Status</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident: Some users are reporting issues triggering shortcut Workflows]]></title>
        <id>https://status.slack.com//2023-05/d3da25ad25333a58</id>
        <link href="https://status.slack.com//2023-05/d3da25ad25333a58"/>
        <updated>2023-06-01T18:00:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Issue summary:


From May 19, 2023 at 12:00 AM PDT until May 25, 2023 at 8:00 AM PDT, some users may have experienced issues triggering shortcut workflows.


We carried out our investigation and determined that cached data on the back end temporarily broke legacy workflows. In the process of determining our path to a resolution the issue resolved itself. We are taking the necessary steps to prevent similar issues in the future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Slack System Status</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident: Users reporting issues with keyboard shortcuts]]></title>
        <id>https://status.slack.com//2023-05/223e97529097de1c</id>
        <link href="https://status.slack.com//2023-05/223e97529097de1c"/>
        <updated>2023-06-01T05:57:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Issue summary:

On May 31, 2023 from 5:15 PM PDT to 7:12 PM PDT, some customers experienced issues with using keyboard shortcuts. 


We’ve traced that this issue was caused by a recent code change. We’ve rolled back this change, resolving the issue for all impacted customers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Slack System Status</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident: Autocomplete results ranking in search degraded]]></title>
        <id>https://status.slack.com//2023-05/aa025f4aef896b16</id>
        <link href="https://status.slack.com//2023-05/aa025f4aef896b16"/>
        <updated>2023-05-31T23:27:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Issue summary:

From May 30th, 2023 at 8:02 AM PDT until 11:18 AM PDT, some users experienced unexpected behavior with autocomplete suggestions, including incorrect rankings & incomplete results when conducting searches.


We traced the source of the issue back to an error that occurred in our autocomplete cache. A fix was rolled out to our search logic which began to show the correct results.


Users can refresh their Slack client (by pressing Cmd/Ctrl + Shift + R) if they are still experiencing issues. We apologize for any interruption.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Slack System Status</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident: Reacji Channeler app is failing for some users]]></title>
        <id>https://status.slack.com//2023-05/0848cba206ef2188</id>
        <link href="https://status.slack.com//2023-05/0848cba206ef2188"/>
        <updated>2023-05-31T23:04:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Issue summary:

From May 30th, 2023 at around 8:00 PM PDT until May 31st, 2023 at 9:20 AM PDT, users with the Reacji Channeler app installed in their workspace experienced some issues where the app would not execute.


The issue was traced back to a recent change that occurred for one of our app databases. This caused the app to accept new requests even though it was unable to connect to the database, resulting in timeout errors. 


We reverted the change and restarted the backend processes which allowed the app to connect to the database again, resolving the issue for impacted users. We apologize for any disruptions to your day.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Slack System Status</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>