<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2023-01-04T00:21:40.673Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2023-01-04T00:21:40.673Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Twilio Voice Maintenance]]></title>
        <id>https://status.twilio.com/incidents/15dcfvt442x3</id>
        <link href="https://status.twilio.com/incidents/15dcfvt442x3"/>
        <updated>2023-01-04T05:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[THIS IS A SCHEDULED EVENT Jan 3, 21:00 PST  -  Jan 4, 00:00 PST
Dec 31, 11:49 PST
Scheduled - Twilio is conducting a planned maintenance from 03 January 2023 at 21:00 PST until 04 January at 00:00 PST. During the maintenance window, there could be intermittent call failures to and from Twilio.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Twilio Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SMS Delivery Receipt Delays to Globe Network In Philippines Over Pre-Registered International Sender IDs]]></title>
        <id>https://status.twilio.com/incidents/0nkgvzthx433</id>
        <link href="https://status.twilio.com/incidents/0nkgvzthx433"/>
        <updated>2023-01-03T23:25:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jan  3, 15:25 PST
Monitoring - We are observing recovery from the issue causing SMS delivery receipt delays when sending messages to Globe Network In Philippines over pre-registered international sender IDs. We will continue monitoring the service to ensure a full recovery. We will provide another update in 2 hours or as soon as more information becomes available.
Jan  3, 14:30 PST
Update - We continue to experience SMS delivery receipt delays when sending messages to Globe Network In Philippines over pre-registered international sender IDs. Our engineers are working with our carrier partner to resolve the issue. We will provide another update in 8 hours or as soon as more information becomes available.
Jan  3, 10:30 PST
Update - We continue to experience SMS delivery receipt delays when sending messages to Globe Network In Philippines over Pre-Registered International Sender IDs. Our engineers are working with our carrier partner to resolve the issue. We will provide another update in 4 hours or as soon as more information becomes available.
Jan  3, 08:33 PST
Update - We are experiencing SMS delivery receipt delays when sending messages to Globe Network In Philippines over Pre-Registered International Sender IDs. Our engineers are working with our carrier partner to resolve the issue. We will provide another update in 2 hours or as soon as more information becomes available.
Jan  3, 07:33 PST
Update - We are experiencing SMS delivery receipt delays when sending messages to Globe Network In Philippines over Pre-Registered International Sender IDs. Our engineers are working with our carrier partner to resolve the issue. We will provide another update in 1 hour or as soon as more information becomes available.
Jan  3, 07:29 PST
Investigating - Our monitoring systems have detected a potential issue with SMS. Our engineering team has been alerted and is actively investigating. We will update as soon as we have more information.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Twilio Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Issues completing a MFA authenticator challenge]]></title>
        <id>https://status.rippling.com/incidents/zgg7pyzjl7tr</id>
        <link href="https://status.rippling.com/incidents/zgg7pyzjl7tr"/>
        <updated>2023-01-03T23:07:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jan  3, 23:07 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Jan  3, 21:33 UTC
Monitoring - A fix has been implemented and we are monitoring the results.
Jan  3, 20:35 UTC
Identified - The issue has been identified and a fix is being implemented.
Jan  3, 20:27 UTC
Investigating - Users asked to complete an MFA challenge are unable to advance past the page. We are investigating this issue]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rippling Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SMS Delivery Delays To Etisalat Network (412-50) In Afghanistan]]></title>
        <id>https://status.twilio.com/incidents/zcbft52kgmv2</id>
        <link href="https://status.twilio.com/incidents/zcbft52kgmv2"/>
        <updated>2023-01-03T22:30:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jan  3, 14:30 PST
Update - We are continuing to work with our carrier partner to investigate the issue causing SMS delivery delays when sending messages to the Etisalat network in Afghanistan. We expect to provide another update in 4 hours or as soon as more information becomes available.
Jan  3, 12:30 PST
Update - We are continuing to work with our carrier partner to investigate the issue causing SMS delivery delays when sending messages to the Etisalat network in Afghanistan. We expect to provide another update in 2 hours or as soon as more information becomes available.
Jan  3, 11:36 PST
Investigating - We are experiencing SMS delivery delays when sending messages to Etisalat network in Afghanistan. Our engineers are working with our carrier partner to resolve the issue. We will provide another update in 1 hour or as soon as more information becomes available.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Twilio Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RESOLVED: We are experiencing an issue with Gmail, Google Chat, Google Voice. Our engineering team continues to investigate the issue. We will provide an update by Tuesday, 2022-12-13 10:30 US/Pacific with current details.
Users may be facing unavailability for Gmail, Google Chat and Google Voice]]></title>
        <id>https://www.google.com/appsstatus/dashboard/incidents/tLjnxF7DdVTCicccdQtj</id>
        <link href="https://www.google.com/appsstatus/dashboard/incidents/tLjnxF7DdVTCicccdQtj"/>
        <updated>2023-01-03T20:28:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p> Incident began at <strong>2022-12-13 15:34</strong> and ended at <strong>2022-12-13 18:04</strong> <span>(times are in <strong>Coordinated Universal Time (UTC)</strong>).</span></p><div class="cBIRi14aVDP__status-update-text"><p>A combined Incident Report has been published on our Google Workspace Status Dashboard for this Incident - <a href="https://www.google.com/appsstatus/dashboard/incidents/AzeVS1iCHxhtzgi8r3mc">https://www.google.com/appsstatus/dashboard/incidents/AzeVS1iCHxhtzgi8r3mc</a></p>
</div><hr><p>Affected products: Gmail</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Workspace Status Dashboard Updates</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RESOLVED: We are experiencing an issue with Google Voice. Our engineering team continues to investigate the issue. We will provide an update by Tuesday, 2022-12-13 10:30 US/Pacific with current details.
For more information please refer to : https://www.google.com/appsstatus/dashboard/incidents/tLjnxF7DdVTCicccdQtj]]></title>
        <id>https://www.google.com/appsstatus/dashboard/incidents/t6TinwQsJNj7AuSoMmmJ</id>
        <link href="https://www.google.com/appsstatus/dashboard/incidents/t6TinwQsJNj7AuSoMmmJ"/>
        <updated>2023-01-03T20:28:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p> Incident began at <strong>2022-12-13 15:34</strong> and ended at <strong>2022-12-13 18:04</strong> <span>(times are in <strong>Coordinated Universal Time (UTC)</strong>).</span></p><div class="cBIRi14aVDP__status-update-text"><p>A combined Incident Report has been published on our Google Workspace Status Dashboard for this Incident - <a href="https://www.google.com/appsstatus/dashboard/incidents/AzeVS1iCHxhtzgi8r3mc">https://www.google.com/appsstatus/dashboard/incidents/AzeVS1iCHxhtzgi8r3mc</a></p>
</div><hr><p>Affected products: Google Voice</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Workspace Status Dashboard Updates</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RESOLVED: We are experiencing an issue with Google Chat. Our engineering team continues to investigate the issue. We will provide an update by Tuesday, 2022-12-13 10:30 US/Pacific with current details.
For more information please refer to : https://www.google.com/appsstatus/dashboard/incidents/tLjnxF7DdVTCicccdQtj]]></title>
        <id>https://www.google.com/appsstatus/dashboard/incidents/AzeVS1iCHxhtzgi8r3mc</id>
        <link href="https://www.google.com/appsstatus/dashboard/incidents/AzeVS1iCHxhtzgi8r3mc"/>
        <updated>2023-01-03T20:08:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p> Incident began at <strong>2022-12-13 15:34</strong> and ended at <strong>2022-12-13 18:04</strong> <span>(times are in <strong>Coordinated Universal Time (UTC)</strong>).</span></p><div class="cBIRi14aVDP__status-update-text"><h1>Incident Report</h1>
<h2>Summary</h2>
<p>On Tuesday, 13 December 2022 at 07:34 PT, users of Gmail, Google Voice, and Google Chat experienced disruption in their services for a period of 2 hours and 30 minutes. To our Google Workspace customers who were impacted during this disruption, we sincerely apologize. This is not the level of quality and reliability we strive to offer you, and we have conducted an internal investigation and are taking immediate steps to improve the resiliency of our service.</p>
<h2>Root Cause</h2>
<p>The issue was caused by an unanticipated increase in traffic to the internal user ID management system used by multiple Google Workspace products. Upon further investigation, we identified that the overwhelming amount of traffic resulted from erroneous changes made to update the membership details from one of the upstream systems.</p>
<h2>Remediation and Prevention</h2>
<p>Google engineers were alerted to this issue through automated monitoring, which also blocked the incoming traffic simultaneously within a few minutes. However, the high traffic during this period impacted downstream services.</p>
<p>Google is committed preventing a repeat of this issue in the future and is completing the following actions:</p>
<ul>
<li>Change the design in the internal user ID management system to not remove users, unless mentioned explicitly as allowed.</li>
<li>Introduce multiple redundancies in the system, including self-throttling auto-kill mechanisms in the involved systems to keep the traffic under a defined threshold.</li>
<li>Introduce robust control and process reviews for data changes.</li>
</ul>
<p>Google is committed to quickly and continually improving our technology and operations to prevent service disruptions. We appreciate your patience and apologize again for the impact to your organization. We thank you for your business.</p>
<h2>Detailed Description of Impact</h2>
<p>On Tuesday, 13 December 2022 between 07:34 and 10:04 PT, various Google Workspace products (noted below) experienced impact in their services:</p>
<h3>Google Chat</h3>
<ul>
<li>Some users observed incorrect status indicators representing their presence and typing status.</li>
</ul>
<h3>Google Voice</h3>
<p>Users experienced impact in various telephony services:</p>
<ul>
<li>Some SMS messages were delayed by an average of 1.2 minutes.</li>
<li>A limited number of Session Initiation Protocol (SIP) registrations were not completed. Affected user devices may have been temporarily unable to place or receive calls.</li>
<li>Active call queue processing was delayed, which may have resulted in delayed call history, billing, or voicemail delivery for some users.</li>
</ul>
<h3>Gmail</h3>
<ul>
<li>A few users experienced intermittent issues signing in and temporary errors.</li>
</ul>
</div><hr><p>Affected products: Google Chat</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Workspace Status Dashboard Updates</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[France SMS Carrier Maintenance - Bouygues Telecom]]></title>
        <id>https://status.twilio.com/incidents/801l1fwhxq3y</id>
        <link href="https://status.twilio.com/incidents/801l1fwhxq3y"/>
        <updated>2023-01-03T05:47:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jan  2, 21:47 PST
Completed - The scheduled maintenance has been completed.
Jan  2, 21:00 PST
In progress - Scheduled maintenance is currently in progress. We will provide updates as necessary.
Dec 23, 21:06 PST
Scheduled - The Bouygues Telecom network in France is conducting a planned maintenance from 02 January 2023 at 21:00 PST until 02 January 2023 at 21:45 PST. During the maintenance window, there could be intermittent delays delivering SMS to and from Bouygues Telecom handsets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Twilio Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MMS Delivery Delays to USA via a Subset of Short Codes]]></title>
        <id>https://status.twilio.com/incidents/d44y6pcfd278</id>
        <link href="https://status.twilio.com/incidents/d44y6pcfd278"/>
        <updated>2023-01-03T00:00:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jan  2, 16:00 PST
Resolved - The issue that caused MMS Delivery Delays to the USA via a subset of short codes is now resolved.
Jan  2, 14:02 PST
Monitoring - We are observing recovery from the issue causing MMS Delivery Delays to USA via a subset of short codes. We will continue monitoring the service to ensure a full recovery. We will provide another update in 2 hours or as soon as more information becomes available.
Jan  2, 13:35 PST
Update - We are experiencing MMS Delivery Delays to USA via a subset of short codes. Our engineers are working with our carrier partner to resolve the issue. We expect to provide another update in 1 hour or as soon as more information becomes available.
Jan  2, 13:28 PST
Investigating - Our monitoring systems have detected a potential issue with MMS Delivery Delays to the USA via a subset of short codes. Our engineering team has been alerted and is actively investigating. We will update as soon as we have more information.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Twilio Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SMS Delivery Delays to Beeline Tajikistan]]></title>
        <id>https://status.twilio.com/incidents/0fyzg1ctwzx6</id>
        <link href="https://status.twilio.com/incidents/0fyzg1ctwzx6"/>
        <updated>2023-01-02T23:30:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jan  2, 15:30 PST
Resolved - The issue that caused SMS delivery delays when sending messages to Beeline Tajikistan is now resolved.
Jan  2, 13:30 PST
Monitoring - A fix has been implemented for the issue causing SMS delivery delays when sending messages to Beeline Tajikistan, and we are monitoring results.  We will provide another update in 2 hours.
Jan  2, 05:30 PST
Update - We are continuing to experience SMS delivery delays when sending messages to Beeline Tajikistan. Our engineers are working with our carrier partner to resolve the issue. We will provide another update in 8 hours or as soon as more information becomes available.
Jan  2, 01:30 PST
Update - We are continuing to experience SMS delivery delays when sending messages to Beeline Tajikistan. Our engineers are working with our carrier partner to resolve the issue. We will provide another update in 4 hours or as soon as more information becomes available.
Jan  1, 23:31 PST
Update - We continue to experience SMS delivery delays when sending messages to Beeline Tajikistan. Our engineers are working with our carrier partner to resolve the issue. We will provide another update in 2 hours or as soon as more information becomes available.
Jan  1, 22:31 PST
Investigating - We are experiencing SMS delivery delays when sending messages to Beeline Tajikistan. Our engineers are working with our carrier partner to resolve the issue. We will provide another update in 1 hour or as soon as more information becomes available.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Twilio Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident with Codespaces]]></title>
        <id>https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/srn4b1fjxp8h</id>
        <link href="https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/srn4b1fjxp8h"/>
        <updated>2023-01-01T18:28:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jan  1, 18:28 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Jan  1, 17:28 UTC
Update - We have identified the issue and are deploying a fix. We will update our status when the fix is fully deployed.
Jan  1, 16:44 UTC
Update - Codespaces is experiencing issues with web connectivity from GitHub.com. The desktop client can still be used to launch or connect to codespaces."
Jan  1, 16:33 UTC
Investigating - We are investigating reports of degraded performance for Codespaces.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GitHub Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SMS Delivery Receipt Delays To SFR Network in France]]></title>
        <id>https://status.twilio.com/incidents/6ryyd1w2b367</id>
        <link href="https://status.twilio.com/incidents/6ryyd1w2b367"/>
        <updated>2023-01-01T04:51:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dec 31, 20:51 PST
Resolved - We are no longer experiencing delays in receiving message delivery reports when sending to SFR Network in France. This incident has been resolved.
Dec 31, 18:48 PST
Monitoring - We are observing recovery in receiving message delivery reports when sending to SFR Network in France. We will continue monitoring the service to ensure a full recovery. We will provide another update in 2 hours or as soon as more information becomes available.
Dec 31, 17:03 PST
Update - We continue to experience delays in receiving message delivery reports when sending to SFR Network in France. Our engineers are working with our carrier partner to resolve the issue. We expect to provide another update in 2 hours or as soon as more information becomes available.
Dec 31, 16:10 PST
Update - We are experiencing delays in receiving message delivery reports when sending to SFR Network in France. Our engineers are working with our carrier partner to resolve the issue. We expect to provide another update in 1 hour or as soon as more information becomes available.
Dec 31, 15:41 PST
Investigating - Our monitoring systems have detected a potential issue with SMS Delivery Receipt  Delays To SFR Network in France. Our engineering team has been alerted and is actively investigating. We will update as soon as we have more information.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Twilio Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Inbound SMS Delays From Subset of Australia Phone Numbers]]></title>
        <id>https://status.twilio.com/incidents/9h01k697ykw5</id>
        <link href="https://status.twilio.com/incidents/9h01k697ykw5"/>
        <updated>2022-12-31T21:35:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dec 31, 13:35 PST
Resolved - The issue affecting inbound SMS delays when receiving messages from a subset of phone numbers in Australia has been resolved, and the service is functioning normally at this time.
Dec 31, 11:40 PST
Monitoring - We have started seeing recovery for the issue causing inbound SMS delays when receiving messages from a subset of phone numbers in Australia. Our engineers are working with the carrier to ensure service stability. We will provide another update in 2 hours or as soon as more information becomes available.
Dec 31, 10:49 PST
Update - We continue experiencing inbound SMS delays when receiving messages from a subset of phone numbers in Australia. Our engineers are working with our carrier partner to resolve the issue. We will provide another update in 8 hours or as soon as more information becomes available.
Dec 31, 06:51 PST
Update - We are still experiencing inbound SMS delays when receiving messages from a subset of phone numbers in Australia. Our engineers are working with our carrier partner to resolve the issue. We will provide another update in 4 hours or as soon as more information becomes available.
Dec 31, 04:52 PST
Investigating - We are experiencing Inbound SMS Delays when receiving messages from a subset of Australia phone numbers. Our engineers are working with our carrier partner to resolve the issue. We will provide another update in 2 hours or as soon as more information becomes available.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Twilio Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SMS Delivery Delays to Africell Network in Multiple Countries]]></title>
        <id>https://status.twilio.com/incidents/jyjyg441wylh</id>
        <link href="https://status.twilio.com/incidents/jyjyg441wylh"/>
        <updated>2022-12-31T13:52:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dec 31, 05:52 PST
Resolved - We are no longer experiencing SMS delivery delays when sending messages to Africell Network in Multiple Countries. This incident has been resolved.
Dec 31, 03:58 PST
Update - We are observing recovery in SMS delivery delays when sending messages to Africell Network in Multiple Countries. We will continue monitoring the service to ensure a full recovery. We will provide another update in 2 hours or as soon as more information becomes available.
Dec 31, 02:03 PST
Monitoring - We are observing recovery in SMS delivery delays when sending messages to Africell Network in Multiple Countries. We will continue monitoring the service to ensure a full recovery. We will provide another update in 2 hours or as soon as more information becomes available.
Dec 31, 00:10 PST
U…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Twilio Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SMS Delivery Delays to Orange Network in Dominican Republic]]></title>
        <id>https://status.twilio.com/incidents/bjvl8b5xxgn8</id>
        <link href="https://status.twilio.com/incidents/bjvl8b5xxgn8"/>
        <updated>2022-12-31T12:28:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dec 31, 04:28 PST
Resolved - We are no longer experiencing SMS delivery delays when sending messages to Orange Network in Dominican Republic. This incident has been resolved.
Dec 31, 02:41 PST
Monitoring - We are observing recovery in SMS delivery delays when sending messages to Orange Network in Dominican Republic. We will continue monitoring the service to ensure a full recovery. We will provide another update in 2 hours or as soon as more information becomes available.
Dec 30, 23:27 PST
Update - We are continuing to experience SMS delivery delays when sending messages to Orange Network in Dominican Republic. Our engineers are working with our carrier partner to resolve the issue. We will provide another update in 8 hours or as soon as more information becomes available.
Dec 30, 19:27 PST
Update - We are continuing to experience SMS delivery delays when sending messages to Orange Network in Dominican Republic. Our engineers are working with our carrier partner to resolve the issue. We will provide another update in 4 hours or as soon as more information becomes available.
Dec 30, 17:28 PST
Update - We continue to experience SMS delivery delays when sending messages to Orange Network in Dominican Republic. Our engineers are working with our carrier partner to resolve the issue. We will provide another update in 2 hour or as soon as more information becomes available.
Dec 30, 16:33 PST
Update - We are experiencing SMS delivery delays when sending messages to Orange Network in Dominican Republic. Our engineers are working with our carrier partner to resolve the issue. We will provide another update in 1 hour or as soon as more information becomes available.
Dec 30, 16:27 PST
Investigating - Our monitoring systems have detected a potential issue with SMS Delivery Delays to Orange Network in Dominican Republic. Our engineering team has been alerted and is actively investigating. We will update as soon as we have more information.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Twilio Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SMS Delivery Delays to Ncell Network in Nepal]]></title>
        <id>https://status.twilio.com/incidents/qtmz63bb6c2d</id>
        <link href="https://status.twilio.com/incidents/qtmz63bb6c2d"/>
        <updated>2022-12-31T12:06:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dec 31, 04:06 PST
Resolved - We are no longer experiencing SMS delivery delays when sending messages to Ncell Network in Nepal. This incident has been resolved.
Dec 31, 03:15 PST
Update - We are observing recovery in SMS delivery delays when sending messages to Ncell Network in Nepal. We will continue monitoring the service to ensure a full recovery. We will provide another update in 2 hours or as soon as more information becomes available.
Dec 31, 01:24 PST
Monitoring - We are observing recovery in SMS delivery delays when sending messages to Ncell Network in Nepal. We will continue monitoring the service to ensure a full recovery. We will provide another update in 2 hours or as soon as more information becomes available.
Dec 30, 21:54 PST
Update - We are continuing to experience SMS delivery delays when sending messages to Ncell Network in Nepal. Our engineers are working with our carrier partner to resolve the issue. We will provide another update in 4 hours or as soon as more information becomes available.
Dec 30, 19:54 PST
Update - We are continuing to experience SMS delivery delays when sending messages to Ncell Network in Nepal. Our engineers are working with our carrier partner to resolve the issue. We will provide another update in 2 hours or as soon as more information becomes available.
Dec 30, 18:54 PST
Investigating - We are experiencing SMS delivery delays when sending messages to Ncell Network in Nepal. Our engineers are working with our carrier partner to resolve the issue. We will provide another update in 1 hour or as soon as more information becomes available.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Twilio Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SMS Delivery Delay to Cellcom and Pelephone Network in Israel]]></title>
        <id>https://status.twilio.com/incidents/fvtvjbm3dqjp</id>
        <link href="https://status.twilio.com/incidents/fvtvjbm3dqjp"/>
        <updated>2022-12-31T12:04:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dec 31, 04:04 PST
Resolved - We are no longer experiencing SMS delivery delays when sending messages to Cellcom and Pelephone Networks in Israel. This incident has been resolved.
Dec 31, 02:14 PST
Monitoring - We are observing recovery in SMS delivery delays when sending messages to Cellcom and Pelephone Networks in Israel. We will continue monitoring the service to ensure a full recovery. We will provide another update in 2 hours or as soon as more information becomes available.
Dec 30, 23:47 PST
Update - We are continuing to experience SMS delivery delays when sending messages to Cellcom and Pelephone Networks in Israel. Our engineers are working with our carrier partner to resolve the issue. We will provide another update in 8 hours or as soon as more information becomes available.
Dec …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Twilio Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SMS Delivery Delays to TNM Network in Malawi]]></title>
        <id>https://status.twilio.com/incidents/8hglmfw28lg1</id>
        <link href="https://status.twilio.com/incidents/8hglmfw28lg1"/>
        <updated>2022-12-31T10:38:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dec 31, 02:38 PST
Resolved - We are no longer experiencing SMS delivery delays when sending messages to TNM Network in Malawi. This incident has been resolved.
Dec 31, 01:06 PST
Update - We are observing recovery in SMS delivery delays when sending messages to TNM Network in Malawi. We will continue monitoring the service to ensure a full recovery. We will provide another update in 2 hours or as soon as more information becomes available.
Dec 30, 23:17 PST
Monitoring - We are observing recovery in SMS delivery delays when sending messages to TNM Network in Malawi. We will continue monitoring the service to ensure a full recovery. We will provide another update in 2 hours or as soon as more information becomes available.
Dec 30, 21:58 PST
Update - We are continuing to experience SMS delivery delays when sending messages to TNM Network in Malawi. Our engineers are working with our carrier partner to resolve the issue. We will provide another update in 4 hours or as soon as more information becomes available.
Dec 30, 19:58 PST
Update - We are continuing to experience SMS delivery delays when sending messages to TNM Network in Malawi. Our engineers are working with our carrier partner to resolve the issue. We will provide another update in 2 hours or as soon as more information becomes available.
Dec 30, 18:58 PST
Investigating - We are experiencing SMS delivery delays when sending messages to TNM Network in Malawi. Our engineers are working with our carrier partner to resolve the issue. We will provide another update in 1 hour or as soon as more information becomes available.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Twilio Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SMS Delivery Delays to Digitel Network in Venezuela]]></title>
        <id>https://status.twilio.com/incidents/fb2y8zvcqy7h</id>
        <link href="https://status.twilio.com/incidents/fb2y8zvcqy7h"/>
        <updated>2022-12-31T09:04:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dec 31, 01:04 PST
Resolved - We are no longer experiencing SMS delivery delays when sending messages to Digitel Network in Venezuela.. This incident has been resolved.
Dec 30, 23:22 PST
Monitoring - We are observing recovery in SMS delivery delays when sending messages to Digitel Network in Venezuela. We will continue monitoring the service to ensure a full recovery. We will provide another update in 2 hours or as soon as more information becomes available.
Dec 30, 19:47 PST
Update - We are continuing to experience SMS delivery delays when sending messages to Digitel Network in Venezuela. Our engineers are working with our carrier partner to resolve the issue. We will provide another update in 4 hours or as soon as more information becomes available.
Dec 30, 17:48 PST
Update - We continue to experience SMS delivery delays when sending messages to Digitel Network in Venezuela. Our engineers are working with our carrier partner to resolve the issue. We will provide another update in 2 hours or as soon as more information becomes available.
Dec 30, 16:43 PST
Investigating - We are experiencing SMS delivery delays when sending messages to Digitel Network in Venezuela. Our engineers are working with our carrier partner to resolve the issue. We will provide another update in 1 hour or as soon as more information becomes available.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Twilio Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident with Codespaces]]></title>
        <id>https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/1whd66ydswnx</id>
        <link href="https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/1whd66ydswnx"/>
        <updated>2022-12-31T01:47:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dec 31, 01:47 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Dec 31, 01:39 UTC
Update - We are continuing mitigation for an issue impacting some Codespaces customers. We will keep you updated on progress.
Dec 31, 01:12 UTC
Update - We are continuing to work on mitigation for an issue impacting some Codespaces customers. We will continue to keep you updated on progress.
Dec 31, 00:39 UTC
Update - We identified an issue that impacts some Codespaces customers and are working on mitigation.We will continue to keep you updated on progress.
Dec 31, 00:07 UTC
Investigating - We are investigating reports of degraded performance for Codespaces.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GitHub Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MDM Enrollment not available for new macOS computers]]></title>
        <id>https://status.rippling.com/incidents/gmll739frv3b</id>
        <link href="https://status.rippling.com/incidents/gmll739frv3b"/>
        <updated>2022-12-22T19:55:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dec 22, 19:55 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Dec 22, 18:13 UTC
Update - We are continuing to monitor for any further issues.
Dec 22, 18:13 UTC
Monitoring - A fix has been implemented and we are monitoring the results.
Dec 22, 17:35 UTC
Identified - The issue has been identified and a fix is being implemented.
Dec 22, 17:12 UTC
Investigating - We are currently investigating this issue.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rippling Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Missing Workspace section in sidebar]]></title>
        <id>https://status.notion.so/incidents/3py88r008jjg</id>
        <link href="https://status.notion.so/incidents/3py88r008jjg"/>
        <updated>2022-12-21T18:31:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dec 21, 10:31 PST
Resolved - We have implemented the fix and confirmed the issue is resolved. Workspace section and pages have been restored to the sidebar for affected users.
Dec 21, 10:06 PST
Identified - Since ~3:30pm Pacific time yesterday, some users on Free and Plus plans have been unable to see pages in the Workspace section of the sidebar. We have identified the root cause and a fix is in progress.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Notion Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident: Messages on iOS are automatically marked as read]]></title>
        <id>https://status.slack.com//2022-12/4db4ec459abdd159</id>
        <link href="https://status.slack.com//2022-12/4db4ec459abdd159"/>
        <updated>2022-12-20T14:36:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Issue summary:

From Monday December 12, 2022 at 10:27 AM PST to Monday December 19, 2022 at 1:30 PM PST, we began investigating reports of messages being marked as read when backgrounding the iOS app while in a conversation. As a result, the sidebar would not show unread messages next to the DM/Channel/Threads view. 


We have now made a change on our end that resolved the issue and released a fix on iOS app version 22.12.21. Users on the iOS app should now be able to receive messages without them being marked as read automatically.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Slack System Status</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident with Actions]]></title>
        <id>https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/cb6ljbzhktxd</id>
        <link href="https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/cb6ljbzhktxd"/>
        <updated>2022-12-20T07:58:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dec 20, 07:58 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Dec 20, 07:23 UTC
Update - We are seeing delayed workflow job status updates for Actions. We are seeing the status update events being backed up and have applied a mitigation. We continue to monitor the delay.
Dec 20, 06:55 UTC
Investigating - We are investigating reports of degraded performance for Actions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GitHub Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident with Actions]]></title>
        <id>https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/3y3y8nnbyt2d</id>
        <link href="https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/3y3y8nnbyt2d"/>
        <updated>2022-12-20T01:38:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dec 20, 01:38 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Dec 20, 01:02 UTC
Update - We have identified the issue with manual workflow invocations from the UI. A mitigation will be deployed shortly.
Dec 20, 00:09 UTC
Investigating - We are investigating reports of degraded performance for Actions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GitHub Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Partial search failres]]></title>
        <id>https://status.notion.so/incidents/vwnxl4hd436q</id>
        <link href="https://status.notion.so/incidents/vwnxl4hd436q"/>
        <updated>2022-12-19T03:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dec 18, 19:00 PST
Resolved - From approximately 5pm Pacific time yesterday to 8:30am today, Notion experienced an issue that caused some search results to fail. This issue has been resolved.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Notion Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Investigating reports of degraded performance.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/d5158f5wh1ly</id>
        <link href="https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/d5158f5wh1ly"/>
        <updated>2022-12-15T20:37:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dec 15, 20:37 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Dec 15, 20:31 UTC
Update - We are working on mitigating the issues loading content from raw.github.com
Dec 15, 20:00 UTC
Update - We are investigating issues loading content from raw.github.com
Dec 15, 20:00 UTC
Investigating - We are currently investigating this issue.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GitHub Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident with API Requests]]></title>
        <id>https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/pkbqcn8dp6dy</id>
        <link href="https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/pkbqcn8dp6dy"/>
        <updated>2022-12-15T20:00:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dec 15, 20:00 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Dec 15, 19:47 UTC
Update - We are investigating issues loading content from raw.github.com
Dec 15, 19:42 UTC
Investigating - We are investigating reports of degraded performance for API Requests.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GitHub Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident: Some users having trouble playing videos]]></title>
        <id>https://status.slack.com//2022-12/ddd9879de59fd9d1</id>
        <link href="https://status.slack.com//2022-12/ddd9879de59fd9d1"/>
        <updated>2022-12-15T18:39:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Issue summary: From December 13, 2022 at 11:46 AM PST to December 14, 2022 at 7:30 AM PST some customers may have experienced issues while playing videos.


We determined this issue was caused by a recent frontend change that caused a failure to load videos via the streaming protocol HLS (Hypertext Live Streaming), for which no fallback existed. 


To resolve this issue, we introduced a fallback to HLS allowing users to play video files with a slightly degraded experience, such as longer load times. 


Additionally, we disabled a code optimization technique which fully restored HLS functionality for all users.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Slack System Status</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident: Some users not receiving 2FA codes via SMS]]></title>
        <id>https://status.slack.com//2022-12/7e95e869e43429ae</id>
        <link href="https://status.slack.com//2022-12/7e95e869e43429ae"/>
        <updated>2022-12-15T01:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Issue Summary:


From December 14, 2022 at 04:30 PST to December 14, 2022 at 09:00 PST, we received reports from customers who were unable to receive SMS 2FA codes to login, we discovered that the Slack Twilio queue on the Twilio services was growing at a high rate and the outgoing SMS message error rate began to grow. Customers who had enabled 2FA via SMS were affected in at least India, China, US, Brazil, and Argentina. It was discovered that a majority of this traffic was coming from nefarious acting workspaces issuing too many app download link SMS requests to the Twilio service. With thousands of workspaces doing this at the same time, our queue became overloaded. The disposable email domains used to create these teams were added to a Total Ban blocklist preventing any users using the domains from accessing Slack — stopping team creation and further SMS pumping. Twilio was also able to drop the messages specific to app download links based on a content filter. With these actions, the queue was able to catch back up.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Slack System Status</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident: Trouble connecting in Slack]]></title>
        <id>https://status.slack.com//2022-12/3404420180fb4113</id>
        <link href="https://status.slack.com//2022-12/3404420180fb4113"/>
        <updated>2022-12-14T22:00:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Issue summary:

From 10:12 AM PST until 10:25 AM PST on December 14, 2022, some customers had trouble loading Slack workspaces, sending messages, and uploading files.


Prior to this issue, we began removing traffic from an isolated location within a data center region as part of a planned exercise. Upon further investigation, we identified a bug within this process. We then stopped the process, which resolved the issue for all users. Error rates were monitored for a short while prior to announcing the resolution, in order to ensure the issue was fully resolved and would not reoccur.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Slack System Status</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident with Git Operations and Pull Requests]]></title>
        <id>https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/4p7zympgsr86</id>
        <link href="https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/4p7zympgsr86"/>
        <updated>2022-12-13T18:43:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dec 13, 18:43 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Dec 13, 18:35 UTC
Update - We have identified the issue impacting pull requests and git operations and are actively working on mitigations.
Dec 13, 17:39 UTC
Investigating - We are investigating reports of degraded performance for Git Operations and Pull Requests.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GitHub Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident with Issues and Pull Requests]]></title>
        <id>https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/6p0msrcyr3qt</id>
        <link href="https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/6p0msrcyr3qt"/>
        <updated>2022-12-10T03:00:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dec 10, 03:00 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Dec 10, 02:37 UTC
Investigating - We are investigating reports of degraded performance for Issues and Pull Requests.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GitHub Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident: Trouble with exports]]></title>
        <id>https://status.slack.com//2022-12/a709513bd336365f</id>
        <link href="https://status.slack.com//2022-12/a709513bd336365f"/>
        <updated>2022-12-08T15:45:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Issue Summary: 


From December 8, 2022 at 03:15 PST to December 8, 2022 at 05:10 PST, some customers may have experienced issues with exports failing. This was due to a lack of disk space on one of the hosts running export jobs. We fixed this issue by terminating the host which resolved the problem for all affected customers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Slack System Status</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[500 Errors Across Reservations and Listings Endpoints]]></title>
        <id>https://airbnbapi.statuspage.io/incidents/yg9s36qmf80z</id>
        <link href="https://airbnbapi.statuspage.io/incidents/yg9s36qmf80z"/>
        <updated>2022-12-06T21:03:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dec  6, 13:03 PST
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Dec  6, 09:13 PST
Monitoring - We have identified and resolved an issue of increased 500 errors across the Reservations and Listings endpoints. The increase occurred between 08:25 and 08:55 AM PT. We'll post updates as we have more information.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Airbnb API Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident with Codespaces]]></title>
        <id>https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/by950fpm0xlg</id>
        <link href="https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/by950fpm0xlg"/>
        <updated>2022-12-06T20:58:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dec  6, 20:58 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Dec  6, 20:34 UTC
Update - We are continuing to investigate issues affecting some Codespaces customers in the westus2 region.
Dec  6, 19:51 UTC
Update - We are continuing to investigate issues affecting some Codespaces customers.
Dec  6, 19:15 UTC
Update - We are continuing to investigate issues affecting customers connecting to and starting Codespaces.
Dec  6, 18:41 UTC
Update - We are continuing to investigate issues affecting customers connecting to and starting Codespaces.
Dec  6, 18:06 UTC
Update - We are investigating issues preventing customers from starting and connecting to existing Codespaces. Creating a new Codespaces is one possible workaround for those affected.
Dec  6, 17:53 UTC
Investigating - We are investigating reports of degraded performance for Codespaces.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GitHub Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident: Some users may be experiencing issues loading DMs or channels]]></title>
        <id>https://status.slack.com//2022-12/825fec838eaeb4cf</id>
        <link href="https://status.slack.com//2022-12/825fec838eaeb4cf"/>
        <updated>2022-12-06T02:47:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Issue summary:

From December 1, 2022 at 12:10 PM PST to December 5, 2022 at 2:43 PM PST, some customers may have experienced issues with blank channels and direct message conversations. 


We made a small change to improve the screen reader experience that inadvertently introduced a syntax error. We corrected this error, resolving the problem for all affected customers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Slack System Status</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident with Git Operations and Pull Requests]]></title>
        <id>https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/01g5rt6z89q2</id>
        <link href="https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/01g5rt6z89q2"/>
        <updated>2022-12-05T18:40:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dec  5, 18:40 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Dec  5, 18:07 UTC
Update - We have identified possible causes slowing down git operations including push and pull for a small number of customers, as well as some slow merge operations and are working on mitigating now.
Dec  5, 17:31 UTC
Investigating - We are investigating reports of degraded performance for Git Operations and Pull Requests.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GitHub Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>