<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2023-05-10T00:20:55.863Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2023-05-10T00:20:55.863Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident with Git Operations]]></title>
        <id>https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/wj1qbq7r9tcl</id>
        <link href="https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/wj1qbq7r9tcl"/>
        <updated>2023-05-10T00:06:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[May 10, 00:06 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
May  9, 23:31 UTC
Update - We are seeing slower than usual times to run git clone over HTTPS. SSH is not impacted. We continue to investigate.
May  9, 22:52 UTC
Update - We are seeing slower than usual times to run git clone over HTTPS. SSH is not impacted. We continue to investigate.
May  9, 22:39 UTC
Investigating - We are investigating reports of degraded performance for Git Operations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GitHub Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MMS/SMS Delivery Delays to AT&T Network in USA]]></title>
        <id>https://status.twilio.com/incidents/j1cqy8lch4vz</id>
        <link href="https://status.twilio.com/incidents/j1cqy8lch4vz"/>
        <updated>2023-05-10T00:05:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[May  9, 17:05 PDT
Resolved - We are no longer experiencing MMS/SMS delivery delays when sending messages to  AT&T network in USA. This incident has been resolved.
May  9, 15:00 PDT
Monitoring - We are observing recovery in MMS/SMS delivery delays when sending messages to AT&T network in USA. We will continue monitoring the service to ensure a full recovery. We will provide another update in 2 hours or as soon as more information becomes available.
May  9, 12:42 PDT
Update - We continue experiencing MMS/SMS delivery delays when sending messages to AT&T network in USA. Our engineers are working with our carrier partner to resolve the issue. We will provide another update in 8 hours or as soon as more information becomes available.
May  9, 09:01 PDT
Update - We continue experiencing MMS/SMS delivery delays when sending messages to AT&T network in USA. Our engineers are working with our carrier partner to resolve the issue. We will provide another update in 4 hours or as soon as more information becomes available.
May  9, 06:52 PDT
Update - We continue experiencing MMS/SMS delivery delays when sending messages to AT&T network in USA. Our engineers are working with our carrier partner to resolve the issue. We will provide another update in 2 hours or as soon as more information becomes available.
May  9, 05:52 PDT
Investigating - We are experiencing MMS/SMS delivery delays when sending messages to AT&T network in USA. Our engineers are working with our carrier partner to resolve the issue. We will provide another update in 1 hour or as soon as more information becomes available.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Twilio Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SMS Delivery Delays to Orange Network in Cameroon]]></title>
        <id>https://status.twilio.com/incidents/nkkblfjm2wwh</id>
        <link href="https://status.twilio.com/incidents/nkkblfjm2wwh"/>
        <updated>2023-05-09T23:38:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[May  9, 16:38 PDT
Update - We are experiencing SMS delivery delays when sending messages to Orange Network in Cameroon. Our engineers are working with our carrier partner to resolve the issue. We will provide another update in 4 hours or as soon as more information becomes available.
May  9, 14:39 PDT
Update - We are experiencing SMS delivery delays when sending messages to Orange Network in Cameroon. Our engineers are working with our carrier partner to resolve the issue. We will provide another update in 2 hours or as soon as more information becomes available.
May  9, 13:35 PDT
Investigating - We are experiencing SMS delivery delays when sending messages to Orange Network in Cameroon. Our engineers are working with our carrier partner to resolve the issue. We will provide another update in 1 hour or as soon as more information becomes available.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Twilio Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SMS Delivery Delays to Econet Network in Zimbabwe]]></title>
        <id>https://status.twilio.com/incidents/4bv92q4c8f92</id>
        <link href="https://status.twilio.com/incidents/4bv92q4c8f92"/>
        <updated>2023-05-09T23:01:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[May  9, 16:01 PDT
Monitoring - We are observing recovery in SMS delivery delays when sending messages to Econet network in Zimbabwe. We will continue monitoring the service to ensure a full recovery. We will provide another update in 2 hours or as soon as more information becomes available.
May  9, 12:35 PDT
Update - We continue experiencing SMS delivery delays when sending messages to Econet network in Zimbabwe. Our engineers are working with our carrier partner to resolve the issue. We will provide another update in 4 hours or as soon as more information becomes available.
May  9, 10:28 PDT
Update - We continue experiencing SMS delivery delays when sending messages to Econet network in Zimbabwe. Our engineers are working with our carrier partner to resolve the issue. We will provide another update in 2 hours or as soon as more information becomes available.
May  9, 09:28 PDT
Investigating - We are experiencing SMS delivery delays when sending messages to Econet network in Zimbabwe. Our engineers are working with our carrier partner to resolve the issue. We will provide another update in 1 hour or as soon as more information becomes available.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Twilio Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[France Voice and SMS Carrier Partner Maintenance]]></title>
        <id>https://status.twilio.com/incidents/zw9dmvs25qz4</id>
        <link href="https://status.twilio.com/incidents/zw9dmvs25qz4"/>
        <updated>2023-05-09T23:00:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[May  9, 16:00 PDT
Completed - The scheduled maintenance has been completed.
May  9, 15:00 PDT
In progress - Scheduled maintenance is currently in progress. We will provide updates as necessary.
Apr 24, 02:58 PDT
Scheduled - Our Voice and SMS carrier partner in France is conducting a planned maintenance from 09 May 2023 at 15:00 PDT until 09 May 2023 at 16:00 PDT. During the maintenance window, there could be intermittent call disconnects to a subset of Twilio France phone numbers and delays delivering SMS to and from France handsets via a Subset of Long codes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Twilio Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[France SMS Carrier Maintenance - Bouygues Telecom]]></title>
        <id>https://status.twilio.com/incidents/5x3yqncfc80k</id>
        <link href="https://status.twilio.com/incidents/5x3yqncfc80k"/>
        <updated>2023-05-09T22:00:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[May  9, 15:00 PDT
In progress - Scheduled maintenance is currently in progress. We will provide updates as necessary.
Apr 30, 18:57 PDT
Scheduled - The Bouygues Telecom network in France is conducting a planned maintenance from 09 May 2023 at 15:00 PDT until 09 May 2023 at 21:00 PDT, During the maintenance window, there could be intermittent delays delivering SMS to and from France Bouygues Telecom handsets]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Twilio Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident with Actions, API Requests, Codespaces, Git Operations, Issues, Pages, Pull Requests and Webhooks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/f0mhbz9xn497</id>
        <link href="https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/f0mhbz9xn497"/>
        <updated>2023-05-09T21:14:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[May  9, 21:14 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
May  9, 19:43 UTC
Update - All services continue to operate normally and we are continuing work on restoring delayed pull request updates for some impacted customers. We will go back to green once that work has completed.
May  9, 16:55 UTC
Update - Git Operations is operating normally.
May  9, 16:38 UTC
Update - All services continue to operate normally and we are continuing work on restoring delayed pull request updates for some impacted customers. We will go back to green once that work has completed.
May  9, 15:07 UTC
Update - All services are operating normally but we are working on restoring delayed pull request updates for some impacted customers and will go back to green once that work has completed.
May  9, 13:40 UTC
Upd…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GitHub Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Global Account Security Carrier Partner Maintenance - 3ID]]></title>
        <id>https://status.twilio.com/incidents/00qpt0j533b7</id>
        <link href="https://status.twilio.com/incidents/00qpt0j533b7"/>
        <updated>2023-05-09T21:00:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[May  9, 14:00 PDT
Completed - The scheduled maintenance has been completed.
May  9, 10:31 PDT
In progress - Scheduled maintenance is currently in progress. We will provide updates as necessary.
May  8, 02:24 PDT
Scheduled - Our Global Carrier Partner 3ID is conducting an emergency maintenance from 09 May 2023 at 10:30 PST until 09 May 2023 at 14:00 PST. During the maintenance window, there could be intermittent API request failures for the following destinations: Indonesia.
Impacted Products - Carrier
Silent Network Authentication (SNA) - 3 Indonesia.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Twilio Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MMS/SMS Delivery Report Delays to Multiple networks in Canada and US for a subset of Long Codes]]></title>
        <id>https://status.twilio.com/incidents/l6b9s59vn6z1</id>
        <link href="https://status.twilio.com/incidents/l6b9s59vn6z1"/>
        <updated>2023-05-09T20:00:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[May  9, 13:00 PDT
Resolved - We are no longer experiencing MMS/SMS delivery delays when sending messages to multiple US and Canada networks using subset of Longcodes. This incident has been resolved.
May  9, 12:31 PDT
Monitoring - We are observing recovery in MMS/SMS delivery delays when sending messages to multiple US and Canada networks using subset of Longcodes. We will continue monitoring the service to ensure a full recovery. We will provide another update in 30 minutes or as soon as more information becomes available.
May  9, 10:31 PDT
Update - We continue observing MMS/SMS delivery receipt delays when sending messages to multiple US and Canada networks using subset of long codes. Our engineers are working with our carrier partner to resolve the issue. We will provide another update …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Twilio Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Issues with promos and trial balances]]></title>
        <id>https://status.twilio.com/incidents/8z9cs1xtpswl</id>
        <link href="https://status.twilio.com/incidents/8z9cs1xtpswl"/>
        <updated>2023-05-09T16:46:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[May  9, 09:46 PDT
Resolved - Billing Pipeline was degraded for 72 minutes between 07:33 and 08:45 Pacific Time on 05/09/2023. During this period, Console users were unable to apply promos and trial balances on  customer accounts. The issue has now been resolved.
May  9, 09:36 PDT
Investigating - We've become aware of a potential issue with Console returning 500 error. Our engineering team has been alerted and is actively investigating. We will update as soon as we have additional information.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Twilio Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident with Pull Requests]]></title>
        <id>https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/wzv2wd9zvhpr</id>
        <link href="https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/wzv2wd9zvhpr"/>
        <updated>2023-05-09T10:04:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[May  9, 10:04 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
May  9, 09:50 UTC
Update - Our engineers continue to monitor the delivery of backlogged notifications.
May  9, 08:44 UTC
Update - We have mitigated the issue impacting the delivery of notifications, and are working to deliver the backlog of notifications.
May  9, 08:09 UTC
Update - We are investigating delays in the delivery of Pull Request notifications.
May  9, 08:07 UTC
Investigating - We are investigating reports of degraded performance for Pull Requests.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GitHub Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v2021.12.31 Migration Enforcement - Phase 4]]></title>
        <id>https://airbnbapi.statuspage.io/incidents/c1zh41bsb899</id>
        <link href="https://airbnbapi.statuspage.io/incidents/c1zh41bsb899"/>
        <updated>2023-05-09T07:00:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[May  9, 00:00 PDT
Completed - The scheduled maintenance has been completed.
May  8, 00:00 PDT
In progress - Scheduled maintenance is currently in progress. We will provide updates as necessary.
May  3, 10:08 PDT
Scheduled - The deprecation date for API Version 2021.12.31 was March 31, 2023. Any applications that have not fully migrated will be automatically migrated to a newer version, which can result in application breakage.
Automatic migration will occur in phases as detailed in https://developer.airbnb.com/docs/versioning-enforcement
Phase 4 begins May 8, 2023 for the Critical Pricing APIs:
- Availability Rules
- Pricing Settings
- Seasonal Rule Groups
- Seasonal Rule Groups Timeline
- Rate Plans
- LOS Records]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Airbnb API Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RESOLVED: We're investigating reports of an issue with Google Meet. We will provide more information shortly. The affected users are unable to access Google Meet, but we've provided a workaround below.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.google.com/appsstatus/dashboard/incidents/8M5Hsx4d2Y9SFYUCqjyj</id>
        <link href="https://www.google.com/appsstatus/dashboard/incidents/8M5Hsx4d2Y9SFYUCqjyj"/>
        <updated>2023-05-08T13:16:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p> Incident began at <strong>2023-04-17 19:04</strong> and ended at <strong>2023-04-25 14:38</strong> <span>(times are in <strong>Coordinated Universal Time (UTC)</strong>).</span></p><div class="cBIRi14aVDP__status-update-text"><h1>Incident Report</h1>
<h2>Summary</h2>
<p>Starting on 17 April 2023 at 12:04, some Google Meet Hardware devices failed to launch the Meet app and the devices displayed a “Waiting for application window” message for a duration of 7 days, 19 hours and 34 minutes. To our Google Meet Hardware customers who were affected we sincerely apologize. This is not the level of quality and reliability we strive to offer you, and we are taking immediate steps to improve the platform’s performance and availability.</p>
<h2>Root Cause</h2>
<p>The device requires a healthy network state and a fully initialized Meet application in order to launch. When the affected devices started up after a reboot, certain conditions caused a network check to fail. Under these circumstances, the device displayed a “Waiting for application window” message indefinitely. Devices that were automatically upgraded to the next version of ChromeOS  were more susceptible to these conditions.</p>
<h2>Remediation and Prevention</h2>
<p>Google engineers were able to identify a fix and deploy to the beta fleet of production on 21 April 2023 at 07:24 US/Pacific (within 24 hours of reproducing the issue). Google engineers instructed affected customers, who wanted to expedite receiving the fix, to move their devices to the Beta release channel. The incident was mitigated after the fix was released to the stable channel on 25 April 2023 at 07:38 US/Pacific.</p>
<p>We apologize for the length and severity of this incident. We are taking immediate steps to prevent a recurrence and improve reliability in the future, by completing the following actions :</p>
<ul>
<li>Fix the underlying issue in the application launcher to prevent it from getting in a stuck state</li>
<li>Improve logging, monitoring, and alerting for the fleet so that issues can be identified quickly</li>
</ul>
<p>Google is committed to quickly and continually improving our technology and operations to prevent service disruptions. We appreciate your patience and apologize again for the impact to your organization. We thank you for your business.</p>
<h2>Detailed Description of Impact</h2>
<p>Beginning from 17 April 2023 at 12:04 US/Pacific, multiple customers of Google Meet Hardware devices, with Operating System (OS) versions greater than 14816.84.1 but lower than 14816.84.35, began to encounter issues in device startup following the upgrade.</p>
<p>At its peak, Google engineers were able to identify that around ~5000 devices had stopped, which caused the admins to receive an “offline device” alert for each of those devices.</p>
<p>These devices were frozen with “Waiting for application window” and would eventually go to sleep if left idle. The devices needed to be rebooted manually (sometimes with mitigation steps involving disconnecting the ethernet cable) or waiting for the device to reboot during a maintenance window.</p>
</div><hr><p>Affected products: Google Meet</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Workspace Status Dashboard Updates</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Airbnb API is down]]></title>
        <id>https://airbnbapi.statuspage.io/incidents/2g99rmdkn9lg</id>
        <link href="https://airbnbapi.statuspage.io/incidents/2g99rmdkn9lg"/>
        <updated>2023-05-04T21:49:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[May  4, 14:49 PDT
Resolved - This incident has been resolve. We apologize the inconvenience caused. Don't hesitate to contact us if you need technical support.
May  4, 10:29 PDT
Monitoring - We have deployed a fix at 10:05 AM PDT, and our systems are back up and running again. We will continue to monitor the results in the upcoming hours.
May  4, 08:40 PDT
Investigating - Starting today, from 08:15 AM PDT we are experiencing issues across Airbnb platform and the API - any requests to the API are returning a 503 error. We are aware of the issue and are working on it urgently.
Please know our engineering and operations teams are working hard to get everything up and running again, and we will update you with the latest information as soon as possible.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Airbnb API Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[website maintenance]]></title>
        <id>https://status.make.com/incidents/10hhnwxqyw68</id>
        <link href="https://status.make.com/incidents/10hhnwxqyw68"/>
        <updated>2023-05-04T16:58:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[May  4, 18:58 CEST
Completed - Maintenance is completed
May  4, 18:40 CEST
In progress - Scheduled maintenance is currently in progress. We will provide updates as necessary.
May  4, 18:39 CEST
Scheduled - Some users might experience unexpected logout. We expect no impact on primary functionality of the platform.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Make Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident with Actions, API Requests, Codespaces, Copilot, Git Operations, Issues, Pages, Pull Requests and Webhooks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/c2jg911dtkjb</id>
        <link href="https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/c2jg911dtkjb"/>
        <updated>2023-05-04T16:23:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[May  4, 16:23 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
May  4, 16:22 UTC
Update - Actions is operating normally.
May  4, 16:22 UTC
Update - Webhooks is operating normally.
May  4, 16:22 UTC
Update - Pages is operating normally.
May  4, 16:21 UTC
Update - Pull Requests is operating normally.
May  4, 16:21 UTC
Update - Codespaces is operating normally.
May  4, 16:21 UTC
Update - Issues is operating normally.
May  4, 16:19 UTC
Update - Codespaces is now experiencing degraded performance. We are still investigating and will provide an update when we have one.
May  4, 16:19 UTC
Update - API Requests is operating normally.
May  4, 16:18 UTC
Update - Pages is operating normally.
May  4, 16:18 UTC
Update - Copilot is operating normally.
May  4, 16:06 UTC
Update - Pages is experiencing degraded performance. We are continuing to investigate.
May  4, 16:06 UTC
Update - Actions is experiencing degraded performance. We are continuing to investigate.
May  4, 16:06 UTC
Update - Copilot is experiencing degraded performance. We are continuing to investigate.
May  4, 16:06 UTC
Update - API Requests is experiencing degraded performance. We are still investigating and will provide an update when we have one.
May  4, 16:04 UTC
Update - Webhooks is experiencing degraded performance. We are still investigating and will provide an update when we have one.
May  4, 16:04 UTC
Update - Codespaces is experiencing degraded availability. We are continuing to investigate.
May  4, 16:03 UTC
Update - Git Operations is experiencing degraded performance. We are still investigating and will provide an update when we have one.
May  4, 16:03 UTC
Update - Pull Requests is experiencing degraded performance. We are still investigating and will provide an update when we have one.
May  4, 15:55 UTC
Investigating - We are investigating reports of degraded performance for Issues.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GitHub Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Notion AI down]]></title>
        <id>https://status.notion.so/incidents/pyrhq77wmg6p</id>
        <link href="https://status.notion.so/incidents/pyrhq77wmg6p"/>
        <updated>2023-05-02T16:32:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[May  2, 09:32 PDT
Resolved - We have resolved this issue and Notion AI should be working again for users.
May  2, 09:14 PDT
Investigating - We are currently experiencing an issue with Notion AI. Engineering is investigating the root cause of this issue.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Notion Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident with Actions]]></title>
        <id>https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/lhw4ny5js29b</id>
        <link href="https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/lhw4ny5js29b"/>
        <updated>2023-05-02T15:49:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[May  2, 15:49 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
May  2, 15:34 UTC
Update - We are investigating reports of issues with service(s): Actions. A subset of customers are experiencing run start delays and job failures. We are deploying a fix to mitigate the issue.
May  2, 14:58 UTC
Investigating - We are investigating reports of degraded performance for Actions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GitHub Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v2021.12.31 Migration Enforcement - Phase 3]]></title>
        <id>https://airbnbapi.statuspage.io/incidents/xgzsxbpp8jy3</id>
        <link href="https://airbnbapi.statuspage.io/incidents/xgzsxbpp8jy3"/>
        <updated>2023-05-02T07:00:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[May  2, 00:00 PDT
Completed - The scheduled maintenance has been completed.
May  1, 00:01 PDT
In progress - Scheduled maintenance is currently in progress. We will provide updates as necessary.
Apr 26, 10:06 PDT
Scheduled - The deprecation date for API Version 2021.12.31 was March 31, 2023. Any applications that have not fully migrated will be automatically migrated to a newer version, which can result in application breakage.
Automatic migration will occur in phases as detailed in https://developer.airbnb.com/docs/versioning-enforcement
Phase 3 begins May 1, 2023 for the following endpoints: Descriptions, Photos, Rooms, Booking Settings]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Airbnb API Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident: Enterprise Grid customers experiencing errors when starting a workflow]]></title>
        <id>https://status.slack.com//2023-05/c2ae05d7865dc16b</id>
        <link href="https://status.slack.com//2023-05/c2ae05d7865dc16b"/>
        <updated>2023-05-02T03:25:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Issue summary:

On May 1, 2023, from 3:53 PM PDT to 6:45 PM PDT, some Enterprise Grid customers may have experienced issues launching workflows in Slack. 


A recent change to workflows inadvertently introduced an issue that resulted in the error codes REBBE72D5DA6 and REBA7F7D9186 when launching workflows. We rolled back the change, which resolved the issue for all affected customers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Slack System Status</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident: Slack.com links are broken for some users on Enterprise Grid]]></title>
        <id>https://status.slack.com//2023-04/aacc14003e92c232</id>
        <link href="https://status.slack.com//2023-04/aacc14003e92c232"/>
        <updated>2023-04-29T05:09:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Issue Summary:

From April 19, 2023 at 3:05 PM PST until April 28, 2023 at 7:51 PM PST, customers signed in with an Enterprise Grid workspace may have experienced unexpected redirect behaviour when navigating https://slack.com/ links.


We appreciate your patience as we investigated the issue. Our engineering team has implemented a fix to resolve the routing behaviour; however, please reach out to feedback@slack.com if you continue to experience any trouble.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Slack System Status</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident with Codespaces]]></title>
        <id>https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/5h6hwm15zt11</id>
        <link href="https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/5h6hwm15zt11"/>
        <updated>2023-04-28T12:45:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apr 28, 12:45 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Apr 28, 12:26 UTC
Investigating - We are investigating reports of degraded availability for Codespaces.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GitHub Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TS-2023-005]]></title>
        <id>https://tailscale.com/security-bulletins/#ts-2023-005/</id>
        <link href="https://tailscale.com/security-bulletins/#ts-2023-005/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-28T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Description: An issue in the Tailscale coordination server in device
reauthentication logic caused previously authenticated and tagged devices to
lose their ACL tags upon reauthentication.
What happened?
The logic that handles the reauthentication to a new identity on an
already-authenticated device with tags had a bug: instead of updating the
device’s logged-in identity to the newly authenticated user, the device’s
identity became that of the user who originally added it to the tailnet, without
any tags.
The bug was introduced on 2022-10-26, and discovered and remediated on
2023-04-21. The bug was discovered when troubleshooting a user-reported issue.
Who is affected?
189 tailnets triggered this bug in the course of normal use of Tailscale, either
directly by explicitly re-authenticating a device, or indirectly by using fast
user switching to switch between multiple
tailnets.
We have notified affected organizations where we have security
contacts.
What is the impact?
Devices that encountered the bug had their tags removed, which reverted the
device’s identity to that of the user who originally authenticated the device,
or the owner of the auth key that was originally used to authenticate the
device. In either case, this is the user listed as “Creator” in the Machines tab
of the admin panel. Depending on access rules in the tailnet policy file, this
could change the device’s network permissions.
We have analyzed the audit logs for affected tailnets, and found no evidence of
deliberate exploitation. In most instances, device owners noticed the incorrect
outcome of reauthentication, and corrected the device’s state themselves.
What do I need to do?
If you were not contacted by Tailscale, no action is required.  If you were
contacted by Tailscale, reapply the desired tags to affected devices in the
admin console, or by reauthenticating the devices. Tailscale has deployed a fix
to the coordination server as of 2023-04-21, and notified affected
organizations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Security Bulletins on Tailscale</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident with Packages]]></title>
        <id>https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/vsc464zj7gv4</id>
        <link href="https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/vsc464zj7gv4"/>
        <updated>2023-04-27T09:56:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apr 27, 09:56 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Apr 27, 09:30 UTC
Update - We have identified the issue impacting GitHub Packages, and are implementing mitigations.
Apr 27, 09:19 UTC
Update - Packages is now experiencing degraded availability. We are continuing to investigate.
Apr 27, 08:59 UTC
Investigating - We are investigating reports of degraded performance for Packages.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GitHub Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident with Copilot]]></title>
        <id>https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/y9cw6kf9pn72</id>
        <link href="https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/y9cw6kf9pn72"/>
        <updated>2023-04-26T00:29:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apr 26, 00:29 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Apr 26, 00:15 UTC
Update - Copilot is experiencing an increase in error rates. Customers may see slower completions or errors until this is resolved.
Apr 25, 23:52 UTC
Update - Copilot is now experiencing degraded performance. We are still investigating and will provide an update when we have one.
Apr 25, 23:47 UTC
Update - Copilot is now experiencing degraded availability. We are continuing to investigate.
Apr 25, 23:26 UTC
Investigating - We are investigating reports of degraded performance for Copilot.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GitHub Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v2021.12.31 Migration Enforcement - Phase 2]]></title>
        <id>https://airbnbapi.statuspage.io/incidents/pph7sbjdqwjh</id>
        <link href="https://airbnbapi.statuspage.io/incidents/pph7sbjdqwjh"/>
        <updated>2023-04-25T07:00:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apr 25, 00:00 PDT
Completed - The scheduled maintenance has been completed.
Apr 24, 00:00 PDT
In progress - Scheduled maintenance is currently in progress. We will provide updates as necessary.
Apr 21, 12:01 PDT
Scheduled - The deprecation date for API Version 2021.12.31 was March 31, 2023. Starting on April 17th, 2023, any applications that have not fully migrated will be automatically migrated to a newer version, which can result in application breakage.
Automatic migration will occur in phases as detailed in https://developer.airbnb.com/docs/versioning-enforcement
Phase 2 begins April 24, 2023 for the following endpoints: Failed Requests, Messages, Reviews, Reservations, Special Offers]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Airbnb API Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident with Actions, API Requests, Copilot and Git Operations]]></title>
        <id>https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/rcnl10p4hywg</id>
        <link href="https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/rcnl10p4hywg"/>
        <updated>2023-04-25T03:18:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apr 25, 03:18 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Apr 25, 03:08 UTC
Update - We are continuing to work towards mitigating the connection resets and connection timeouts that some clients located in West US are experiencing.
Apr 25, 01:31 UTC
Update - Starting at 20:30 UTC, a small % of clients in West US are seeing connection resets or connection timeouts, leading to failed action downloads.  We are continuing to work to identify a mitigation.
Apr 25, 00:13 UTC
Update - Copilot is operating normally.
Apr 24, 23:14 UTC
Update - We continue to investigate an issue causing fewer than 1% of workflow runs on GitHub-hosted runners to fail.
Apr 24, 22:33 UTC
Update - API Requests is experiencing degraded performance. We are still investigating and will provide an update when we have one.
Apr 24, 22:29 UTC
Update - Git Operations is experiencing degraded performance. We are still investigating and will provide an update when we have one.
Apr 24, 22:17 UTC
Update - We are actively investigating an issue causing fewer than 1% of workflow runs on GitHub-hosted runners to fail.
Apr 24, 22:03 UTC
Update - We are actively investigating an issue causing fewer than 1% of Copilot code suggestions to time out.
Apr 24, 21:29 UTC
Update - Actions is experiencing degraded performance. We are still investigating and will provide an update when we have one.
Apr 24, 21:14 UTC
Investigating - We are investigating reports of degraded performance for Copilot.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GitHub Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident: Users are not able to send, shuffle or cancel gifs with Giphy.]]></title>
        <id>https://status.slack.com//2023-04/51a77ae8a06c6717</id>
        <link href="https://status.slack.com//2023-04/51a77ae8a06c6717"/>
        <updated>2023-04-24T23:29:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Issue summary:

On April 24, 2023 from 11:25 AM PDT to 2:00 PM PDT, some users experienced issues with sending, shuffling and cancelling gifs using the Giphy app. We traced the issue to a recent update that impacted how we handle buttons in the /giphy slash command. 


We rolled back this change, resolving the issue for all impacted users.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Slack System Status</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident with Actions]]></title>
        <id>https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/113cggyjrxpr</id>
        <link href="https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/113cggyjrxpr"/>
        <updated>2023-04-24T13:27:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apr 24, 13:27 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Apr 24, 12:57 UTC
Investigating - We are investigating reports of degraded performance for Actions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GitHub Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident: A small percentage of users may be experiencing slowness in Slack.]]></title>
        <id>https://status.slack.com//2023-04/9a270de38235b921</id>
        <link href="https://status.slack.com//2023-04/9a270de38235b921"/>
        <updated>2023-04-20T18:38:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Issue Summary:

On April 20th, 2023 from 6:00 AM PDT until 7:45 AM PDT, a small number of users experienced latency issues when using Slack. Users reported a delay in loading threads, channels, direct messages, marking messages as read, and executing workflows. 


The issue resulted from an increased database load on one of our data center regions. We made a change in order manage the larger load and return to normal response times. 


Our team is continuing to look into what causes some queries to run slower than others to prevent degraded performance in the future.


Thank you for your patience while we worked through this. We apologize for any disruption to your work.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Slack System Status</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident with Actions]]></title>
        <id>https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/jl6ryhty8h5x</id>
        <link href="https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/jl6ryhty8h5x"/>
        <updated>2023-04-19T19:27:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apr 19, 19:27 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Apr 19, 19:27 UTC
Update - We've applied a mitigation and workflows targeting hosted Linux/Windows Larger Runners are running again. There may be some continued delays as queues are processed.
Apr 19, 18:33 UTC
Update - Actions is experiencing capacity constraints with hosted Linux/Windows Larger Runners, leading to high wait times. Other hosted labels and self-hosted runners are not impacted.
Apr 19, 18:28 UTC
Investigating - We are investigating reports of degraded performance for Actions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GitHub Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[eu1.make.com web UI unavailable]]></title>
        <id>https://status.make.com/incidents/gh5y2fn4pjzz</id>
        <link href="https://status.make.com/incidents/gh5y2fn4pjzz"/>
        <updated>2023-04-19T09:32:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apr 19, 11:32 CEST
Resolved - Users might have experienced problems using web UI, login was not available between 10:45 and 11:10 CEST. The issue was resolved, all systems are now operational.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Make Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident with Actions, Issues, Pull Requests and Webhooks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/g8mb319cqjsp</id>
        <link href="https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/g8mb319cqjsp"/>
        <updated>2023-04-18T15:29:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apr 18, 15:29 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Apr 18, 15:29 UTC
Update - Issues is operating normally.
Apr 18, 15:29 UTC
Update - Webhooks is operating normally.
Apr 18, 15:27 UTC
Update - Actions is operating normally.
Apr 18, 15:12 UTC
Update - We have identified the cause for latency issues affecting Pull Requests and Issues UI experiences and Actions jobs being delayed to process. We have deployed a fix and are monitoring closely.
Apr 18, 14:56 UTC
Update - Actions is experiencing degraded performance. We are continuing to investigate.
Apr 18, 14:35 UTC
Update - Issues and Pull Requests are experiencing degraded performance. We are still investigating and will provide an update when we have one.
Apr 18, 14:35 UTC
Investigating - We are investigating reports of degraded performance for Webhooks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GitHub Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident with Git Operations, Issues and Pull Requests]]></title>
        <id>https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/k1qts16jgtcp</id>
        <link href="https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/k1qts16jgtcp"/>
        <updated>2023-04-18T09:51:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apr 18, 09:51 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Apr 18, 09:45 UTC
Update - Git Operations is operating normally.
Apr 18, 09:43 UTC
Update - Issues is operating normally.
Apr 18, 09:30 UTC
Update - Git Operations is experiencing degraded performance. We are continuing to investigate.
Apr 18, 09:28 UTC
Investigating - We are investigating reports of degraded availability for Issues and Pull Requests.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GitHub Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v2021.12.31 Migration Enforcement]]></title>
        <id>https://airbnbapi.statuspage.io/incidents/ymym186bx049</id>
        <link href="https://airbnbapi.statuspage.io/incidents/ymym186bx049"/>
        <updated>2023-04-18T07:00:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apr 18, 00:00 PDT
Completed - The scheduled maintenance has been completed.
Apr 17, 00:00 PDT
In progress - Scheduled maintenance is currently in progress. We will provide updates as necessary.
Apr 14, 10:19 PDT
Scheduled - The deprecation date for API Version 2021.12.31 is on March 31, 2023. Starting on April 17th, 2023, any applications that have not fully migrated will be automatically migrated to a newer version, which can result in application breakage.
Automatic migration will occur in phases as detailed in https://developer.airbnb.com/docs/versioning-enforcement
Phase 1 begins April 17, 2023 for the following endpoints: Transactions, Resolutions, Users, Opportunities]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Airbnb API Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident with Actions and Pages]]></title>
        <id>https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/5w7lb9j98x96</id>
        <link href="https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/5w7lb9j98x96"/>
        <updated>2023-04-17T19:53:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apr 17, 19:53 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Apr 17, 19:34 UTC
Update - Pages is experiencing degraded performance. We are still investigating and will provide an update when we have one.
Apr 17, 19:28 UTC
Investigating - We are investigating reports of degraded performance for Actions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GitHub Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident with Codespaces]]></title>
        <id>https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/yqbbq78g1vpk</id>
        <link href="https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/yqbbq78g1vpk"/>
        <updated>2023-04-17T17:42:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apr 17, 17:42 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Apr 17, 17:17 UTC
Investigating - We are investigating reports of degraded performance for Codespaces.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GitHub Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New damage deposit payment management setting]]></title>
        <id>262720</id>
        <link href="https://changelog.bookingsync.com/new-damage-deposit-payment-management-setting-262720"/>
        <updated>2023-04-17T08:19:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New!
  
We are happy to announce that new damage deposit payment settings are now available in your Smily account. Those new settings will allow you to better manage your damage deposit payments, as well as provide a better experience to your guests.
Why the changes?
Up until now, when going to your general damage deposit payment management settings (in Settings > Payments > Default preferences), the only option available regarding the collection of your damage deposit was the collection time: either with bookings payment or on arrival.
Both options led to the damage deposit being due via the Smily payment link, and to wrong information being displayed on the Smily payment page and the Smily booking contract in case you were managing your damage deposit via a partner app such as Swikly.
Wh…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>JB, FinOps Product Dept. Director &amp; Core CS Team Lead</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident: Channels are missing for Android users]]></title>
        <id>https://status.slack.com//2023-04/6091d7559163f33c</id>
        <link href="https://status.slack.com//2023-04/6091d7559163f33c"/>
        <updated>2023-04-16T23:40:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Issue summary:


On April 16rd, 2023 from 12:11 PM PDT until 14:39 PM PDT, certain Android users on the Free plan reported issues with loading channels in the Android app.  


Upon investigation, this was attributed to the implementation of a data optimization feature, intended to improve app performance. We have rolled back this feature temporarily, which has corrected the observed issue.  A full investigation and remedy will take place prior to reimplementation. 


Thank you for your patience while we worked through this.  We apologize for any disruption to your work.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Slack System Status</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident: Direct messages view failing to load]]></title>
        <id>https://status.slack.com//2023-04/ac28ceabd64fe276</id>
        <link href="https://status.slack.com//2023-04/ac28ceabd64fe276"/>
        <updated>2023-04-12T22:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This issue has now been resolved, please reload Slack to restore functionality to the direct messages view. Thank you for your patience while we worked on this.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Slack System Status</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident: Images slow to upload]]></title>
        <id>https://status.slack.com//2023-04/d105ce7854fc93d2</id>
        <link href="https://status.slack.com//2023-04/d105ce7854fc93d2"/>
        <updated>2023-04-12T14:38:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Issue summary:

On April 10, 2023 at 7:30 PM PDT, some customers began experiencing delays when uploading files. We traced the issue back to a recent update made to how some file uploads are handled. Reverting this change fixed the issue, and customers were no longer experiencing it as of April 11, 2023 at 7:33 AM PDT. 


Thank you so much for your patience as our team actively worked on this.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Slack System Status</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Issue impacting users in Korea]]></title>
        <id>https://status.notion.so/incidents/7txs6dn5qhmp</id>
        <link href="https://status.notion.so/incidents/7txs6dn5qhmp"/>
        <updated>2023-04-11T00:10:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apr 10, 17:10 PDT
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Apr 10, 12:29 PDT
Monitoring - Impacted users should see improvements when interacting with static elements. We're still actively monitoring the issue.
Apr  6, 23:01 PDT
Investigating - We are experiencing performance issues that may impact users in Korea. Users may experience significant delays when interacting with static content, like images and videos. Engineering is investigating the root cause of the degradation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Notion Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>