<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2023-01-16T00:23:06.793Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2023-01-16T00:23:06.793Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Russia SMS Carrier Maintenance - Tele2]]></title>
        <id>https://status.twilio.com/incidents/wzbwhmbj6cp2</id>
        <link href="https://status.twilio.com/incidents/wzbwhmbj6cp2"/>
        <updated>2023-01-16T00:01:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jan 15, 16:01 PST
Completed - The scheduled maintenance has been completed.
Jan 15, 12:01 PST
In progress - Scheduled maintenance is currently in progress. We will provide updates as necessary.
Jan 13, 09:31 PST
Scheduled - The Tele2 network in Russia is conducting an emergency maintenance from 15 January 2023 at 12:00 PST until 15 January 2023 at 16:00 PST. During the maintenance window, there could be intermittent delays delivering SMS to and from Tele2 Russia handsets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Twilio Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SMS Carrier Partner Maintenance in Denmark]]></title>
        <id>https://status.twilio.com/incidents/6x7vmtq7d4rm</id>
        <link href="https://status.twilio.com/incidents/6x7vmtq7d4rm"/>
        <updated>2023-01-16T00:00:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jan 15, 16:00 PST
In progress - Scheduled maintenance is currently in progress. We will provide updates as necessary.
Jan 12, 10:25 PST
Scheduled - Our SMS carrier partner in Denmark is conducting an emergency maintenance from 15 January 2023 at 16:00 PST until 15 January 2023 at 17:00 PST. During the maintenance window, there could be intermittent delays delivering SMS to and from a subset of handset in Denmark.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Twilio Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SMS Delivery Delays to 9Mobile Network in Nigeria]]></title>
        <id>https://status.twilio.com/incidents/psf5j4t63d1d</id>
        <link href="https://status.twilio.com/incidents/psf5j4t63d1d"/>
        <updated>2023-01-15T23:55:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jan 15, 15:55 PST
Investigating - We are experiencing SMS delivery delays when sending messages to 9Mobile network in Nigeria. Our engineers are working with our carrier partner to resolve the issue. We will provide another update in 1 hour or as soon as more information becomes available.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Twilio Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Malaysia SMS Carrier Maintenance - U Mobile]]></title>
        <id>https://status.twilio.com/incidents/bm6mn1hwv38b</id>
        <link href="https://status.twilio.com/incidents/bm6mn1hwv38b"/>
        <updated>2023-01-15T21:00:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jan 15, 13:00 PST
Completed - The scheduled maintenance has been completed.
Jan 15, 10:00 PST
In progress - Scheduled maintenance is currently in progress. We will provide updates as necessary.
Jan 10, 07:16 PST
Scheduled - The U Mobile network in Malaysia is conducting a planned maintenance from 15 January 2023 at 10:00 PST until 15 January 2023 at 13:00 PST. During the maintenance window, there could be intermittent delays delivering SMS to and from U Mobile Malaysia handsets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Twilio Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Port Away Notifications Not Being Sent to User]]></title>
        <id>https://status.twilio.com/incidents/ltkr8d2n9bx3</id>
        <link href="https://status.twilio.com/incidents/ltkr8d2n9bx3"/>
        <updated>2023-01-15T13:20:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jan 15, 05:20 PST
Resolved - Port Away Notifications issue has been resolved and Phone numbers are operating normally at this time.
Jan 14, 07:06 PST
Update - We continue experiencing an issue with port away notifications not being sent to customers. Our engineers are working with our carrier partner to resolve the issue. We will provide another update in 24 hours or as soon as more information becomes available.
Jan 13, 14:46 PST
Update - We are still experiencing an issue with port away notifications not being sent to customers. Our engineers are working with our carrier partner to resolve the issue. We will provide another update in 16 hours or as soon as more information becomes available.
Jan 13, 06:44 PST
Update - We are still experiencing issue with Port Away Notifications not Being…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Twilio Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US and Canada MMS Carrier Partner Maintenance]]></title>
        <id>https://status.twilio.com/incidents/s2t3hqszmlr5</id>
        <link href="https://status.twilio.com/incidents/s2t3hqszmlr5"/>
        <updated>2023-01-15T08:00:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jan 15, 00:00 PST
Completed - The scheduled maintenance has been completed.
Jan 14, 19:00 PST
In progress - Scheduled maintenance is currently in progress. We will provide updates as necessary.
Jan 10, 06:57 PST
Scheduled - Our MMS carrier partner in the US and Canada is conducting a planned maintenance from 14 January 2023 at 19:00 PST until 15 January 2023 at 00:00 PST. During the maintenance window, there could be intermittent delays delivering MMS to and from US and Canadian handsets via subset of Longcodes and Shortcodes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Twilio Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SMS Delivery Delays to MTN Network in Uganda]]></title>
        <id>https://status.twilio.com/incidents/2qzxyq9khf0m</id>
        <link href="https://status.twilio.com/incidents/2qzxyq9khf0m"/>
        <updated>2023-01-15T00:41:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jan 14, 16:41 PST
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Jan 14, 14:24 PST
Monitoring - We are observing recovery in SMS delivery delays when sending messages to MTN network in Uganda. We will continue monitoring the service to ensure a full recovery. We will provide another update in 2 hours or as soon as more information becomes available.
Jan 14, 14:11 PST
Update - We are still experiencing SMS delivery delays to MTN network in Uganda. Our engineers are working with our carrier partner to resolve the issue. We will provide another update in 4 hours or as soon as more information becomes available.
Jan 14, 12:12 PST
Update - We are still experiencing SMS delivery delays to MTN network in Uganda. Our engineers are working with our carrier partner to resolve the issue. We will provide another update in 2 hours or as soon as more information becomes available.
Jan 14, 11:03 PST
Investigating - We are experiencing SMS delivery delays to MTN network in Uganda. Our engineers are working with our carrier partner to resolve the issue. We will provide another update in 1 hour or as soon as more information becomes available.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Twilio Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SMS Delivery Delays to Orange Network in Burkina Faso]]></title>
        <id>https://status.twilio.com/incidents/xh062fflv385</id>
        <link href="https://status.twilio.com/incidents/xh062fflv385"/>
        <updated>2023-01-15T00:05:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jan 14, 16:05 PST
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Jan 14, 14:26 PST
Monitoring - We are observing recovery in SMS delivery delays when sending messages to Orange network in Burkina Faso. We will continue monitoring the service to ensure a full recovery. We will provide another update in 2 hours or as soon as more information becomes available.
Jan 14, 12:31 PST
Update - We continue to experience SMS delivery delays to Orange network in Burkina Faso. Our engineers are working with our carrier partner to resolve the issue. We will provide another update in 4 hours or as soon as more information becomes available.
Jan 14, 10:32 PST
Update - We are still experiencing SMS delivery delays to Orange network in Burkina Faso. Our engineers are working with our carrier partner to resolve the issue. We will provide another update in 2 hours or as soon as more information becomes available.
Jan 14, 09:39 PST
Investigating - We are experiencing SMS delivery delays to Orange network in Burkina Faso. Our engineers are working with our carrier partner to resolve the issue. We will provide another update in 1 hour or as soon as more information becomes available.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Twilio Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident with Codespaces]]></title>
        <id>https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/hzgtxb033mym</id>
        <link href="https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/hzgtxb033mym"/>
        <updated>2023-01-14T16:58:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jan 14, 16:58 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Jan 14, 16:09 UTC
Update - We are investigating issues with Codespaces port forwarding. Users may be able to use the desktop client as a workaround.
Jan 14, 15:13 UTC
Investigating - We are investigating reports of degraded performance for Codespaces.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GitHub Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SMS Delivery Delays to U-Mobile Network in Malaysia]]></title>
        <id>https://status.twilio.com/incidents/5v9y626kpmsl</id>
        <link href="https://status.twilio.com/incidents/5v9y626kpmsl"/>
        <updated>2023-01-14T10:24:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jan 14, 02:24 PST
Resolved - We are no longer experiencing SMS delivery delays when sending messages to U-Mobile network In Malaysia.. This incident has been resolved.
Jan 14, 00:37 PST
Monitoring - We are observing recovery in SMS delivery delays when sending messages to U-Mobile network In Malaysia. We will continue monitoring the service to ensure a full recovery. We will provide another update in 2 hours or as soon as more information becomes available.
Jan 13, 23:58 PST
Update - We are still experiencing SMS delivery delays when sending messages to U-Mobile network In Malaysia. Our engineers are working with our carrier partner to resolve the issue. We will provide another update in 2 hours or as soon as more information becomes available.
Jan 13, 22:58 PST
Investigating - We are experiencing SMS delivery delays when sending messages to U-Mobile network In Malaysia. Our engineers are working with our carrier partner to resolve the issue. We will provide another update in 1 hour or as soon as more information becomes available.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Twilio Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MMS Delivery Report Delays From a Subset of Shortcodes to Multiple Networks in US]]></title>
        <id>https://status.twilio.com/incidents/706dyvywmj0m</id>
        <link href="https://status.twilio.com/incidents/706dyvywmj0m"/>
        <updated>2023-01-14T04:07:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jan 13, 20:07 PST
Resolved - We are no longer experiencing MMS delivery report delays when sending from a subset Twilio short codes to multiple networks in the US. This incident has been resolved.
Jan 13, 19:19 PST
Update - We are observing recovery in MMS delivery report delays when sending from a subset Twilio short codes to multiple networks in the US. We will continue monitoring the service to ensure a full recovery. We will provide another update in 2 hours or as soon as more information becomes available.
Jan 13, 17:19 PST
Monitoring - We are observing recovery in MMS delivery report delays when sending from a subset Twilio short codes to multiple networks in the US. We will continue monitoring the service to ensure a full recovery. We will provide another update in 2 hours or as soon as more information becomes available.
Jan 13, 13:21 PST
Update - We are still observing delays in receiving MMS delivery reports to multiple networks in USA from a subset of short codes. Our engineering team has been alerted and is actively investigating. We will update in the next 4 hours or as soon as we have more information.
Jan 13, 11:19 PST
Update - We are still observing delay in receiving MMS delivery reports to multiple networks in USA from a sub-set of short code. Our engineering team has been alerted and is actively investigating. We will update in the next 2 hours or as soon as we have more information.
Jan 13, 10:21 PST
Investigating - We are observing delay in receiving MMS delivery reports to multiple networks in USA from a sub-set of short code. Our engineering team has been alerted and is actively investigating. We will update in the next 1 hour or as soon as we have more information.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Twilio Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Egypt SMS Carrier Maintenance - Vodafone]]></title>
        <id>https://status.twilio.com/incidents/npckcr0j02yy</id>
        <link href="https://status.twilio.com/incidents/npckcr0j02yy"/>
        <updated>2023-01-14T04:00:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jan 13, 20:00 PST
Completed - The scheduled maintenance has been completed.
Jan 13, 15:00 PST
In progress - Scheduled maintenance is currently in progress. We will provide updates as necessary.
Jan 10, 13:13 PST
Scheduled - The Vodafone network in Egypt is conducting an emergency maintenance from 13 January 2023 at 15:00 PST until 13 January 2023 at 20:00 PST. During the maintenance window, there could be intermittent delays delivering SMS to and from Vodafone Egypt handsets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Twilio Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident with Copilot]]></title>
        <id>https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/n6wxc7xwrk1z</id>
        <link href="https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/n6wxc7xwrk1z"/>
        <updated>2023-01-12T04:55:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jan 12, 04:55 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Jan 12, 04:51 UTC
Update - Some Copilot plans were impacted by a recent backend change causing those users to see an error that access has ended.  We have applied a change to correct this and are seeing full recovery.
Jan 12, 03:59 UTC
Investigating - We are investigating reports of degraded performance for Copilot.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GitHub Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Make intermittent login issues]]></title>
        <id>https://status.make.com/incidents/0zz20hbhy112</id>
        <link href="https://status.make.com/incidents/0zz20hbhy112"/>
        <updated>2023-01-11T16:36:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jan 11, 17:36 CET
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Jan 11, 12:00 CET
Monitoring - The root cause of the issue has been identified and a remedy is already in place . Some users might have experienced troubles with logging in to the platform whilst we can confirm that there was no impact on running scenarios . We are actively monitoring the situation .
Jan 11, 11:37 CET
Investigating - We are currently experiencing intermittent issues when logging in to make zones . We are actively investigating the issue and working on a solution.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Make Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident with Actions and Git Operations]]></title>
        <id>https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/00km0kwpz23b</id>
        <link href="https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/00km0kwpz23b"/>
        <updated>2023-01-10T18:14:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jan 10, 18:14 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Jan 10, 17:54 UTC
Update - Some action hosted runners are experiencing longer than normal run times.
Jan 10, 17:22 UTC
Update - Actions is experiencing degraded performance. We are still investigating and will provide an update when we have one.
Jan 10, 17:04 UTC
Investigating - We are investigating reports of degraded performance for Git Operations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GitHub Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[500 Errors Across Multiple Endpoints]]></title>
        <id>https://airbnbapi.statuspage.io/incidents/dz7fk8vqftbf</id>
        <link href="https://airbnbapi.statuspage.io/incidents/dz7fk8vqftbf"/>
        <updated>2023-01-09T23:10:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jan  9, 15:10 PST
Resolved - From 14:00-15:00 Pacific Time (PT), we saw increased 500 errors for multiple API endpoints, including reservations, listings and threads. The issue is now identified and resolved, please retry any failed requests during this time. Apologies for the inconvenience caused due to this incident and thank you for your patience and understanding.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Airbnb API Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident with Actions]]></title>
        <id>https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/ffwkvn9j77d1</id>
        <link href="https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/ffwkvn9j77d1"/>
        <updated>2023-01-07T23:30:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jan  7, 23:30 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Jan  7, 23:25 UTC
Update - We are investigating reports of timeouts with Actions. We will continue to keep users updated on progress towards mitigation.
Jan  7, 22:50 UTC
Investigating - We are investigating reports of degraded performance for Actions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GitHub Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Delay in email delivery due to third-party outage]]></title>
        <id>https://status.rippling.com/incidents/mbk89dt1vc41</id>
        <link href="https://status.rippling.com/incidents/mbk89dt1vc41"/>
        <updated>2023-01-05T15:49:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jan  5, 15:49 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Jan  5, 02:25 UTC
Monitoring - A fix has been implemented and we are monitoring the results.
Jan  5, 01:45 UTC
Update - We are continuing to monitor our third-party service provider for updates. Service has not been restored by the third-party email provider. Once service is restored, the majority of emails that were not sent during the outage will be resent.
Jan  5, 01:14 UTC
Update - We are continuing to monitor our third-party service provider for updates. Service has not been restored by the third-party email provider. Once service is restored, the majority of emails that were not sent during the outage will be resent.
Jan  5, 00:38 UTC
Update - Service has not been restored by the third-party email provider. Once service is restored, the majority of emails that were not sent during the outage will be resent.
Jan  5, 00:17 UTC
Identified - A fix has been implemented by the third-party service. We are working to confirm service has been restored.
Jan  4, 23:31 UTC
Investigating - Our third-party email delivery provider has been experiencing an outage since Jan 4th, 2:10 PM PST, causing a delay in notification delivery for all Rippling emails (including password resets). We are investigating this issue with the third-party provider.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rippling Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Issues completing a MFA authenticator challenge]]></title>
        <id>https://status.rippling.com/incidents/zgg7pyzjl7tr</id>
        <link href="https://status.rippling.com/incidents/zgg7pyzjl7tr"/>
        <updated>2023-01-03T23:07:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jan  3, 23:07 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Jan  3, 21:33 UTC
Monitoring - A fix has been implemented and we are monitoring the results.
Jan  3, 20:35 UTC
Identified - The issue has been identified and a fix is being implemented.
Jan  3, 20:27 UTC
Investigating - Users asked to complete an MFA challenge are unable to advance past the page. We are investigating this issue]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rippling Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RESOLVED: We are experiencing an issue with Gmail, Google Chat, Google Voice. Our engineering team continues to investigate the issue. We will provide an update by Tuesday, 2022-12-13 10:30 US/Pacific with current details.
Users may be facing unavailability for Gmail, Google Chat and Google Voice]]></title>
        <id>https://www.google.com/appsstatus/dashboard/incidents/tLjnxF7DdVTCicccdQtj</id>
        <link href="https://www.google.com/appsstatus/dashboard/incidents/tLjnxF7DdVTCicccdQtj"/>
        <updated>2023-01-03T20:28:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p> Incident began at <strong>2022-12-13 15:34</strong> and ended at <strong>2022-12-13 18:04</strong> <span>(times are in <strong>Coordinated Universal Time (UTC)</strong>).</span></p><div class="cBIRi14aVDP__status-update-text"><p>A combined Incident Report has been published on our Google Workspace Status Dashboard for this Incident - <a href="https://www.google.com/appsstatus/dashboard/incidents/AzeVS1iCHxhtzgi8r3mc">https://www.google.com/appsstatus/dashboard/incidents/AzeVS1iCHxhtzgi8r3mc</a></p>
</div><hr><p>Affected products: Gmail</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Workspace Status Dashboard Updates</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident with Codespaces]]></title>
        <id>https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/srn4b1fjxp8h</id>
        <link href="https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/srn4b1fjxp8h"/>
        <updated>2023-01-01T18:28:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jan  1, 18:28 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Jan  1, 17:28 UTC
Update - We have identified the issue and are deploying a fix. We will update our status when the fix is fully deployed.
Jan  1, 16:44 UTC
Update - Codespaces is experiencing issues with web connectivity from GitHub.com. The desktop client can still be used to launch or connect to codespaces."
Jan  1, 16:33 UTC
Investigating - We are investigating reports of degraded performance for Codespaces.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GitHub Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident with Codespaces]]></title>
        <id>https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/1whd66ydswnx</id>
        <link href="https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/1whd66ydswnx"/>
        <updated>2022-12-31T01:47:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dec 31, 01:47 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Dec 31, 01:39 UTC
Update - We are continuing mitigation for an issue impacting some Codespaces customers. We will keep you updated on progress.
Dec 31, 01:12 UTC
Update - We are continuing to work on mitigation for an issue impacting some Codespaces customers. We will continue to keep you updated on progress.
Dec 31, 00:39 UTC
Update - We identified an issue that impacts some Codespaces customers and are working on mitigation.We will continue to keep you updated on progress.
Dec 31, 00:07 UTC
Investigating - We are investigating reports of degraded performance for Codespaces.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GitHub Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MDM Enrollment not available for new macOS computers]]></title>
        <id>https://status.rippling.com/incidents/gmll739frv3b</id>
        <link href="https://status.rippling.com/incidents/gmll739frv3b"/>
        <updated>2022-12-22T19:55:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dec 22, 19:55 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Dec 22, 18:13 UTC
Update - We are continuing to monitor for any further issues.
Dec 22, 18:13 UTC
Monitoring - A fix has been implemented and we are monitoring the results.
Dec 22, 17:35 UTC
Identified - The issue has been identified and a fix is being implemented.
Dec 22, 17:12 UTC
Investigating - We are currently investigating this issue.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rippling Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Missing Workspace section in sidebar]]></title>
        <id>https://status.notion.so/incidents/3py88r008jjg</id>
        <link href="https://status.notion.so/incidents/3py88r008jjg"/>
        <updated>2022-12-21T18:31:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dec 21, 10:31 PST
Resolved - We have implemented the fix and confirmed the issue is resolved. Workspace section and pages have been restored to the sidebar for affected users.
Dec 21, 10:06 PST
Identified - Since ~3:30pm Pacific time yesterday, some users on Free and Plus plans have been unable to see pages in the Workspace section of the sidebar. We have identified the root cause and a fix is in progress.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Notion Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident: Messages on iOS are automatically marked as read]]></title>
        <id>https://status.slack.com//2022-12/4db4ec459abdd159</id>
        <link href="https://status.slack.com//2022-12/4db4ec459abdd159"/>
        <updated>2022-12-20T14:36:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Issue summary:

From Monday December 12, 2022 at 10:27 AM PST to Monday December 19, 2022 at 1:30 PM PST, we began investigating reports of messages being marked as read when backgrounding the iOS app while in a conversation. As a result, the sidebar would not show unread messages next to the DM/Channel/Threads view. 


We have now made a change on our end that resolved the issue and released a fix on iOS app version 22.12.21. Users on the iOS app should now be able to receive messages without them being marked as read automatically.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Slack System Status</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident with Actions]]></title>
        <id>https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/cb6ljbzhktxd</id>
        <link href="https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/cb6ljbzhktxd"/>
        <updated>2022-12-20T07:58:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dec 20, 07:58 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Dec 20, 07:23 UTC
Update - We are seeing delayed workflow job status updates for Actions. We are seeing the status update events being backed up and have applied a mitigation. We continue to monitor the delay.
Dec 20, 06:55 UTC
Investigating - We are investigating reports of degraded performance for Actions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GitHub Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident with Actions]]></title>
        <id>https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/3y3y8nnbyt2d</id>
        <link href="https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/3y3y8nnbyt2d"/>
        <updated>2022-12-20T01:38:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dec 20, 01:38 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Dec 20, 01:02 UTC
Update - We have identified the issue with manual workflow invocations from the UI. A mitigation will be deployed shortly.
Dec 20, 00:09 UTC
Investigating - We are investigating reports of degraded performance for Actions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GitHub Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Partial search failres]]></title>
        <id>https://status.notion.so/incidents/vwnxl4hd436q</id>
        <link href="https://status.notion.so/incidents/vwnxl4hd436q"/>
        <updated>2022-12-19T03:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dec 18, 19:00 PST
Resolved - From approximately 5pm Pacific time yesterday to 8:30am today, Notion experienced an issue that caused some search results to fail. This issue has been resolved.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Notion Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>