<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2023-05-03T00:21:04.148Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2023-05-03T00:21:04.148Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SMS Carrier Partner Maintenance to Multiple Countries]]></title>
        <id>https://status.twilio.com/incidents/hdkw1k63xyxt</id>
        <link href="https://status.twilio.com/incidents/hdkw1k63xyxt"/>
        <updated>2023-05-03T04:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[THIS IS A SCHEDULED EVENT May 2, 21:00 - 23:00 PDT
Apr 28, 22:01 PDT
Scheduled - Our SMS carrier partner is conducting a planned maintenance from 02 May 2023 at 21:00 PDT until 02 May 2023 at 23:00 PDT. During the maintenance window, there could be intermittent delays delivering SMS to and from the following countries via a subset of Short code and Long codes.
Germany
United Kingdom
Mexico
Spain]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Twilio Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US SMS Carriers Maintenance - Small US Carriers]]></title>
        <id>https://status.twilio.com/incidents/sqwmjstlkhpd</id>
        <link href="https://status.twilio.com/incidents/sqwmjstlkhpd"/>
        <updated>2023-05-03T04:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[THIS IS A SCHEDULED EVENT May 2, 21:00 PDT  -  May 3, 01:30 PDT
Apr 28, 16:48 PDT
Scheduled - A subset of Small US networks in the US is conducting a planned maintenance from 02 May 2023 at 21:00 PDT until 03 May 2023 at 01:30 PDT. During the maintenance window, there could be intermittent delays delivering SMS to and from Small US Carriers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Twilio Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SMS Carrier Partner Maintenance]]></title>
        <id>https://status.twilio.com/incidents/gf2hwfmprr1h</id>
        <link href="https://status.twilio.com/incidents/gf2hwfmprr1h"/>
        <updated>2023-05-03T03:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[THIS IS A SCHEDULED EVENT May 2, 20:30 - 22:00 PDT
Apr 26, 16:53 PDT
Scheduled - Our SMS carrier partner in Spain is conducting a maintenance from 02 May 2023 at 20:30 PDT until 02 May 2023 at 22:00 PDT. During the maintenance window, there could be intermittent delays delivering SMS to and from Spain handsets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Twilio Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Russia SMS Carrier Maintenance - Megafon]]></title>
        <id>https://status.twilio.com/incidents/89brqyg8xfqw</id>
        <link href="https://status.twilio.com/incidents/89brqyg8xfqw"/>
        <updated>2023-05-03T00:01:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[May  2, 17:01 PDT
Completed - The scheduled maintenance has been completed.
May  2, 13:00 PDT
In progress - Scheduled maintenance is currently in progress. We will provide updates as necessary.
Apr 27, 05:24 PDT
Scheduled - The Megafon network in Russia is conducting a planned maintenance from 02 May 2023 at 13:00 PDT until 02 May 2023 at 17:00 PDT. During the maintenance window, there could be intermittent delays delivering SMS to and from Megafon Russia handsets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Twilio Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Issues with Authy Public Domain]]></title>
        <id>https://status.twilio.com/incidents/467skfh7jt4f</id>
        <link href="https://status.twilio.com/incidents/467skfh7jt4f"/>
        <updated>2023-05-02T23:48:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[May  2, 16:48 PDT
Resolved - We are no longer seeing issues with Authy.com domain. This incident has been resolved.
May  2, 16:07 PDT
Update - We are seeing recovery when using Authy.com domain. We will continue to monitor for stability and we will provide an update in 30 minutes or as soon as information becomes available.
May  2, 15:26 PDT
Update - Our engineers have identified a potential issue with Authy.com domain, Authy end users may be restricted to perform certain actions. We will provide an update in 1 hour or as soon as information becomes available.
May  2, 15:14 PDT
Investigating - Our monitoring systems have detected a potential issue with Authy.com website. Our engineering team has been alerted and is actively investigating. We will update as soon as we have more information.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Twilio Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Issues with Billing Services]]></title>
        <id>https://status.twilio.com/incidents/0hc38g35mfd8</id>
        <link href="https://status.twilio.com/incidents/0hc38g35mfd8"/>
        <updated>2023-05-02T23:36:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[May  2, 16:36 PDT
Update - We are investigating an issue with Billing that might show charges for incorrect Billable item. We expect to provide another update in 1 hour or as soon as more information becomes available.
May  2, 16:27 PDT
Investigating - Our monitoring systems have detected a potential issue with Pricing Services. Our engineering team has been alerted and is actively investigating. We will update as soon as we have more information.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Twilio Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SMS Delivery Delays to IER Network in Ireland]]></title>
        <id>https://status.twilio.com/incidents/rswkww6w1qh7</id>
        <link href="https://status.twilio.com/incidents/rswkww6w1qh7"/>
        <updated>2023-05-02T22:30:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[May  2, 15:30 PDT
Resolved - We are no longer experiencing SMS delivery delays when sending messages to IER network in Ireland. This incident has been resolved.
May  2, 13:19 PDT
Monitoring - We are observing recovery in SMS delivery delays when sending messages to IER network in Ireland. We will continue monitoring the service to ensure a full recovery. We will provide another update in 2 hours or as soon as more information becomes available.
May  2, 11:20 PDT
Update - We are still experiencing SMS delivery delays when sending messages to IER network in Ireland. Our engineers are working with our carrier partner to resolve the issue. We will provide another update in 4 hours or as soon as more information becomes available.
May  2, 09:10 PDT
Update - We are still experiencing SMS delivery delays when sending messages to IER network in Ireland. Our engineers are working with our carrier partner to resolve the issue. We will provide another update in 2 hours or as soon as more information becomes available.
May  2, 08:10 PDT
Investigating - We are experiencing SMS delivery delays when sending messages to IER network in Ireland. Our engineers are working with our carrier partner to resolve the issue. We will provide another update in 1 hour or as soon as more information becomes available.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Twilio Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SMS Delivery Delays to Airtel Network]]></title>
        <id>https://status.twilio.com/incidents/25dwdzsh02b3</id>
        <link href="https://status.twilio.com/incidents/25dwdzsh02b3"/>
        <updated>2023-05-02T21:51:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[May  2, 14:51 PDT
Resolved - After investigating, our engineers confirmed that we are not experiencing SMS delivery delays to Airtel Network. There is ongoing maintenance activity(https://status.twilio.com/incidents/x67dmqwkltgy) and this incident has been resolved.
May  2, 14:32 PDT
Investigating - We are experiencing SMS delivery delays when sending messages to Airtel Network worldwide excluding India. Our engineers are working with our carrier partner to resolve the issue. We will provide another update in 1 hours or as soon as more information becomes available.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Twilio Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Notion AI down]]></title>
        <id>https://status.notion.so/incidents/pyrhq77wmg6p</id>
        <link href="https://status.notion.so/incidents/pyrhq77wmg6p"/>
        <updated>2023-05-02T16:32:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[May  2, 09:32 PDT
Resolved - We have resolved this issue and Notion AI should be working again for users.
May  2, 09:14 PDT
Investigating - We are currently experiencing an issue with Notion AI. Engineering is investigating the root cause of this issue.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Notion Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident with Actions]]></title>
        <id>https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/lhw4ny5js29b</id>
        <link href="https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/lhw4ny5js29b"/>
        <updated>2023-05-02T15:49:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[May  2, 15:49 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
May  2, 15:34 UTC
Update - We are investigating reports of issues with service(s): Actions. A subset of customers are experiencing run start delays and job failures. We are deploying a fix to mitigate the issue.
May  2, 14:58 UTC
Investigating - We are investigating reports of degraded performance for Actions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GitHub Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RESOLVED: We're aware of a problem with Classroom affecting a significant subset of users. We will provide an update by Apr 19, 2023, 4:00 PM UTC detailing when we expect to resolve the problem. Please note that this resolution time is an estimate and may change. The affected users are unable to access Classroom, but we've provided a workaround below.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.google.com/appsstatus/dashboard/incidents/17yVRt1dxPg9L7WZHfXw</id>
        <link href="https://www.google.com/appsstatus/dashboard/incidents/17yVRt1dxPg9L7WZHfXw"/>
        <updated>2023-05-02T13:48:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p> Incident began at <strong>2023-04-19 00:32</strong> and ended at <strong>2023-04-20 14:58</strong> <span>(times are in <strong>Coordinated Universal Time (UTC)</strong>).</span></p><div class="cBIRi14aVDP__status-update-text"><h1>Incident Report</h1>
<h2>Summary</h2>
<p>On Tuesday, 18 April 2023 at 17:32 US/Pacific, the Google Classroom application was unavailable for some Android users for a period of 1 day, 12 hours, 52 minutes. Some users were unable to sign in and, if already signed in, experienced an error for the duration of this incident.</p>
<h2>Root Cause</h2>
<p>The root cause has been identified as a misconfiguration in a recent Android Classroom release which caused the Android app to point to a backend staging environment instead of production. This resulted in elevated traffic and task failures, ultimately causing Android app availability issues.</p>
<h2>Remediation and Prevention</h2>
<p>On Tuesday 18 April at 17:32 US/Pacific, Google engineers were alerted to an issue via internal monitoring impacting Google Classroom Android users and immediately started an investigation. Google engineers identified that the latest Classroom Android Version (Version Name: 8.0.141.20.90.2, Version Code: 213051414) release contained a backend misconfiguration which resulted in the Android Classroom application availability issues, causing an estimated ~2.5% of users to experience sign in issues and error messages if already signed in. The issue was mitigated by rolling back the misconfigured release and updating a fix release, this fully resolved the issue for all users Friday, 21 April at 07:58 US/Pacific.</p>
<p>Google is committed to preventing a repeat of this issue in the future and is completing the following actions:</p>
<ul>
<li>Implement Classroom specific alerting mechanism to capture staging and production anomalies.</li>
<li>Optimize and improve manual and automated testing validation for release components.</li>
</ul>
</div><hr><p>Affected products: Classroom</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Workspace Status Dashboard Updates</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v2021.12.31 Migration Enforcement - Phase 3]]></title>
        <id>https://airbnbapi.statuspage.io/incidents/xgzsxbpp8jy3</id>
        <link href="https://airbnbapi.statuspage.io/incidents/xgzsxbpp8jy3"/>
        <updated>2023-05-02T07:00:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[May  2, 00:00 PDT
Completed - The scheduled maintenance has been completed.
May  1, 00:01 PDT
In progress - Scheduled maintenance is currently in progress. We will provide updates as necessary.
Apr 26, 10:06 PDT
Scheduled - The deprecation date for API Version 2021.12.31 was March 31, 2023. Any applications that have not fully migrated will be automatically migrated to a newer version, which can result in application breakage.
Automatic migration will occur in phases as detailed in https://developer.airbnb.com/docs/versioning-enforcement
Phase 3 begins May 1, 2023 for the following endpoints: Descriptions, Photos, Rooms, Booking Settings]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Airbnb API Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident: Enterprise Grid customers experiencing errors when starting a workflow]]></title>
        <id>https://status.slack.com//2023-05/c2ae05d7865dc16b</id>
        <link href="https://status.slack.com//2023-05/c2ae05d7865dc16b"/>
        <updated>2023-05-02T03:25:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Issue summary:

On May 1, 2023, from 3:53 PM PDT to 6:45 PM PDT, some Enterprise Grid customers may have experienced issues launching workflows in Slack. 


A recent change to workflows inadvertently introduced an issue that resulted in the error codes REBBE72D5DA6 and REBA7F7D9186 when launching workflows. We rolled back the change, which resolved the issue for all affected customers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Slack System Status</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident: Slack.com links are broken for some users on Enterprise Grid]]></title>
        <id>https://status.slack.com//2023-04/aacc14003e92c232</id>
        <link href="https://status.slack.com//2023-04/aacc14003e92c232"/>
        <updated>2023-04-29T05:09:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Issue Summary:

From April 19, 2023 at 3:05 PM PST until April 28, 2023 at 7:51 PM PST, customers signed in with an Enterprise Grid workspace may have experienced unexpected redirect behaviour when navigating https://slack.com/ links.


We appreciate your patience as we investigated the issue. Our engineering team has implemented a fix to resolve the routing behaviour; however, please reach out to feedback@slack.com if you continue to experience any trouble.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Slack System Status</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident with Codespaces]]></title>
        <id>https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/5h6hwm15zt11</id>
        <link href="https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/5h6hwm15zt11"/>
        <updated>2023-04-28T12:45:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apr 28, 12:45 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Apr 28, 12:26 UTC
Investigating - We are investigating reports of degraded availability for Codespaces.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GitHub Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TS-2023-005]]></title>
        <id>https://tailscale.com/security-bulletins/#ts-2023-005/</id>
        <link href="https://tailscale.com/security-bulletins/#ts-2023-005/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-28T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Description: An issue in the Tailscale coordination server in device
reauthentication logic caused previously authenticated and tagged devices to
lose their ACL tags upon reauthentication.
What happened?
The logic that handles the reauthentication to a new identity on an
already-authenticated device with tags had a bug: instead of updating the
device’s logged-in identity to the newly authenticated user, the device’s
identity became that of the user who originally added it to the tailnet, without
any tags.
The bug was introduced on 2022-10-26, and discovered and remediated on
2023-04-21. The bug was discovered when troubleshooting a user-reported issue.
Who is affected?
189 tailnets triggered this bug in the course of normal use of Tailscale, either
directly by explicitly re-authenticating a device, or indirectly by using fast
user switching to switch between multiple
tailnets.
We have notified affected organizations where we have security
contacts.
What is the impact?
Devices that encountered the bug had their tags removed, which reverted the
device’s identity to that of the user who originally authenticated the device,
or the owner of the auth key that was originally used to authenticate the
device. In either case, this is the user listed as “Creator” in the Machines tab
of the admin panel. Depending on access rules in the tailnet policy file, this
could change the device’s network permissions.
We have analyzed the audit logs for affected tailnets, and found no evidence of
deliberate exploitation. In most instances, device owners noticed the incorrect
outcome of reauthentication, and corrected the device’s state themselves.
What do I need to do?
If you were not contacted by Tailscale, no action is required.  If you were
contacted by Tailscale, reapply the desired tags to affected devices in the
admin console, or by reauthenticating the devices. Tailscale has deployed a fix
to the coordination server as of 2023-04-21, and notified affected
organizations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Security Bulletins on Tailscale</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident with Packages]]></title>
        <id>https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/vsc464zj7gv4</id>
        <link href="https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/vsc464zj7gv4"/>
        <updated>2023-04-27T09:56:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apr 27, 09:56 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Apr 27, 09:30 UTC
Update - We have identified the issue impacting GitHub Packages, and are implementing mitigations.
Apr 27, 09:19 UTC
Update - Packages is now experiencing degraded availability. We are continuing to investigate.
Apr 27, 08:59 UTC
Investigating - We are investigating reports of degraded performance for Packages.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GitHub Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident with Copilot]]></title>
        <id>https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/y9cw6kf9pn72</id>
        <link href="https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/y9cw6kf9pn72"/>
        <updated>2023-04-26T00:29:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apr 26, 00:29 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Apr 26, 00:15 UTC
Update - Copilot is experiencing an increase in error rates. Customers may see slower completions or errors until this is resolved.
Apr 25, 23:52 UTC
Update - Copilot is now experiencing degraded performance. We are still investigating and will provide an update when we have one.
Apr 25, 23:47 UTC
Update - Copilot is now experiencing degraded availability. We are continuing to investigate.
Apr 25, 23:26 UTC
Investigating - We are investigating reports of degraded performance for Copilot.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GitHub Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v2021.12.31 Migration Enforcement - Phase 2]]></title>
        <id>https://airbnbapi.statuspage.io/incidents/pph7sbjdqwjh</id>
        <link href="https://airbnbapi.statuspage.io/incidents/pph7sbjdqwjh"/>
        <updated>2023-04-25T07:00:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apr 25, 00:00 PDT
Completed - The scheduled maintenance has been completed.
Apr 24, 00:00 PDT
In progress - Scheduled maintenance is currently in progress. We will provide updates as necessary.
Apr 21, 12:01 PDT
Scheduled - The deprecation date for API Version 2021.12.31 was March 31, 2023. Starting on April 17th, 2023, any applications that have not fully migrated will be automatically migrated to a newer version, which can result in application breakage.
Automatic migration will occur in phases as detailed in https://developer.airbnb.com/docs/versioning-enforcement
Phase 2 begins April 24, 2023 for the following endpoints: Failed Requests, Messages, Reviews, Reservations, Special Offers]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Airbnb API Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident with Actions, API Requests, Copilot and Git Operations]]></title>
        <id>https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/rcnl10p4hywg</id>
        <link href="https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/rcnl10p4hywg"/>
        <updated>2023-04-25T03:18:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apr 25, 03:18 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Apr 25, 03:08 UTC
Update - We are continuing to work towards mitigating the connection resets and connection timeouts that some clients located in West US are experiencing.
Apr 25, 01:31 UTC
Update - Starting at 20:30 UTC, a small % of clients in West US are seeing connection resets or connection timeouts, leading to failed action downloads.  We are continuing to work to identify a mitigation.
Apr 25, 00:13 UTC
Update - Copilot is operating normally.
Apr 24, 23:14 UTC
Update - We continue to investigate an issue causing fewer than 1% of workflow runs on GitHub-hosted runners to fail.
Apr 24, 22:33 UTC
Update - API Requests is experiencing degraded performance. We are still investigating and will provide an update when we have one.
Apr 24, 22:29 UTC
Update - Git Operations is experiencing degraded performance. We are still investigating and will provide an update when we have one.
Apr 24, 22:17 UTC
Update - We are actively investigating an issue causing fewer than 1% of workflow runs on GitHub-hosted runners to fail.
Apr 24, 22:03 UTC
Update - We are actively investigating an issue causing fewer than 1% of Copilot code suggestions to time out.
Apr 24, 21:29 UTC
Update - Actions is experiencing degraded performance. We are still investigating and will provide an update when we have one.
Apr 24, 21:14 UTC
Investigating - We are investigating reports of degraded performance for Copilot.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GitHub Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident: Users are not able to send, shuffle or cancel gifs with Giphy.]]></title>
        <id>https://status.slack.com//2023-04/51a77ae8a06c6717</id>
        <link href="https://status.slack.com//2023-04/51a77ae8a06c6717"/>
        <updated>2023-04-24T23:29:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Issue summary:

On April 24, 2023 from 11:25 AM PDT to 2:00 PM PDT, some users experienced issues with sending, shuffling and cancelling gifs using the Giphy app. We traced the issue to a recent update that impacted how we handle buttons in the /giphy slash command. 


We rolled back this change, resolving the issue for all impacted users.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Slack System Status</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident with Actions]]></title>
        <id>https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/113cggyjrxpr</id>
        <link href="https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/113cggyjrxpr"/>
        <updated>2023-04-24T13:27:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apr 24, 13:27 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Apr 24, 12:57 UTC
Investigating - We are investigating reports of degraded performance for Actions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GitHub Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident: A small percentage of users may be experiencing slowness in Slack.]]></title>
        <id>https://status.slack.com//2023-04/9a270de38235b921</id>
        <link href="https://status.slack.com//2023-04/9a270de38235b921"/>
        <updated>2023-04-20T18:38:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Issue Summary:

On April 20th, 2023 from 6:00 AM PDT until 7:45 AM PDT, a small number of users experienced latency issues when using Slack. Users reported a delay in loading threads, channels, direct messages, marking messages as read, and executing workflows. 


The issue resulted from an increased database load on one of our data center regions. We made a change in order manage the larger load and return to normal response times. 


Our team is continuing to look into what causes some queries to run slower than others to prevent degraded performance in the future.


Thank you for your patience while we worked through this. We apologize for any disruption to your work.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Slack System Status</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident with Actions]]></title>
        <id>https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/jl6ryhty8h5x</id>
        <link href="https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/jl6ryhty8h5x"/>
        <updated>2023-04-19T19:27:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apr 19, 19:27 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Apr 19, 19:27 UTC
Update - We've applied a mitigation and workflows targeting hosted Linux/Windows Larger Runners are running again. There may be some continued delays as queues are processed.
Apr 19, 18:33 UTC
Update - Actions is experiencing capacity constraints with hosted Linux/Windows Larger Runners, leading to high wait times. Other hosted labels and self-hosted runners are not impacted.
Apr 19, 18:28 UTC
Investigating - We are investigating reports of degraded performance for Actions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GitHub Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[eu1.make.com web UI unavailable]]></title>
        <id>https://status.make.com/incidents/gh5y2fn4pjzz</id>
        <link href="https://status.make.com/incidents/gh5y2fn4pjzz"/>
        <updated>2023-04-19T09:32:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apr 19, 11:32 CEST
Resolved - Users might have experienced problems using web UI, login was not available between 10:45 and 11:10 CEST. The issue was resolved, all systems are now operational.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Make Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident with Actions, Issues, Pull Requests and Webhooks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/g8mb319cqjsp</id>
        <link href="https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/g8mb319cqjsp"/>
        <updated>2023-04-18T15:29:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apr 18, 15:29 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Apr 18, 15:29 UTC
Update - Issues is operating normally.
Apr 18, 15:29 UTC
Update - Webhooks is operating normally.
Apr 18, 15:27 UTC
Update - Actions is operating normally.
Apr 18, 15:12 UTC
Update - We have identified the cause for latency issues affecting Pull Requests and Issues UI experiences and Actions jobs being delayed to process. We have deployed a fix and are monitoring closely.
Apr 18, 14:56 UTC
Update - Actions is experiencing degraded performance. We are continuing to investigate.
Apr 18, 14:35 UTC
Update - Issues and Pull Requests are experiencing degraded performance. We are still investigating and will provide an update when we have one.
Apr 18, 14:35 UTC
Investigating - We are investigating reports of degraded performance for Webhooks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GitHub Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident with Git Operations, Issues and Pull Requests]]></title>
        <id>https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/k1qts16jgtcp</id>
        <link href="https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/k1qts16jgtcp"/>
        <updated>2023-04-18T09:51:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apr 18, 09:51 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Apr 18, 09:45 UTC
Update - Git Operations is operating normally.
Apr 18, 09:43 UTC
Update - Issues is operating normally.
Apr 18, 09:30 UTC
Update - Git Operations is experiencing degraded performance. We are continuing to investigate.
Apr 18, 09:28 UTC
Investigating - We are investigating reports of degraded availability for Issues and Pull Requests.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GitHub Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v2021.12.31 Migration Enforcement]]></title>
        <id>https://airbnbapi.statuspage.io/incidents/ymym186bx049</id>
        <link href="https://airbnbapi.statuspage.io/incidents/ymym186bx049"/>
        <updated>2023-04-18T07:00:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apr 18, 00:00 PDT
Completed - The scheduled maintenance has been completed.
Apr 17, 00:00 PDT
In progress - Scheduled maintenance is currently in progress. We will provide updates as necessary.
Apr 14, 10:19 PDT
Scheduled - The deprecation date for API Version 2021.12.31 is on March 31, 2023. Starting on April 17th, 2023, any applications that have not fully migrated will be automatically migrated to a newer version, which can result in application breakage.
Automatic migration will occur in phases as detailed in https://developer.airbnb.com/docs/versioning-enforcement
Phase 1 begins April 17, 2023 for the following endpoints: Transactions, Resolutions, Users, Opportunities]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Airbnb API Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident with Actions and Pages]]></title>
        <id>https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/5w7lb9j98x96</id>
        <link href="https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/5w7lb9j98x96"/>
        <updated>2023-04-17T19:53:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apr 17, 19:53 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Apr 17, 19:34 UTC
Update - Pages is experiencing degraded performance. We are still investigating and will provide an update when we have one.
Apr 17, 19:28 UTC
Investigating - We are investigating reports of degraded performance for Actions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GitHub Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident with Codespaces]]></title>
        <id>https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/yqbbq78g1vpk</id>
        <link href="https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/yqbbq78g1vpk"/>
        <updated>2023-04-17T17:42:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apr 17, 17:42 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Apr 17, 17:17 UTC
Investigating - We are investigating reports of degraded performance for Codespaces.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GitHub Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New damage deposit payment management setting]]></title>
        <id>262720</id>
        <link href="https://changelog.bookingsync.com/new-damage-deposit-payment-management-setting-262720"/>
        <updated>2023-04-17T08:19:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New!
  
We are happy to announce that new damage deposit payment settings are now available in your Smily account. Those new settings will allow you to better manage your damage deposit payments, as well as provide a better experience to your guests.
Why the changes?
Up until now, when going to your general damage deposit payment management settings (in Settings > Payments > Default preferences), the only option available regarding the collection of your damage deposit was the collection time: either with bookings payment or on arrival.
Both options led to the damage deposit being due via the Smily payment link, and to wrong information being displayed on the Smily payment page and the Smily booking contract in case you were managing your damage deposit via a partner app such as Swikly.
Wh…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>JB, FinOps Product Dept. Director &amp; Core CS Team Lead</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident: Channels are missing for Android users]]></title>
        <id>https://status.slack.com//2023-04/6091d7559163f33c</id>
        <link href="https://status.slack.com//2023-04/6091d7559163f33c"/>
        <updated>2023-04-16T23:40:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Issue summary:


On April 16rd, 2023 from 12:11 PM PDT until 14:39 PM PDT, certain Android users on the Free plan reported issues with loading channels in the Android app.  


Upon investigation, this was attributed to the implementation of a data optimization feature, intended to improve app performance. We have rolled back this feature temporarily, which has corrected the observed issue.  A full investigation and remedy will take place prior to reimplementation. 


Thank you for your patience while we worked through this.  We apologize for any disruption to your work.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Slack System Status</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident: Direct messages view failing to load]]></title>
        <id>https://status.slack.com//2023-04/ac28ceabd64fe276</id>
        <link href="https://status.slack.com//2023-04/ac28ceabd64fe276"/>
        <updated>2023-04-12T22:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This issue has now been resolved, please reload Slack to restore functionality to the direct messages view. Thank you for your patience while we worked on this.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Slack System Status</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident: Images slow to upload]]></title>
        <id>https://status.slack.com//2023-04/d105ce7854fc93d2</id>
        <link href="https://status.slack.com//2023-04/d105ce7854fc93d2"/>
        <updated>2023-04-12T14:38:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Issue summary:

On April 10, 2023 at 7:30 PM PDT, some customers began experiencing delays when uploading files. We traced the issue back to a recent update made to how some file uploads are handled. Reverting this change fixed the issue, and customers were no longer experiencing it as of April 11, 2023 at 7:33 AM PDT. 


Thank you so much for your patience as our team actively worked on this.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Slack System Status</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Issue impacting users in Korea]]></title>
        <id>https://status.notion.so/incidents/7txs6dn5qhmp</id>
        <link href="https://status.notion.so/incidents/7txs6dn5qhmp"/>
        <updated>2023-04-11T00:10:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apr 10, 17:10 PDT
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Apr 10, 12:29 PDT
Monitoring - Impacted users should see improvements when interacting with static elements. We're still actively monitoring the issue.
Apr  6, 23:01 PDT
Investigating - We are experiencing performance issues that may impact users in Korea. Users may experience significant delays when interacting with static content, like images and videos. Engineering is investigating the root cause of the degradation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Notion Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Twitter app is down]]></title>
        <id>https://status.make.com/incidents/kk37sgh6xp08</id>
        <link href="https://status.make.com/incidents/kk37sgh6xp08"/>
        <updated>2023-04-07T15:19:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apr  7, 17:19 CEST
Resolved - While we still await details from Twitter the only way how to create a connection at this moment is to have every user to create their own Twitter app at developer.twitter.com and use the apps API Key and API Key Secret to create a new connection in Make. We updated our documentation with details about how to obtain API Key and API Key Secret - https://www.make.com/en/help/apps/marketing/twitter#obtaining-api-key-and-api-key-secret-values-for-your-twitter-account
Apr  3, 23:56 CEST
Update - Twitter has suspended our app. We are continuing to investigate.
Apr  3, 21:29 CEST
Investigating - We are currently investigating this issue.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Make Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reminder - Important information regarding your website domain!]]></title>
        <id>262029</id>
        <link href="https://changelog.bookingsync.com/reminder-important-information-regarding-your-website-domain!-262029"/>
        <updated>2023-04-06T07:36:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Action required
  
Following our recent messages concerning the changes needed for your website domains, we would like to inform you that we have extended the support for the previous configuration until April 10 2023.
If you have not made the needeed changes yet, please consult our manual article here.
If you need assistance doing the changes, please contact our support team and we will be happy to assist you with the modifications. Please make sure to have access to your registrar (Gandi, OVH, Godaddy…) so we can assist you in performing this change.
Thanks,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yannick, Customer Care Team Leader - Pro Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[403 and 404 Errors Across Multiple Endpoints]]></title>
        <id>https://airbnbapi.statuspage.io/incidents/3v91lr711bpb</id>
        <link href="https://airbnbapi.statuspage.io/incidents/3v91lr711bpb"/>
        <updated>2023-04-05T09:01:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apr  5, 02:01 PDT
Resolved - We have identified and resolved an internal issue that resulted in 403 and 404 errors across multiple API endpoints. The incident was active between April 4th 20:00 PDT and April 5th 00:00 PDT. You can retry any failed requests at this point, and if you keep experiencing issues, please contact the API integration team for additional help.
We apologize for the inconvenience caused.
Apr  5, 00:51 PDT
Monitoring - A fix has been implemented and we are monitoring the results.
Apr  4, 23:15 PDT
Identified - The issue has been identified and a fix is being implemented.
Apr  4, 21:57 PDT
Investigating - We are currently investigating an issue related to 403 and 404 Errors across multiple endpoints. We'll post updates as we have more information.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Airbnb API Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[XML Migration Enforcement]]></title>
        <id>https://airbnbapi.statuspage.io/incidents/g18hcjbzzsfk</id>
        <link href="https://airbnbapi.statuspage.io/incidents/g18hcjbzzsfk"/>
        <updated>2023-04-05T08:46:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apr  5, 01:46 PDT
Completed - The scheduled maintenance has been completed.
Jul  5, 13:00 PDT
In progress - Scheduled maintenance is currently in progress. We will provide updates as necessary.
Jun 30, 10:55 PDT
Scheduled - As announced on July 5, 2021 we are deprecating our XML API connection.
XML listings can no longer be activated: this means that new XML listings will remain unlisted even if you set 
true
. The same is valid for existing listing that are deactivated (i.e. you will not be able to reactivate a XML listing if it gets unlisted).
More information about this enforcement here: https://developer.airbnb.com/docs/enforcement]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Airbnb API Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[500 Errors Across Multiple Endpoints]]></title>
        <id>https://airbnbapi.statuspage.io/incidents/flsz0qg3ysj6</id>
        <link href="https://airbnbapi.statuspage.io/incidents/flsz0qg3ysj6"/>
        <updated>2023-04-05T02:03:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apr  4, 19:03 PDT
Resolved - We have identified and resolved an internal issue that resulted in 500 errors across multiple API endpoints. The incident was active between 17:30 and 19:00 PDT on April 4th. You can retry any failed requests at this point, and if you keep experiencing issues, please contact the API integration team for additional help.
We apologize for the inconvenience.
Apr  4, 18:30 PDT
Monitoring - A fix has been implemented and we are monitoring the results.
Apr  4, 18:06 PDT
Investigating - We are currently investigating an issue related to 500 errors across multiple endpoints. We'll post updates as we have more information.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Airbnb API Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[500 Errors on Price Quote and Reservation Endpoints]]></title>
        <id>https://airbnbapi.statuspage.io/incidents/s6nclwbgvrb3</id>
        <link href="https://airbnbapi.statuspage.io/incidents/s6nclwbgvrb3"/>
        <updated>2023-04-04T05:24:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apr  3, 22:24 PDT
Resolved - We have identified and resolved an internal issue that resulted in 500 errors across multiple API endpoints, especially calendar operations, reservations and price quote endpoints. The incident was active between 17:00 and 20:10 PDT on April 3rd. You can retry any failed requests at this point, and if you keep experiencing issues, please contact the API integration team for additional help.
We apologize for the inconvenience.
Apr  3, 21:58 PDT
Monitoring - A fix has been implemented and we are monitoring the results.
Apr  3, 20:25 PDT
Identified - The issue has been identified and we are working on a fix.
Apr  3, 17:58 PDT
Update - The issue is now impacting more endpoints including calendar operations and rate plan, we'll post updates as we have more information.
Apr  3, 17:45 PDT
Investigating - We are currently investigating an issue related to 500 errors on price quote API and reservation APIs. We'll post updates as we have more information.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Airbnb API Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TS-2023-004]]></title>
        <id>https://tailscale.com/security-bulletins/#ts-2023-004/</id>
        <link href="https://tailscale.com/security-bulletins/#ts-2023-004/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-04T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Description: An issue in the Tailscale coordination server allowed tailnets created by GitHub organizations which were subsequently renamed to be associated with a new GitHub organization with the previous name.
What happened?
Tailscale mapped tailnets created by GitHub organizations to their organization name, rather than to their organization ID. This meant that if a GitHub organization was renamed, and the previous name taken over by a new GitHub organization, the existing tailnet would be tied to the new GitHub organization instead of the original one.
Who is affected?
Up to 1,305 tailnets created by GitHub organizations may have been affected, if those GitHub organizations were renamed between 2021-06-18 and 2023-03-30 and fully relinquished the old GitHub organization name. Additiona…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Security Bulletins on Tailscale</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident with Git Operations]]></title>
        <id>https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/5nlnzt80fk7g</id>
        <link href="https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/5nlnzt80fk7g"/>
        <updated>2023-04-03T22:41:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apr  3, 22:41 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Apr  3, 22:17 UTC
Update - We have mitigated the intermittent errors for Git requests and are continuing to monitor the system
Apr  3, 21:52 UTC
Update - We are currently working to mitigate intermittent errors for Git requests
Apr  3, 21:32 UTC
Update - We are currently investigating intermittent errors for Git requests
Apr  3, 20:57 UTC
Investigating - We are investigating reports of degraded performance for Git Operations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GitHub Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident: Some users have trouble receiving 2FA code via SMS]]></title>
        <id>https://status.slack.com//2023-04/fdaa42009b1486bc</id>
        <link href="https://status.slack.com//2023-04/fdaa42009b1486bc"/>
        <updated>2023-04-03T21:29:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Issue summary: 

On April 3rd, 2023 from 11:00 AM PDT until 11:45 AM PDT, users on certain cellular service networks had issues receiving SMS texts for two-factor authentication (2FA). 


Upon investigation, this was traced to one unverified toll free number, which prevented 2FA codes from being approved for delivery. That number was removed from our 2FA pool, and services have resumed as usual. We are reviewing our process and alerting around outgoing phone number verification to ensure the issue doesn't happen again.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Slack System Status</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident with Actions and Pages]]></title>
        <id>https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/0d1bcqt29hm2</id>
        <link href="https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/0d1bcqt29hm2"/>
        <updated>2023-04-03T19:00:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apr  3, 19:00 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Apr  3, 19:00 UTC
Update - Actions is operating normally.
Apr  3, 18:43 UTC
Update - We are investigating issues with workflow run failures when downloading actions.
Apr  3, 18:42 UTC
Update - Pages is experiencing degraded performance. We are still investigating and will provide an update when we have one.
Apr  3, 18:35 UTC
Investigating - We are investigating reports of degraded performance for Actions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GitHub Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Issues loading Devices page]]></title>
        <id>https://status.rippling.com/incidents/n1h5yd5mmfc9</id>
        <link href="https://status.rippling.com/incidents/n1h5yd5mmfc9"/>
        <updated>2023-04-03T17:46:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apr  3, 17:46 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Apr  3, 16:57 UTC
Identified - The issue has been identified and a fix is being implemented.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rippling Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>