<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2023-08-17T00:18:59.896Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2023-08-17T00:18:59.896Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mexico SMS Carrier Maintenance - AT&T]]></title>
        <id>https://status.twilio.com/incidents/z4t80hdw4fxn</id>
        <link href="https://status.twilio.com/incidents/z4t80hdw4fxn"/>
        <updated>2023-08-17T06:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[THIS IS A SCHEDULED EVENT Aug 16, 23:00 PDT  -  Aug 17, 05:00 PDT
Aug 14, 21:19 PDT
Scheduled - The AT&T network in Mexico is conducting an emergency maintenance from 16 August 2023 at 23:00 PDT until 17 August 2023 at 05:00 PDT. During the maintenance window, there could be intermittent delays delivering SMS to and from AT&T Mexico handsets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Twilio Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US Voice Carrier Partner Maintenance]]></title>
        <id>https://status.twilio.com/incidents/vmdzjgxy94pw</id>
        <link href="https://status.twilio.com/incidents/vmdzjgxy94pw"/>
        <updated>2023-08-17T06:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[THIS IS A SCHEDULED EVENT Aug 16, 23:00 PDT  -  Aug 17, 02:00 PDT
Aug 11, 15:45 PDT
Scheduled - Our Voice carrier Partner in the US is conducting a planned maintenance from 16 August 2023 at 23:00 PDT until 17 August 2023 at 02:00 PDT. During the maintenance window, there could be intermittent call disconnects and call failures for calls to a subset of Twilio toll-free US phone numbers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Twilio Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US SMS Carriers Maintenance - Small US Carriers]]></title>
        <id>https://status.twilio.com/incidents/34bsbxqgbscw</id>
        <link href="https://status.twilio.com/incidents/34bsbxqgbscw"/>
        <updated>2023-08-17T04:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[THIS IS A SCHEDULED EVENT Aug 16, 21:30 PDT  -  Aug 17, 02:00 PDT
Aug  9, 18:22 PDT
Scheduled - A subset of small US networks in the US is conducting a planned maintenance from 16 August 2023 at 21:30 PDT until 17 August 2023 at 02:00 PDT. During the maintenance window, there could be intermittent delays delivering SMS to and from small US Carriers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Twilio Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chile SMS Carrier Maintenance - WOM (Nextel)]]></title>
        <id>https://status.twilio.com/incidents/57csfdnmw61n</id>
        <link href="https://status.twilio.com/incidents/57csfdnmw61n"/>
        <updated>2023-08-17T03:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[THIS IS A SCHEDULED EVENT Aug 16, 20:00 PDT  -  Aug 17, 03:00 PDT
Aug 16, 11:45 PDT
Scheduled - The WOM (Nextel) network in Chile is conducting an emergency maintenance from 16 August 2023 at 20:00 PDT until 17 August 2023 at 03:00 PDT. During the maintenance window, there could be intermittent delays delivering SMS to and from WOM (Nextel) handsets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Twilio Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Russia SMS Carrier Maintenance - MTT]]></title>
        <id>https://status.twilio.com/incidents/q5qgkvblw1j7</id>
        <link href="https://status.twilio.com/incidents/q5qgkvblw1j7"/>
        <updated>2023-08-16T23:55:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Aug 16, 16:55 PDT
Completed - The scheduled maintenance has been completed.
Aug 16, 13:55 PDT
In progress - Scheduled maintenance is currently in progress. We will provide updates as necessary.
Aug 16, 03:21 PDT
Scheduled - The MTT network in Russia is conducting an emergency maintenance from 16 August 2023 at 13:55 PDT until 16 August 2023 at 16:55 PDT. During the maintenance window, there could be intermittent delays delivering SMS to MTT Russia handsets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Twilio Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[France Voice Carrier Partner Maintenance]]></title>
        <id>https://status.twilio.com/incidents/48kyr5pn68v6</id>
        <link href="https://status.twilio.com/incidents/48kyr5pn68v6"/>
        <updated>2023-08-16T22:00:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Aug 16, 15:00 PDT
Completed - The scheduled maintenance has been completed.
Aug 16, 13:00 PDT
In progress - Scheduled maintenance is currently in progress. We will provide updates as necessary.
Aug  8, 12:44 PDT
Scheduled - Our Voice carrier partner in France is conducting a planned maintenance from 16 August 2023 at 13:00 PDT until 16 August 2023 at 15:00 PDT. During the maintenance window, there could be intermittent call disconnects and call failures for calls from and to Twilio France phone numbers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Twilio Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US SMS Carrier Maintenance - T-Mobile]]></title>
        <id>https://status.twilio.com/incidents/bgwwg0m56vx0</id>
        <link href="https://status.twilio.com/incidents/bgwwg0m56vx0"/>
        <updated>2023-08-16T11:01:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Aug 16, 04:01 PDT
Completed - The scheduled maintenance has been completed.
Aug 15, 22:00 PDT
In progress - Scheduled maintenance is currently in progress. We will provide updates as necessary.
Aug 14, 15:31 PDT
Scheduled - The T-Mobile network in the US is conducting an emergency maintenance from 15 August 2023 at 22:00 PDT until 16 August 2023 at 04:00 PDT. During the maintenance window, there could be intermittent delays delivering SMS to and from T-Mobile US handsets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Twilio Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US SMS and MMS Carrier Maintenance - AT&T]]></title>
        <id>https://status.twilio.com/incidents/9pbptdzv5xvr</id>
        <link href="https://status.twilio.com/incidents/9pbptdzv5xvr"/>
        <updated>2023-08-16T09:00:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Aug 16, 02:00 PDT
Completed - The scheduled maintenance has been completed.
Aug 13, 20:00 PDT
In progress - Scheduled maintenance is currently in progress. We will provide updates as necessary.
Aug  9, 16:01 PDT
Scheduled - The AT&T network in the US is conducting a series of planned maintenances from 13 August 2023 at 20:00 PDT until 16 August 2023 at 02:00 PDT. During the maintenance window, there could be intermittent delays delivering SMS and MMS to and from AT&T US handsets.

Note, the maintenance will be carried out on each of the following dates and times:

13 August 2023 at 20:00 PDT until 14 August 2023 at 02:00 PDT
15 August 2023 at 20:00 PDT until 16 August 2023 at 02:00 PDT]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Twilio Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SMS Delivery Delays and Failures To Viva Network In Bolivia]]></title>
        <id>https://status.twilio.com/incidents/khjsvtd4nksk</id>
        <link href="https://status.twilio.com/incidents/khjsvtd4nksk"/>
        <updated>2023-08-16T06:25:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Aug 15, 23:25 PDT
Resolved - We are no longer experiencing SMS delivery delays and failures when sending messages to to Viva Network In Bolivia. This incident has been resolved.
Aug 15, 21:25 PDT
Monitoring - We are observing recovery in SMS delivery delays and failures when sending messages to Viva Network In Bolivia. We will continue monitoring the service to ensure a full recovery. We will provide another update in 2 hours or as soon as more information becomes available.
Aug 15, 20:28 PDT
Update - We continue to experience SMS delivery delays and failures when sending messages to Viva Network In Bolivia. Our engineers are working with our carrier partner to resolve the issue. We will provide another update in 2 hours or as soon as more information becomes available.
Aug 15, 19:28 PDT
Investigating - We are experiencing SMS delivery delays when sending messages to Viva Network In Bolivia. Our engineers are working with our carrier partner to resolve the issue. We will provide another update in 1 hour or as soon as more information becomes available.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Twilio Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[App Platform Deployments]]></title>
        <id>https://status.digitalocean.com/incidents/cst5jm8gwzsz</id>
        <link href="https://status.digitalocean.com/incidents/cst5jm8gwzsz"/>
        <updated>2023-08-16T06:05:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Aug 16, 06:05 UTC
Resolved - As of 05:55, our Engineering team has resolved the issue impacting Python builds for the App platform. The users will not be experiencing the error "Requested runtime 'python-3.11.3' is not available for this stack (heroku-18)" during the build deployment. 
We appreciate your patience throughout the process and if you continue to experience problems, please open a ticket with our Support team for further review.
Aug 16, 05:28 UTC
Monitoring - As of 05:18 UTC, our Engineering team has deployed a fix to resolve the issue impacting Python builds for App platform. We are actively monitoring the situation to ensure stability and will provide an update once the incident has been fully resolved. Thank you for your patience and we apologize for the inconvenience.
Aug 16, 01:30 UTC
Update - Our Engineering team continues work on the rollout with the fix for Python builds failing in App Platform. 
We've identified that a very small number of Apps are impacted by this issue - less than 1% of users have encountered this issue. 
We will post an update once the rollout completes.
Aug 15, 20:27 UTC
Identified - Our Engineering team has investigated and identified an issue impacting Python builds for App Platform. Beginning approximately 17:30 UTC, users will see the error "Requested runtime 'python-3.11.3' is not available for this stack (heroku-18)". 
The team is in the process of rolling out a fix. 
In the meantime as a workaround, users may update their Apps to use the Ubuntu 22.04-based stack. This stack is in beta, but provides dependency upgrades, and removes support for PHP version 8.0 and earlier. To update, users will need to specify the new stack in the app spec by adding: 
"features:
    - buildpack-stack=ubuntu-22"
We will post another update once the fix has completed rolling out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>DigitalOcean Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SMS Delivery Delays and Failures to Telstra in Australia]]></title>
        <id>https://status.twilio.com/incidents/qg7144ktx77d</id>
        <link href="https://status.twilio.com/incidents/qg7144ktx77d"/>
        <updated>2023-08-16T00:21:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Aug 15, 17:21 PDT
Resolved - We are no longer experiencing SMS delivery delays and failures when sending messages to Telstra in Australia. This incident has been resolved.
Aug 15, 15:22 PDT
Monitoring - We are observing recovery in SMS delivery delays and failures when sending messages to Telstra in Australia. We will continue monitoring the service to ensure a full recovery. We will provide another update in 2 hours or as soon as more information becomes available.
Aug 15, 13:29 PDT
Update - We are experiencing SMS delivery delays and failures when sending messages to Telstra in Australia. Our engineers are working with our carrier partner to resolve the issue. We will provide another update in 2 hours or as soon as more information becomes available.
Aug 15, 12:31 PDT
Investigating - We are experiencing SMS delivery delays and failures when sending messages to Telstra in Australia. Our engineers are working with our carrier partner to resolve the issue. We will provide another update in 1 hour or as soon as more information becomes available.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Twilio Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Users authenticating to networks utilizing RADIUS are experiencing timeouts]]></title>
        <id>https://status.rippling.com/incidents/233zk80cc63v</id>
        <link href="https://status.rippling.com/incidents/233zk80cc63v"/>
        <updated>2023-08-15T23:10:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Aug 15, 23:10 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Aug 15, 23:06 UTC
Monitoring - A fix has been implemented and we are monitoring the results.
Aug 15, 23:04 UTC
Identified - The issue has been identified and a fix is being implemented.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rippling Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US SMS and MMS Carrier Maintenance - AT&T]]></title>
        <id>https://status.twilio.com/incidents/gtg65x9ybpbj</id>
        <link href="https://status.twilio.com/incidents/gtg65x9ybpbj"/>
        <updated>2023-08-15T22:01:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Aug 15, 15:01 PDT
Completed - The scheduled maintenance has been completed.
Aug 15, 09:00 PDT
In progress - Scheduled maintenance is currently in progress. We will provide updates as necessary.
Aug 14, 02:21 PDT
Scheduled - The AT&T network in the US is conducting a planned maintenance from 15 August 2023 at 09:00 PDT until 15 August 2023 at 15:00 PDT. During the maintenance window, there could be intermittent delays delivering SMS and MMS to and from AT&T US handsets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Twilio Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident with Webhooks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/ljhhhw2tplqp</id>
        <link href="https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/ljhhhw2tplqp"/>
        <updated>2023-08-15T21:46:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Aug 15, 21:46 UTC
Resolved - The backlog of webhook deliveries has been processed and delivery times have returned to normal.
Aug 15, 20:33 UTC
Update - We are continuing to process our backlog of webhook deliveries and our estimated time to clear the backlog is 2 hours.
Aug 15, 19:24 UTC
Update - We are processing our backlog of webhook deliveries and estimate that it will take 3 hours to clear. Webhook deliveries will be delayed during this time.
Aug 15, 18:20 UTC
Update - We are continuing to investigate the degraded performance of Webhooks and will provide further updates as we continue to investigate.  The current impact is delayed delivery of webhooks.
Aug 15, 18:05 UTC
Update - We are continuing to investigate the degraded performance of Webhooks. The current impact is delayed delivery of hooks.
Aug 15, 17:24 UTC
Investigating - We are investigating reports of degraded performance for Webhooks]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GitHub Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FRA1 Network Maintenance Phase 2]]></title>
        <id>https://status.digitalocean.com/incidents/y7tbd8m83pzj</id>
        <link href="https://status.digitalocean.com/incidents/y7tbd8m83pzj"/>
        <updated>2023-08-15T20:59:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Aug 15, 20:59 UTC
Completed - The scheduled maintenance has been completed.
Aug 15, 18:02 UTC
In progress - Scheduled maintenance is currently in progress. We will provide updates as necessary.
Aug 15, 17:06 UTC
Scheduled - Start: 2023-08-15 18:00 UTC
End: 2023-08-15 22:00 UTC
During the above window, our Networking team will be making changes to our core networking infrastructure to improve performance and scalability in the FRA1 region. This will be the second of the two maintenance activities performed by our team in the region on consecutive days.
Expected Impact:
These upgrades are designed and tested to be seamless and we do not expect any impact to customer traffic due to this maintenance. If an unexpected issue arises, affected Droplets and Droplet-based services may experience a temporary loss of private connectivity between VPCs. We will endeavor to keep any such impact to a minimum.
If you have any questions or concerns regarding this maintenance, please reach out to us by opening up a ticket on your account via https://cloudsupport.digitalocean.com/s/createticket.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>DigitalOcean Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident with Webhooks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/fjj29dxw0m7c</id>
        <link href="https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/fjj29dxw0m7c"/>
        <updated>2023-08-15T17:41:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Aug 15, 17:41 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Aug 15, 17:24 UTC
Investigating - We are investigating reports of degraded performance for Webhooks]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GitHub Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Canada Account Security Service Partner Maintenance]]></title>
        <id>https://status.twilio.com/incidents/5hn3lfp77p49</id>
        <link href="https://status.twilio.com/incidents/5hn3lfp77p49"/>
        <updated>2023-08-15T10:00:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Aug 15, 03:00 PDT
Completed - The scheduled maintenance has been completed.
Aug 14, 21:00 PDT
In progress - Scheduled maintenance is currently in progress. We will provide updates as necessary.
Aug 11, 21:06 PDT
Scheduled - Our service partner is conducting a planned maintenance from 14 August 2023 at 21:00 PDT until 15 August 2023 at 03:00 PDT. During the maintenance window, there could be intermittent API request failures for the following destination: Canada 

Impacted Products: 
Lookup SIM Swap 
Legacy Identity MatchAndAttributes]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Twilio Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Russia SMS Carrier Maintenance - MTS]]></title>
        <id>https://status.twilio.com/incidents/rzp5twt2bw71</id>
        <link href="https://status.twilio.com/incidents/rzp5twt2bw71"/>
        <updated>2023-08-15T06:02:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Aug 14, 23:02 PDT
Completed - The scheduled maintenance has been completed.
Aug 14, 21:30 PDT
In progress - Scheduled maintenance is currently in progress. We will provide updates as necessary.
Aug 14, 02:27 PDT
Scheduled - The MTS network in Russia is conducting a planned maintenance from 14 August 2023 at 21:30 PDT until 14 August 2023 at 23:00 PDT. During the maintenance window, there could be intermittent delays delivering SMS to MTS Russia handsets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Twilio Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Queue Real Stats Page Is Showing Incorrect Info for Longest Tasks]]></title>
        <id>https://status.twilio.com/incidents/ncdlqn1ngxr6</id>
        <link href="https://status.twilio.com/incidents/ncdlqn1ngxr6"/>
        <updated>2023-08-15T05:29:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Aug 14, 22:29 PDT
Resolved - Incorrect information has been resolved and real time queue stats page in Flex is operating normally at this time.
Aug 14, 21:59 PDT
Update - Real time queue stats page in Flex is now operating normally. We will continue to monitor for system stability. We'll provide another update in 30 minutes or as soon as more information becomes available.
Aug 14, 21:29 PDT
Monitoring - Real time queue stats page in Flex is now operating normally. We will continue to monitor for system stability. We'll provide another update in 30 minutes or as soon as more information becomes available.
Aug 14, 19:29 PDT
Update - We are still investigating incorrect information showing on the real time queue stats page in Flex. We expect to provide another update in 2 hours or as soon as …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Twilio Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Belarus SMS Carrier Maintenance - A1, MTS, Life]]></title>
        <id>https://status.twilio.com/incidents/w96981ck6qhq</id>
        <link href="https://status.twilio.com/incidents/w96981ck6qhq"/>
        <updated>2023-08-15T03:01:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Aug 14, 20:01 PDT
Completed - The scheduled maintenance has been completed.
Aug 14, 15:00 PDT
In progress - Scheduled maintenance is currently in progress. We will provide updates as necessary.
Aug 11, 04:16 PDT
Scheduled - The A1, MTS and Life networks in Belarus are conducting a planned maintenance from 14 August 2023 at 15:00 PDT until 14 August 2023 at 20:00 PDT. During the maintenance window, there could be intermittent delays delivering SMS to Belarus handsets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Twilio Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FRA1 Network Maintenance Phase 1]]></title>
        <id>https://status.digitalocean.com/incidents/jqpf8zhmx2j3</id>
        <link href="https://status.digitalocean.com/incidents/jqpf8zhmx2j3"/>
        <updated>2023-08-14T22:23:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Aug 14, 22:23 UTC
Completed - The scheduled maintenance has been completed.
Aug 14, 20:12 UTC
Update - Our Engineering team has completed the rollback and VPC connectivity for all Droplets and Droplet-based services is restored. 
We'll now continue this maintenance as scheduled. 
We apologize for the brief interruption.
Aug 14, 20:03 UTC
Verifying - Our Engineering team has identified an issue stemming from this maintenance, which impacts approximately 1-3% of Droplets and Droplet-based services in our FRA1 region. 
At this time, a small percentage of customers will experience VPC network connectivity issues. An emergency rollback is already underway to mitigate this issue. 
We will update this post with further information as soon as possible.
Aug 14, 18:42 UTC
In progress - Scheduled maintenance is currently in progress. We will provide updates as necessary.
Aug 14, 18:41 UTC
Scheduled - Start: 2023-08-14 18:00 UTC
End: 2023-08-14 22:00 UTC
During the above window, our Networking team will be making changes to our core networking infrastructure to improve performance and scalability in the FRA1 region. This maintenance will occur in two parts on consecutive days and we will send another maintenance notice for the second phase. 
Expected Impact:
These upgrades are designed and tested to be seamless and we do not expect any impact to customer traffic due to this maintenance. If an unexpected issue arises, affected Droplets and Droplet-based services may experience a temporary loss of private connectivity between VPCs. We will endeavor to keep any such impact to a minimum.
If you have any questions or concerns regarding this maintenance, please reach out to us by opening up a ticket on your account via https://cloudsupport.digitalocean.com/s/createticket.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>DigitalOcean Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Container Registry in Multiple Regions]]></title>
        <id>https://status.digitalocean.com/incidents/45pv9lj0zj1v</id>
        <link href="https://status.digitalocean.com/incidents/45pv9lj0zj1v"/>
        <updated>2023-08-12T04:27:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Aug 12, 04:27 UTC
Resolved - From 23:16 - 04:00, updates to DigitalOcean Container Registry images were not displayed correctly in the UI (Cloud Control Panel), due to a lapsed internal authorization token. Our Engineering team was able to issue a new token and rolled out the change regionally in order to not disrupt multiple data planes at once. 
This issue is fully resolved. If you continue to experience problems, please open a ticket with our Support team. Thank you for your patience and we apologize for the inconvenience.
Aug 12, 03:54 UTC
Monitoring - Our Engineering team has confirmed the root cause of the issue with updates to the UI for DigitalOcean Container Registry and a fix is now rolling out regionally. 
As this rolls out, we expect users to once again be able to see updates to Container Registry images in the UI (Cloud Control Panel). 
We will post another update once the fix finishes rolling out in all regions.
Aug 12, 02:09 UTC
Identified - From 23:16 UTC, our Engineering team has identified an issue with DigitalOcean Container Registry and is actively working on a fix. During this time, customers will not be able to see changes on UI for new DOCR Images in multiple regions. We will post an update as soon as additional information is available.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>DigitalOcean Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[We are investigating reports of degraded performance.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/sz8pjjhzcy3t</id>
        <link href="https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/sz8pjjhzcy3t"/>
        <updated>2023-08-11T21:41:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Aug 11, 21:41 UTC
Resolved - This issue has been resolved.
Aug 11, 20:44 UTC
Update - From 16:45-20:01 UTC, OAuth App and GitHub App user auth tokens created with OAuth flow were not SAML authorized as expected. App authorizations created during this time may need to be reauthorized.
Aug 11, 20:44 UTC
Investigating - We are currently investigating this issue.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GitHub Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SGP1 Network Maintenance - Phase 2]]></title>
        <id>https://status.digitalocean.com/incidents/xh9qhhhvcl77</id>
        <link href="https://status.digitalocean.com/incidents/xh9qhhhvcl77"/>
        <updated>2023-08-10T23:24:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Aug 10, 23:24 UTC
Completed - The scheduled maintenance has been completed.
Aug 10, 20:00 UTC
In progress - Scheduled maintenance is currently in progress. We will provide updates as necessary.
Aug  6, 14:39 UTC
Scheduled - Start: 2023-08-10 20:00 UTC
End:  2023-08-11 00:00 UTC
During the above window, our Networking team will be making changes to our core networking infrastructure to improve performance and scalability in the SGP1 region. 
Expected impact:
These upgrades are designed and tested to be seamless and we do not expect any impact to customer traffic due to this maintenance. If an unexpected issue arises, affected Droplets and Droplet-based services may experience a temporary loss of private connectivity between VPCs. We will endeavor to keep any such impact to a minimum.
If you have any questions related to this issue please send us a ticket from your cloud support page. https://cloudsupport.digitalocean.com/s/createticket]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>DigitalOcean Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Support tickets submission issue]]></title>
        <id>https://airbnbapi.statuspage.io/incidents/6c9mb4kd3fy7</id>
        <link href="https://airbnbapi.statuspage.io/incidents/6c9mb4kd3fy7"/>
        <updated>2023-08-10T22:27:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Aug 10, 15:27 PDT
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Aug 10, 05:08 PDT
Investigating - We are currently investigating an issue that prevents partners from creating Support Tickets. For critical issues that require escalation, kindly contact your Airbnb Connectivity Partner Manager. 
Please see ticket priority guidelines - https://developer.airbnb.com/docs/create-and-manage-support-cases#ticket-priority
Our engineering teams are working to get everything up and running again, and we will update you with the latest information as soon as possible.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Airbnb API Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident: Trouble signing into the desktop app for some Enterprise Grid customers]]></title>
        <id>https://status.slack.com//2023-08/c68673e38899ac38</id>
        <link href="https://status.slack.com//2023-08/c68673e38899ac38"/>
        <updated>2023-08-10T21:28:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Issue Summary:

On August 9, 2023 from 9:00 AM PDT to August 10th 2023, 8:00 AM PDT, some Enterprise Grid users experienced a failure to redirect from browser to app during login - focus was moved to the app, but the sign in process did not complete.


We made a change to some logging functions and introduced a fix that mitigated the issue. This fix is permanent and will keep this issue from happening again.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Slack System Status</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident with Webhooks and Actions]]></title>
        <id>https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/rk1918knvr0w</id>
        <link href="https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/rk1918knvr0w"/>
        <updated>2023-08-10T21:20:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Aug 10, 21:20 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Aug 10, 21:07 UTC
Update - Webhooks delivery latency has recovered, and we will continue to monitor.
Aug 10, 20:56 UTC
Update - Actions is operating normally.
Aug 10, 20:21 UTC
Update - We have applied mitigations and are seeing improvements in webhooks delivery latency. We continue to monitor for full recovery. We are also working to mitigate unrelated issues with Actions.
Aug 10, 19:47 UTC
Update - Actions is experiencing degraded performance. We are continuing to investigate.
Aug 10, 19:33 UTC
Update - We are still working to resolve high webhooks delivery latency.
Aug 10, 18:54 UTC
Update - We are still seeing high latency in webhook delivery and are actively working to resolve the issue.
Aug 10, 18:12 UTC
Update - Webhooks deliveries are experiencing high latency. We are actively investigating and working to mitigate.
Aug 10, 17:35 UTC
Investigating - We are investigating reports of degraded performance for Webhooks]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GitHub Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SGP1 Network Maintenance - Phase 1]]></title>
        <id>https://status.digitalocean.com/incidents/k65k44vxwr9j</id>
        <link href="https://status.digitalocean.com/incidents/k65k44vxwr9j"/>
        <updated>2023-08-09T22:46:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Aug  9, 22:46 UTC
Completed - The scheduled maintenance has been completed.
Aug  9, 20:01 UTC
In progress - Scheduled maintenance is currently in progress. We will provide updates as necessary.
Aug  6, 14:36 UTC
Scheduled - Start: 2023-08-09 20:00 UTC
End:  2023-08-10 00:00 UTC
During the above window, our Networking team will be making changes to our core networking infrastructure to improve performance and scalability in the SGP1 region. This maintenance will occur in two parts on consecutive days and we will send another maintenance notice for the second phase.
Expected impact:
These upgrades are designed and tested to be seamless and we do not expect any impact to customer traffic due to this maintenance. If an unexpected issue arises, affected Droplets and Droplet-based services may experience a temporary loss of private connectivity between VPCs. We will endeavor to keep any such impact to a minimum.
If you have any questions related to this issue please send us a ticket from your cloud support page. https://cloudsupport.digitalocean.com/s/createticket]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>DigitalOcean Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident with Git Operations and Actions]]></title>
        <id>https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/nwb8m3ppfxw6</id>
        <link href="https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/nwb8m3ppfxw6"/>
        <updated>2023-08-09T20:14:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Aug  9, 20:14 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Aug  9, 20:02 UTC
Update - Git Operations is operating normally.
Aug  9, 19:54 UTC
Update - Actions is experiencing degraded performance. We are continuing to investigate.
Aug  9, 19:42 UTC
Investigating - We are investigating reports of degraded performance for Git Operations]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GitHub Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Networking in AMS3, LON1, and SFO2]]></title>
        <id>https://status.digitalocean.com/incidents/q4b09b022nmh</id>
        <link href="https://status.digitalocean.com/incidents/q4b09b022nmh"/>
        <updated>2023-08-09T16:01:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Aug  9, 16:01 UTC
Resolved - Our Engineering team has confirmed full resolution of the issue impacting network connectivity in multiple regions. The impact has been completely subsided and the network connectivity is back to normal for all the impacted services. Users should now be able to process events normally for Droplets and Droplet-based services like Load Balancers, Kubernetes or Database clusters, etc.
If you continue to experience problems, please open a ticket with our support team from your Cloud Control Panel.
Thank you for your patience and we apologize for any inconvenience.
Aug  9, 14:58 UTC
Monitoring - The rollout of the fix to redundant networking equipment is fully completed, meaning all networking devices in AMS3, LON1, and SFO2 have been patched. Our Engineering team s…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>DigitalOcean Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident: Users may be experiencing issues uploading images and creating canvases.]]></title>
        <id>https://status.slack.com//2023-08/5f97959abbaeeaa1</id>
        <link href="https://status.slack.com//2023-08/5f97959abbaeeaa1"/>
        <updated>2023-08-07T17:39:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Issue Summary:


On August 7, 2023, customers may have experienced issues with loading images, creating canvases, and workflow modals being delayed. A small number of customers may have been impacted as early as 5:50 AM PDT, with larger impact seen between 7:03AM PDT to 7:14AM PDT.


We traced the issue to a change that caused our server infrastructure to be overloaded. We rolled back this change, resolving the issue for all impacted users.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Slack System Status</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Increased site latency]]></title>
        <id>https://status.rippling.com/incidents/s4g3w61q9lsr</id>
        <link href="https://status.rippling.com/incidents/s4g3w61q9lsr"/>
        <updated>2023-08-07T17:35:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Aug  7, 17:35 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved. Site performance should be back to normal.
Aug  7, 16:26 UTC
Monitoring - We've stopped a data migration job that is believed to be contributing, and we're now seeing site latency return back to baseline numbers. The site latency should now be back to normal, but we are continuing to monitor.
Aug  7, 16:01 UTC
Investigating - There is degraded performance across the Rippling application, with certain pages loading slowly. We are investigating the issue.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rippling Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident: Some users may be experiencing issues uploading files.]]></title>
        <id>https://status.slack.com//2023-08/8fd09ebe40c64df0</id>
        <link href="https://status.slack.com//2023-08/8fd09ebe40c64df0"/>
        <updated>2023-08-04T19:19:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’ve restored full functionality to file uploads for all impacted users. You may need to reload Slack (Command/Ctrl + Shift + R) in order for this fix to be reflected on your end. We’re sorry for the disruption we brought to your day.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Slack System Status</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident: Users may be experiencing issues connecting to Slack]]></title>
        <id>https://status.slack.com//2023-08/8ec13e4962a9bf43</id>
        <link href="https://status.slack.com//2023-08/8ec13e4962a9bf43"/>
        <updated>2023-08-03T02:32:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Issue summary:

On August 2, 2023 from 9:01 AM PDT to 11:00 AM PDT, customers may have experienced issues with blurry images in Slack, as well as trouble uploading files. A small percentage of customers may have also experienced errors or slowness when loading channels, sending messages, accessing admin pages, and connecting to Slack.


An issue with a routine database cluster migration inadvertently caused a decrease in capacity. Unfortunately, this coincided with a scheduled job to process a large number of custom status requests, an activity that commonly occurs at the top of each hour. The number of incoming requests exceeded the unintentionally reduced capacity of the database cluster, leading to errors and sluggishness for some actions in Slack. As these requests piled up, other Slack services began to experience issues as well, including a small number of users being unable to connect.


We paused the scheduled custom status job to immediately mitigate the load on the affected database cluster. This resolved some of the errors affecting Slack services. Once we established we had sufficient capacity to handle the scheduled job, we resumed processing the custom status requests, fully restoring normal service for all affected users.


Once the load was balanced and custom status processing had returned to normal, we deployed a fix to correct the issue with the database cluster migration, bringing capacity back to the expected level.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Slack System Status</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RESOLVED: We're investigating reports of an issue with Classroom. We will provide more information shortly.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.google.com/appsstatus/dashboard/incidents/nukLGccNGE22LWLXw5Tu</id>
        <link href="https://www.google.com/appsstatus/dashboard/incidents/nukLGccNGE22LWLXw5Tu"/>
        <updated>2023-08-02T20:08:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p> Incident began at <strong>2023-07-24 14:50</strong> and ended at <strong>2023-07-26 11:15</strong> <span>(times are in <strong>Coordinated Universal Time (UTC)</strong>).</span></p><div class="cBIRi14aVDP__status-update-text"><h1>Incident Report</h1>
<h2>Summary</h2>
<p>On 24 July 2023 at 07:50, following a Google Classroom iOS app update,  the app would not load properly if users attempted to access any course page that had attached materials for a duration of 1 day, 20 hours, 25 minutes. During the disruption, users were able to access course pages by uninstalling and reinstalling the Classroom iOS app.</p>
<h2>Root Cause</h2>
<p>The root cause has been identified as a bug, triggered by an update released for Classroom iOS, that caused an issue with the local database migration. This caused the iOS app to not load properly when users attempted to access course pages with attached materials, as the migration was specific to the materials configuration.</p>
<h2>Remediation and Prevention</h2>
<p>Google engineers were alerted to the issue via internal monitoring on 24 July 2023 at 07:50 US/Pacific and immediately started an investigation. Google engineers reproduced the issue,  identified the trigger as a failed database migration, and paused the auto update. This prevented any further disruption. An app update with a fix was released for the Classroom iOS app, thereby resolving the issue on 26 July 2023 at 04:15 US/Pacific. Users who had already updated to the problematic app version were advised to either uninstall and reinstall or update the app to the version with the fix.</p>
<p>Google is committed to preventing recurrence by implementing the following action items:</p>
<ul>
<li>Implement additional pre-release migration and application testing plans to validate app stability</li>
</ul>
</div><hr><p>Affected products: Classroom</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Workspace Status Dashboard Updates</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident with Copilot]]></title>
        <id>https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/s9scz41r9wkx</id>
        <link href="https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/s9scz41r9wkx"/>
        <updated>2023-08-01T20:28:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Aug  1, 20:28 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Aug  1, 20:12 UTC
Investigating - We are investigating reports of degraded performance for Copilot]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GitHub Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mobile Push Notifications]]></title>
        <id>https://status.notion.so/incidents/56mkzzfczbws</id>
        <link href="https://status.notion.so/incidents/56mkzzfczbws"/>
        <updated>2023-08-01T17:10:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Aug  1, 10:10 PDT
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Aug  1, 10:10 PDT
Investigating - Between 7/26 and 8/1, Notion experienced an issue which prevented users from receiving push notifications on mobile devices. The issue was resolved today, at approximately 9:45 am PDT.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Notion Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident: Channel canvases not loading correctly.]]></title>
        <id>https://status.slack.com//2023-07/4a00e5109815910b</id>
        <link href="https://status.slack.com//2023-07/4a00e5109815910b"/>
        <updated>2023-07-28T23:12:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Issue Summary:


From July 26th, 2023 at 8:00AM PDT to July 28th 2023 at 1:00PM PDT some users had trouble loading and editing canvases when accessing them from the channel canvas icon.


We determined this issue was caused by a recent code change related to how canvases persist across sessions. We issued a code update which resolved the issue for all impacted users. To see the fix applied, user impacted users should press Command/Control + R. We are also working on deploying a subsequent code update intended to prevent the issue from reoccurring in the future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Slack System Status</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident Affecting LOS Records API]]></title>
        <id>https://airbnbapi.statuspage.io/incidents/9ydjrhv3dwh2</id>
        <link href="https://airbnbapi.statuspage.io/incidents/9ydjrhv3dwh2"/>
        <updated>2023-07-28T18:28:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jul 28, 11:28 PDT
Resolved - [False alarm] This incident was a false alarm—the LOS Records API is working as expected. Apologies for the inconvenience.
Jul 28, 10:02 PDT
Identified - Starting today (July 28, 2023), we identified an issue affecting the LOS Records API. Records for 180 days from today (beyond Jan 24, 2024) are being ignored, and the dates are marked as unavailable on Airbnb, although requests to set those records are not failing. We are actively working to find the root cause, and mitigate this issue. We will post more information as soon as possible.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Airbnb API Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident with Pull Requests]]></title>
        <id>https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/l59z35rhzdky</id>
        <link href="https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/l59z35rhzdky"/>
        <updated>2023-07-28T15:45:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jul 28, 15:45 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Jul 28, 15:38 UTC
Update - We are actively mitigating delays in commits showing on pull requests.
Jul 28, 15:13 UTC
Update - We are investigating an issue which is causing a delay in the time it takes new commits to show up on a pull request.
Jul 28, 14:51 UTC
Update - We are investigating an issue which is causing a delay in the time it takes new commits to show up on a pull request.
Jul 28, 14:49 UTC
Investigating - We are investigating reports of degraded performance for Pull Requests.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GitHub Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Delay in email delivery due to third-party outage]]></title>
        <id>https://status.rippling.com/incidents/dg5nlq85bkk3</id>
        <link href="https://status.rippling.com/incidents/dg5nlq85bkk3"/>
        <updated>2023-07-28T15:44:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jul 28, 15:44 UTC
Resolved - The incident is now resolved
Jul 28, 15:15 UTC
Monitoring - The third party provider has resumed service. We are closely monitoring the status of all outgoing emails
Jul 28, 15:01 UTC
Investigating - Our third-party email delivery provider has been experiencing an intermittent outage since Jul 28th, 7:45 AM PST, causing a delay in notification delivery for all Rippling emails (including password resets). We are investigating this issue with the third-party provider.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rippling Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident with Issues]]></title>
        <id>https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/9f8dkxjg67qq</id>
        <link href="https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/9f8dkxjg67qq"/>
        <updated>2023-07-28T10:00:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jul 28, 10:00 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Jul 28, 09:31 UTC
Investigating - We are investigating reports of degraded performance for Issues.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GitHub Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident with Pull Requests]]></title>
        <id>https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/xfmyxxhcknvj</id>
        <link href="https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/xfmyxxhcknvj"/>
        <updated>2023-07-28T01:08:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jul 28, 01:08 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Jul 28, 00:50 UTC
Update - We have identified a problem causing an issue with Pull Requests for some users. We are working on a mitigation.
Jul 28, 00:07 UTC
Update - We have identified a problem causing an issue with Pull Requests for some users. We are working on a mitigation.
Jul 27, 23:35 UTC
Update - We have identified a problem causing an issue with Pull Requests for some users. We are working on a mitigation.
Jul 27, 22:56 UTC
Update - We are still investigating an issue with Pull Requests. We will continue to keep users updated on progress towards mitigation.
Jul 27, 22:18 UTC
Update - We found an issue with repos that affects ability of some of the customers to merge pull requests. We are working on mitigation.
Jul 27, 22:04 UTC
Investigating - We are investigating reports of degraded performance for Pull Requests.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GitHub Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Issues Affecting Guest Details in Reservation Webhooks]]></title>
        <id>https://airbnbapi.statuspage.io/incidents/fg9fy7k4mhk4</id>
        <link href="https://airbnbapi.statuspage.io/incidents/fg9fy7k4mhk4"/>
        <updated>2023-07-27T19:13:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jul 27, 12:13 PDT
Resolved - We have resolved this incident.
Jul 27, 00:02 PDT
Monitoring - There has been an increase in confirmed reservation notifications not including guest details in full since 2023-07-24.
The issue worsened significantly earlier today on 2023-07-27.
The root cause has been identified and a fix has been implemented.
We are monitoring the situation.
We recommend to retrieve the details with GET reservations requests.
Apologies for the inconvenience caused.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Airbnb API Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Issues with the employee profile payroll tab]]></title>
        <id>https://status.rippling.com/incidents/5b7jz0d5pc9s</id>
        <link href="https://status.rippling.com/incidents/5b7jz0d5pc9s"/>
        <updated>2023-07-27T15:51:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jul 27, 15:51 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Jul 27, 15:30 UTC
Update - A fix has been implemented and product functionality has been restored.
Jul 27, 14:58 UTC
Identified - The issue has been identified and a fix is being implemented.
Jul 27, 14:52 UTC
Update - Users are reporting missing values on the payroll tab in the employee profile. This will be fixed momentarily. This does not impact any processing of payroll.
Jul 27, 14:20 UTC
Monitoring - A fix has been implemented and we are monitoring the results.
Jul 27, 14:18 UTC
Identified - The issue has been identified and a fix is being implemented.
Jul 27, 14:13 UTC
Investigating - Users are reporting issues with signing in to apps that they use Rippling as the identity provider. Our recommended workaround is to sign in to Rippling first and then navigate to the app using the SSO navigation bar. We are currently investigating this issue.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rippling Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Outage: Slack Systemwide Issues]]></title>
        <id>https://status.slack.com//2023-07/08e3781ccbef33d5</id>
        <link href="https://status.slack.com//2023-07/08e3781ccbef33d5"/>
        <updated>2023-07-27T14:32:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Issue summary: 


On July 27, 2023 between 2:03 AM PDT - 2:59 AM PDT, Slack was experiencing a systemwide issue during which users were not able to send or receive messages across multiple platforms. 


Our engineering team identified an issue after a change was made to a service that manages our internal system communication. This resulted in degradation of Slack functionality until the change was reverted which resolved the issue for all users. 


We are currently hard at work on scoping measures to prevent this from happening in the future. More information about remediation and prevention steps will be included in an upcoming RCA which you can request by writing into feedback@slack.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Slack System Status</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SFO3 Network Maintenance Phase 2]]></title>
        <id>https://status.digitalocean.com/incidents/szklqql7y77c</id>
        <link href="https://status.digitalocean.com/incidents/szklqql7y77c"/>
        <updated>2023-07-27T03:20:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jul 27, 03:20 UTC
Completed - The scheduled maintenance has been completed.
Jul 27, 01:02 UTC
In progress - Scheduled maintenance is currently in progress. We will provide updates as necessary.
Jul 26, 23:08 UTC
Scheduled - Start: 2023-07-27 01:00 UTC
End: 2023-07-27 05:00 UTC

During the above window, our Networking team will be making changes to our core networking infrastructure to improve performance and scalability in the SFO3 region. This will be the second of the two maintenance activities performed by our team in the region on consecutive days.
Expected Impact:
These upgrades are designed and tested to be seamless and we do not expect any impact to customer traffic due to this maintenance. If an unexpected issue arises, affected Droplets and Droplet-based services may experience a temporary loss of private connectivity between VPCs. We will endeavour to keep any such impact to a minimum.
If you have any questions or concerns regarding this maintenance, please reach out to us by opening up a ticket on your account via https://cloudsupport.digitalocean.com/s/createticket.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>DigitalOcean Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Relations degraded performance]]></title>
        <id>https://status.notion.so/incidents/jxbwzkjpwvph</id>
        <link href="https://status.notion.so/incidents/jxbwzkjpwvph"/>
        <updated>2023-07-27T00:22:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jul 26, 17:22 PDT
Resolved - This incident is resolved for all customers.
Jul 26, 12:39 PDT
Investigating - We are currently investigating an issue with relations experiencing degraded performance]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Notion Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident with Pull Requests]]></title>
        <id>https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/mbvjmqbcb1xk</id>
        <link href="https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/mbvjmqbcb1xk"/>
        <updated>2023-07-26T15:04:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jul 26, 15:04 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Jul 26, 14:09 UTC
Update - For a small subset of customers some pull requests may not show up as mergeable. We are investigating the cause of the issue and will post an update as we have more information.
Jul 26, 13:50 UTC
Investigating - We are investigating reports of degraded performance for Pull Requests.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GitHub Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident: Email service is failing across Slack]]></title>
        <id>https://status.slack.com//2023-07/1633ff35517d83b8</id>
        <link href="https://status.slack.com//2023-07/1633ff35517d83b8"/>
        <updated>2023-07-26T06:46:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Issue summary:

On July 25th, 2023 from 3:00 PM PDT to 6:00 PM PDT we received reports of existing members unable to invite new members to workspaces. We traced the cause of issue to a recent code change which prevented emails from being sent. This also impacted logins, workspace creation and potentially other email-based processes. We’ve reverted this change, and the issue was resolved for all customers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Slack System Status</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SFO3 Network Maintenance]]></title>
        <id>https://status.digitalocean.com/incidents/d750rzt8dtgw</id>
        <link href="https://status.digitalocean.com/incidents/d750rzt8dtgw"/>
        <updated>2023-07-26T03:45:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jul 26, 03:45 UTC
Completed - The scheduled maintenance has been completed.
Jul 26, 01:00 UTC
In progress - Scheduled maintenance is currently in progress. We will provide updates as necessary.
Jul 25, 23:09 UTC
Scheduled - Start: 2023-07-26 01:00 UTC
End: 2023-07-26 05:00 UTC
During the above window, our Networking team will be making changes to our core networking infrastructure to improve performance and scalability in the SFO3 region. This maintenance will occur in two parts on consecutive days and we will send another maintenance notice for the second phase. 
Expected Impact:
These upgrades are designed and tested to be seamless and we do not expect any impact to customer traffic due to this maintenance. If an unexpected issue arises, affected Droplets and Droplet-based services may experience a temporary loss of private connectivity between VPCs. We will endeavor to keep any such impact to a minimum.
If you have any questions or concerns regarding this maintenance, please reach out to us by opening up a ticket on your account via https://cloudsupport.digitalocean.com/s/createticket.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>DigitalOcean Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Investigating reports of degraded performance.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/98fs1552d2nw</id>
        <link href="https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/98fs1552d2nw"/>
        <updated>2023-07-25T22:43:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jul 25, 22:43 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Jul 25, 22:33 UTC
Update - We found an issue that impacts a small subset of customers Jul 25, 22:33 UTC
Investigating - We are currently investigating this issue.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GitHub Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[500 Error on PUT Pricing Settings API]]></title>
        <id>https://airbnbapi.statuspage.io/incidents/ysvh24l8l9w1</id>
        <link href="https://airbnbapi.statuspage.io/incidents/ysvh24l8l9w1"/>
        <updated>2023-07-25T20:03:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jul 25, 13:03 PDT
Resolved - We resolved the incident. Please retry any request that failed during the incident, and don't hesitate to contact us if you need support.
Jul 25, 11:50 PDT
Monitoring - We have deployed a fix for this issue around 11:00 AM (PDT), and are monitoring the results.
Jul 25, 09:49 PDT
Investigating - We are actively investigating an increased number of 500 errors on the PUT Pricing Settings endpoint. These errors started today (July 25, 2023) around 05:00 AM (PDT). Our engineering teams are working to get everything up and running again, and we will update you with the latest information as soon as possible.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Airbnb API Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[500 Error Across Multiple Endpoints and Support Tools]]></title>
        <id>https://airbnbapi.statuspage.io/incidents/qj19z52zmnqj</id>
        <link href="https://airbnbapi.statuspage.io/incidents/qj19z52zmnqj"/>
        <updated>2023-07-24T22:37:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jul 24, 15:37 PDT
Resolved - We resolved the incident around 03:00 PM (PDT). Please retry any request that failed during the incident, and don't hesitate to contact us if you need support.
Jul 24, 14:16 PDT
Investigating - We are actively investigating an increased number of 500 errors across multiple endpoints, as well as timeout errors on the Partner Portal. These errors started today (July 24, 2023) around 02:00 PM PDT. Our engineering teams are working to get everything up and running again, and we will update you with the latest information as soon as possible.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Airbnb API Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident: Option to unarchive private channels is missing]]></title>
        <id>https://status.slack.com//2023-07/87cc7f492c7c074a</id>
        <link href="https://status.slack.com//2023-07/87cc7f492c7c074a"/>
        <updated>2023-07-24T22:19:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Issue Summary:

From 2:46 PM PDT to 6:44 PM PDT on July 21, 2023, some users were unable to unarchive channels to which they belonged.

We determined that a recent code change caused this issue. We reverted the code change and the issue was resolved.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Slack System Status</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident: Thread search results may be returning as blank for users.]]></title>
        <id>https://status.slack.com//2023-07/6f8189e691513b85</id>
        <link href="https://status.slack.com//2023-07/6f8189e691513b85"/>
        <updated>2023-07-24T18:30:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Users should no longer be experiencing any trouble searching threads. Apologies for the trouble today and thank you for your patience.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Slack System Status</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident: Users may be experiencing issues loading threads and sending messages.]]></title>
        <id>https://status.slack.com//2023-07/fd848c4da89c73cd</id>
        <link href="https://status.slack.com//2023-07/fd848c4da89c73cd"/>
        <updated>2023-07-24T18:06:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Users should no longer be experiencing any trouble loading threads or sending messages. Apologies for the trouble today and thank you for your patience.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Slack System Status</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Delayed scenario executions in the EU1 zone]]></title>
        <id>https://status.make.com/incidents/b17vq1m1ztj4</id>
        <link href="https://status.make.com/incidents/b17vq1m1ztj4"/>
        <updated>2023-07-23T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jul 23, 16:00 CEST
Resolved - Executions of scheduled scenarios in the EU1 zone are delayed.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Make Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident: Some user unable to load profiles]]></title>
        <id>https://status.slack.com//2023-07/ca6b134d9fd2d5a4</id>
        <link href="https://status.slack.com//2023-07/ca6b134d9fd2d5a4"/>
        <updated>2023-07-21T16:12:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’ve identified the cause of this issue. Any users encountering a REB9FC2A4F43 error can reload Slack (Command/Ctrl + Shift + R) in order to resolve this error. Thank you for your patience while we sorted out this issue.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Slack System Status</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident with Actions, API Requests, Git Operations, Packages, Pages and Pull Requests]]></title>
        <id>https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/6503rcn8s34s</id>
        <link href="https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/6503rcn8s34s"/>
        <updated>2023-07-21T14:01:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jul 21, 14:01 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Jul 21, 14:01 UTC
Update - Actions is operating normally.
Jul 21, 14:01 UTC
Update - Packages is operating normally.
Jul 21, 14:01 UTC
Update - API Requests is operating normally.
Jul 21, 14:01 UTC
Update - Git Operations is operating normally.
Jul 21, 14:01 UTC
Update - Pages is operating normally.
Jul 21, 14:00 UTC
Update - Networking issues are fully mitigated and service operation is restored. We will continue to work on follow ups internally but all services are operating normally.
Jul 21, 13:45 UTC
Update - We have mitigated the network power issue and are watching services recover. We will continue to monitor recovery and return status to green when the issue is fully mitigated.
Jul 21, 13:36 UTC
Update - API Requests is experiencing degraded performance. We are continuing to investigate.
Jul 21, 13:34 UTC
Update - We are experiencing a power failure at a datacenter related to our networking infrastructure that is impacting a subset of customers using our services. We are working on mitigating the issue.
Jul 21, 13:27 UTC
Update - Pull Requests is experiencing degraded performance. We are still investigating and will provide an update when we have one.
Jul 21, 13:22 UTC
Update - Pages is experiencing degraded performance. We are still investigating and will provide an update when we have one.
Jul 21, 13:21 UTC
Update - Packages is experiencing degraded performance. We are still investigating and will provide an update when we have one.
Jul 21, 13:15 UTC
Update - Actions is experiencing degraded performance. We are continuing to investigate.
Jul 21, 13:12 UTC
Investigating - We are investigating reports of degraded performance for Git Operations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GitHub Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Improvements of our Invoicing app]]></title>
        <id>270079</id>
        <link href="https://changelog.bookingsync.com/improvements-of-our-invoicing-app-270079"/>
        <updated>2023-07-21T11:15:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Improvement
  
We’re happy to announce that we just upgraded our Invoicing app with several improvements. 
Here are the highlights of what you can expect from the latest update:
Better User Experience
We’ve improved the app to make it more intuitive and user-friendly, with a smoother navigation flow.
Enhanced Stability
Our developers have put in significant effort to ensure the app’s stability and avoid unexpected crashes or performance hiccups.
Improved Search Function
Finding invoices and relevant information is now quicker and more precise.
Cleaner Interface
We understand the importance of a clutter-free interface. The app now flaunts a cleaner and more modern look that ensures a visually appealing invoicing experience.
As always, our customer support team is here to assist you should you have any questions or encounter any issues.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yannick, Customer Care Team Leader - Pro Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Some users prevented from accessing Notion due to change in request cookie consent]]></title>
        <id>https://status.notion.so/incidents/ps6b5r9s5sfk</id>
        <link href="https://status.notion.so/incidents/ps6b5r9s5sfk"/>
        <updated>2023-07-20T23:05:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jul 20, 16:05 PDT
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Jul 20, 15:30 PDT
Monitoring - We published a fix and validating the problem is fixed
Jul 20, 14:46 PDT
Identified - A change to request cookie consent is preventing users from accessing Notion. We have identified the issue and are working on a fix.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Notion Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spaces directories creation]]></title>
        <id>https://status.digitalocean.com/incidents/hwy11pmr6hgl</id>
        <link href="https://status.digitalocean.com/incidents/hwy11pmr6hgl"/>
        <updated>2023-07-20T22:31:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jul 20, 22:31 UTC
Resolved - As of 21:52 UTC, our Engineering team has confirmed the full resolution of the issue impacting the creation of directories/folders/files in Spaces buckets via the Cloud Control Panel. 
If you continue to experience problems, please open a ticket with our Support team. Thank you for your patience and we apologize for the inconvenience.
Jul 20, 22:05 UTC
Monitoring - As of 21:32 UTC, our Engineering team has implemented a fix for the issue impacting the creation of directories/folders/files in Spaces buckets in the Cloud Control Panel.
We're now monitoring the situation closely. We will post an update as soon as the issue is fully resolved.
Jul 20, 21:39 UTC
Update - Our Engineering team is investigating an issue with creating directories/folders/files in Spaces buckets using the Cloud Control Panel.
During this time, users should still be able to create the Spaces Bucket using Control Panel and API.
We will share an update as soon as possible.
Jul 20, 21:38 UTC
Investigating - Our Engineering team is investigating an issue with creating directories/folders/files in Spaces buckets using the Cloud Control Panel.
During this time, users should still be able to create the Spaces Bucket using Control Panel and API.
We will share an update as soon as possible.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>DigitalOcean Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Users cannot access any exported files from pages or workspaces]]></title>
        <id>https://status.notion.so/incidents/g2ywgyryp910</id>
        <link href="https://status.notion.so/incidents/g2ywgyryp910"/>
        <updated>2023-07-20T22:07:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jul 20, 15:07 PDT
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Jul 20, 14:57 PDT
Investigating - Users are unable to export workspace and page files. We are currently investigating the issue]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Notion Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident with Git Operations and Pull Requests]]></title>
        <id>https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/shbq71s0g00z</id>
        <link href="https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/shbq71s0g00z"/>
        <updated>2023-07-18T16:44:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jul 18, 16:44 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Jul 18, 16:43 UTC
Update - Pull Requests is operating normally.
Jul 18, 16:34 UTC
Update - We have mitigated the issue causing slow git operations for some customers and operations should now be performing normally.
Jul 18, 16:05 UTC
Update - Some customers may be experiencing slow git operations. We have identified the cause of the issue and are working on a mitigation.
Jul 18, 15:51 UTC
Update - Pull Requests is experiencing degraded performance. We are still investigating and will provide an update when we have one.
Jul 18, 15:44 UTC
Investigating - We are investigating reports of degraded performance for Git Operations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GitHub Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>