<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2023-04-08T00:19:27.843Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2023-04-08T00:19:27.843Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SMS Delivery Delays to Digicel Network in Papua New Guinea]]></title>
        <id>https://status.twilio.com/incidents/sp4kw0fxfcsz</id>
        <link href="https://status.twilio.com/incidents/sp4kw0fxfcsz"/>
        <updated>2023-04-07T23:50:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apr  7, 16:50 PDT
Update - We are experiencing SMS delivery delays when sending messages to Digicel network in Papua New Guinea. Our engineers are working with our carrier partner to resolve the issue. We will provide another update in 8 hours or as soon as more information becomes available.
Apr  7, 16:45 PDT
Update - We are experiencing SMS delivery delays when sending messages to Digicel network in Papua New Guinea. Our engineers are working with our carrier partner to resolve the issue. We will provide another update in 1 hour or as soon as more information becomes available.
Apr  7, 12:54 PDT
Update - We continue experiencing SMS delivery delays when sending messages to Digicel network in Papua New Guinea. Our engineers are working with our carrier partner to resolve the issue. We will provide another update in 4 hours or as soon as more information becomes available.
Apr  7, 11:15 PDT
Update - We continue experiencing SMS delivery delays when sending messages to Digicel network in Papua New Guinea. Our engineers are working with our carrier partner to resolve the issue. We will provide another update in 2 hours or as soon as more information becomes available.
Apr  7, 10:22 PDT
Investigating - We are experiencing SMS delivery delays when sending messages to Digicel network in Papua New Guinea. Our engineers are working with our carrier partner to resolve the issue. We will provide another update in 1 hour or as soon as more information becomes available.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Twilio Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SMS Delivery Delays to Glo Network in Nigeria]]></title>
        <id>https://status.twilio.com/incidents/258r6t65q1h4</id>
        <link href="https://status.twilio.com/incidents/258r6t65q1h4"/>
        <updated>2023-04-07T17:35:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apr  7, 10:35 PDT
Resolved - We are no longer experiencing SMS delivery delays when sending messages to Glo Network in Nigeria. This incident has been resolved.
Apr  7, 07:52 PDT
Update - We continue observing recovery in SMS delivery delays when sending messages to Glo Network in Nigeria. We will continue monitoring the service to ensure a full recovery. We will provide another update in 2 hours or as soon as more information becomes available.
Apr  7, 05:49 PDT
Monitoring - We are observing recovery in SMS delivery delays when sending messages to Glo Network in Nigeria. We will continue monitoring the service to ensure a full recovery. We will provide another update in 2 hours or as soon as more information becomes available.
Apr  7, 02:00 PDT
Update - We are still experiencing SMS delivery delays when sending messages to Glo Network in Nigeria. Our engineers are working with our carrier partner to resolve the issue. We will provide another update in 4 hours or as soon as more information becomes available.
Apr  7, 00:12 PDT
Update - We are still experiencing SMS delivery delays when sending messages to Glo Network in Nigeria. Our engineers are working with our carrier partner to resolve the issue. We will provide another update in 2 hours or as soon as more information becomes available.
Apr  6, 23:17 PDT
Investigating - We are experiencing SMS delivery delays when sending messages to Glo Network in Nigeria. Our engineers are working with our carrier partner to resolve the issue. We will provide another update in 1 hour or as soon as more information becomes available.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Twilio Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Twitter app is down]]></title>
        <id>https://status.make.com/incidents/kk37sgh6xp08</id>
        <link href="https://status.make.com/incidents/kk37sgh6xp08"/>
        <updated>2023-04-07T15:19:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apr  7, 17:19 CEST
Resolved - While we still await details from Twitter the only way how to create a connection at this moment is to have every user to create their own Twitter app at developer.twitter.com and use the apps API Key and API Key Secret to create a new connection in Make. We updated our documentation with details about how to obtain API Key and API Key Secret - https://www.make.com/en/help/apps/marketing/twitter#obtaining-api-key-and-api-key-secret-values-for-your-twitter-account
Apr  3, 23:56 CEST
Update - Twitter has suspended our app. We are continuing to investigate.
Apr  3, 21:29 CEST
Investigating - We are currently investigating this issue.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Make Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Issue impacting users in Korea]]></title>
        <id>https://status.notion.so/incidents/7txs6dn5qhmp</id>
        <link href="https://status.notion.so/incidents/7txs6dn5qhmp"/>
        <updated>2023-04-07T06:01:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apr  6, 23:01 PDT
Investigating - We are experiencing performance issues that may impact users in Korea. Users may experience significant delays when interacting with static content, like images and videos. Engineering is investigating the root cause of the degradation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Notion Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reminder - Important information regarding your website domain!]]></title>
        <id>262029</id>
        <link href="https://changelog.bookingsync.com/reminder-important-information-regarding-your-website-domain!-262029"/>
        <updated>2023-04-06T07:36:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Action required
  
Following our recent messages concerning the changes needed for your website domains, we would like to inform you that we have extended the support for the previous configuration until April 10 2023.
If you have not made the needeed changes yet, please consult our manual article here.
If you need assistance doing the changes, please contact our support team and we will be happy to assist you with the modifications. Please make sure to have access to your registrar (Gandi, OVH, Godaddy…) so we can assist you in performing this change.
Thanks,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yannick, Customer Care Team Leader - Pro Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[403 and 404 Errors Across Multiple Endpoints]]></title>
        <id>https://airbnbapi.statuspage.io/incidents/3v91lr711bpb</id>
        <link href="https://airbnbapi.statuspage.io/incidents/3v91lr711bpb"/>
        <updated>2023-04-05T09:01:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apr  5, 02:01 PDT
Resolved - We have identified and resolved an internal issue that resulted in 403 and 404 errors across multiple API endpoints. The incident was active between April 4th 20:00 PDT and April 5th 00:00 PDT. You can retry any failed requests at this point, and if you keep experiencing issues, please contact the API integration team for additional help.
We apologize for the inconvenience caused.
Apr  5, 00:51 PDT
Monitoring - A fix has been implemented and we are monitoring the results.
Apr  4, 23:15 PDT
Identified - The issue has been identified and a fix is being implemented.
Apr  4, 21:57 PDT
Investigating - We are currently investigating an issue related to 403 and 404 Errors across multiple endpoints. We'll post updates as we have more information.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Airbnb API Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[XML Migration Enforcement]]></title>
        <id>https://airbnbapi.statuspage.io/incidents/g18hcjbzzsfk</id>
        <link href="https://airbnbapi.statuspage.io/incidents/g18hcjbzzsfk"/>
        <updated>2023-04-05T08:46:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apr  5, 01:46 PDT
Completed - The scheduled maintenance has been completed.
Jul  5, 13:00 PDT
In progress - Scheduled maintenance is currently in progress. We will provide updates as necessary.
Jun 30, 10:55 PDT
Scheduled - As announced on July 5, 2021 we are deprecating our XML API connection.
XML listings can no longer be activated: this means that new XML listings will remain unlisted even if you set 
true
. The same is valid for existing listing that are deactivated (i.e. you will not be able to reactivate a XML listing if it gets unlisted).
More information about this enforcement here: https://developer.airbnb.com/docs/enforcement]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Airbnb API Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[500 Errors Across Multiple Endpoints]]></title>
        <id>https://airbnbapi.statuspage.io/incidents/flsz0qg3ysj6</id>
        <link href="https://airbnbapi.statuspage.io/incidents/flsz0qg3ysj6"/>
        <updated>2023-04-05T02:03:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apr  4, 19:03 PDT
Resolved - We have identified and resolved an internal issue that resulted in 500 errors across multiple API endpoints. The incident was active between 17:30 and 19:00 PDT on April 4th. You can retry any failed requests at this point, and if you keep experiencing issues, please contact the API integration team for additional help.
We apologize for the inconvenience.
Apr  4, 18:30 PDT
Monitoring - A fix has been implemented and we are monitoring the results.
Apr  4, 18:06 PDT
Investigating - We are currently investigating an issue related to 500 errors across multiple endpoints. We'll post updates as we have more information.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Airbnb API Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[500 Errors on Price Quote and Reservation Endpoints]]></title>
        <id>https://airbnbapi.statuspage.io/incidents/s6nclwbgvrb3</id>
        <link href="https://airbnbapi.statuspage.io/incidents/s6nclwbgvrb3"/>
        <updated>2023-04-04T05:24:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apr  3, 22:24 PDT
Resolved - We have identified and resolved an internal issue that resulted in 500 errors across multiple API endpoints, especially calendar operations, reservations and price quote endpoints. The incident was active between 17:00 and 20:10 PDT on April 3rd. You can retry any failed requests at this point, and if you keep experiencing issues, please contact the API integration team for additional help.
We apologize for the inconvenience.
Apr  3, 21:58 PDT
Monitoring - A fix has been implemented and we are monitoring the results.
Apr  3, 20:25 PDT
Identified - The issue has been identified and we are working on a fix.
Apr  3, 17:58 PDT
Update - The issue is now impacting more endpoints including calendar operations and rate plan, we'll post updates as we have more information.
Apr  3, 17:45 PDT
Investigating - We are currently investigating an issue related to 500 errors on price quote API and reservation APIs. We'll post updates as we have more information.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Airbnb API Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TS-2023-004]]></title>
        <id>https://tailscale.com/security-bulletins/#ts-2023-004/</id>
        <link href="https://tailscale.com/security-bulletins/#ts-2023-004/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-04T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Description: An issue in the Tailscale coordination server allowed tailnets created by GitHub organizations which were subsequently renamed to be associated with a new GitHub organization with the previous name.
What happened?
Tailscale mapped tailnets created by GitHub organizations to their organization name, rather than to their organization ID. This meant that if a GitHub organization was renamed, and the previous name taken over by a new GitHub organization, the existing tailnet would be tied to the new GitHub organization instead of the original one.
Who is affected?
Up to 1,305 tailnets created by GitHub organizations may have been affected, if those GitHub organizations were renamed between 2021-06-18 and 2023-03-30 and fully relinquished the old GitHub organization name. Additiona…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Security Bulletins on Tailscale</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident with Git Operations]]></title>
        <id>https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/5nlnzt80fk7g</id>
        <link href="https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/5nlnzt80fk7g"/>
        <updated>2023-04-03T22:41:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apr  3, 22:41 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Apr  3, 22:17 UTC
Update - We have mitigated the intermittent errors for Git requests and are continuing to monitor the system
Apr  3, 21:52 UTC
Update - We are currently working to mitigate intermittent errors for Git requests
Apr  3, 21:32 UTC
Update - We are currently investigating intermittent errors for Git requests
Apr  3, 20:57 UTC
Investigating - We are investigating reports of degraded performance for Git Operations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GitHub Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident: Some users have trouble receiving 2FA code via SMS]]></title>
        <id>https://status.slack.com//2023-04/fdaa42009b1486bc</id>
        <link href="https://status.slack.com//2023-04/fdaa42009b1486bc"/>
        <updated>2023-04-03T21:29:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Issue summary: 

On April 3rd, 2023 from 11:00 AM PDT until 11:45 AM PDT, users on certain cellular service networks had issues receiving SMS texts for two-factor authentication (2FA). 


Upon investigation, this was traced to one unverified toll free number, which prevented 2FA codes from being approved for delivery. That number was removed from our 2FA pool, and services have resumed as usual. We are reviewing our process and alerting around outgoing phone number verification to ensure the issue doesn't happen again.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Slack System Status</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident with Actions and Pages]]></title>
        <id>https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/0d1bcqt29hm2</id>
        <link href="https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/0d1bcqt29hm2"/>
        <updated>2023-04-03T19:00:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apr  3, 19:00 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Apr  3, 19:00 UTC
Update - Actions is operating normally.
Apr  3, 18:43 UTC
Update - We are investigating issues with workflow run failures when downloading actions.
Apr  3, 18:42 UTC
Update - Pages is experiencing degraded performance. We are still investigating and will provide an update when we have one.
Apr  3, 18:35 UTC
Investigating - We are investigating reports of degraded performance for Actions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GitHub Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Issues loading Devices page]]></title>
        <id>https://status.rippling.com/incidents/n1h5yd5mmfc9</id>
        <link href="https://status.rippling.com/incidents/n1h5yd5mmfc9"/>
        <updated>2023-04-03T17:46:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apr  3, 17:46 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Apr  3, 16:57 UTC
Identified - The issue has been identified and a fix is being implemented.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rippling Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident: Some users are unable to sign-in using the Continue with Google feature on the Android and iOS app]]></title>
        <id>https://status.slack.com//2023-04/7c6ac904c99e5234</id>
        <link href="https://status.slack.com//2023-04/7c6ac904c99e5234"/>
        <updated>2023-04-02T03:27:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Issue summary: 

From March 31st, 2023 at 7:18 PM PDT to April 1st, 2023 at 11:30 AM PDT, some customers may not have been able to sign in to Slack with the 'Continue with Google' feature. 


During a routine cleanup process, we made some changes to the project behind the 'Continue with Google' feature. This change inadvertently prevented the Slack mobile apps from confirming the validity of customer Google accounts during login. 


We reverted this change, restoring normal login behaviour for all affected customers, and we're working to ensure it does not happen again. We apologize for any disruption to your work.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Slack System Status</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RESOLVED: We're investigating reports of an issue with Google Workspace Support. We will provide more information shortly.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.google.com/appsstatus/dashboard/incidents/79iVdMKGvjfeHpdG2J6L</id>
        <link href="https://www.google.com/appsstatus/dashboard/incidents/79iVdMKGvjfeHpdG2J6L"/>
        <updated>2023-03-31T21:53:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p> Incident began at <strong>2023-03-24 08:10</strong> and ended at <strong>2023-03-24 11:38</strong> <span>(times are in <strong>Coordinated Universal Time (UTC)</strong>).</span></p><div class="cBIRi14aVDP__status-update-text"><h1>Incident Report</h1>
<h2>Summary</h2>
<p>On 24 March 2023, Google Workspace Support Chat experienced issues displaying some support language options for 3 hours, 28 minutes. As a result, some customers may have been unable to choose their preferred support language when starting a chat session.</p>
<h2>Root Cause</h2>
<p>When Google Workspace customers choose chat support, the Support UI displays a list of languages the customer may choose from before the chat session begins.</p>
<p>On 24 March 2023 at 01:10 US/Pacific, engineers rolled out an update for the Support UI that migrated the language select dropdown to a new select component. This update introduced an issue where the rendering of the select component would cut off some language options when the number of available languages exceeded the select component’s container boundaries.</p>
<h2>Remediation and Prevention</h2>
<p>Google engineers were alerted to the issue via an internal report on 24 March 2023 at 03:27 US/Pacific and immediately started an investigation. Engineers identified the Support UI change as the cause of the issue at 04:13 US/Pacific and started a rollback of the update at 04:16 US/Pacific. The rollback finished at 04:38 US/Pacific, resolving the issue.</p>
<p>Google is committed to preventing a repeat of this issue in the future and is completing the following actions:</p>
<ul>
<li>Update automated testing for Support UI releases to better detect these types of potential UI issues.</li>
</ul>
<h2>Detailed Description of Impact</h2>
<p>On 24 March 2023 from 01:10 to 04:38 US/Pacific, Google Workspace Support Chat experienced issues displaying some support language options.</p>
<p>Normally, all languages the customer is entitled to use should appear in the list of languages whether available or not. For the duration of this issue, Workspace support admins may have not seen their preferred language listed at all.</p>
</div><hr><p>Affected products: Google Workspace Support</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Workspace Status Dashboard Updates</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Degradation of database performance]]></title>
        <id>https://status.notion.so/incidents/1zx7mzp3m9qh</id>
        <link href="https://status.notion.so/incidents/1zx7mzp3m9qh"/>
        <updated>2023-03-31T16:29:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mar 31, 09:29 PDT
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Mar 31, 08:55 PDT
Monitoring - A fix has been implemented and we are monitoring results.
Mar 31, 08:49 PDT
Update - We are continuing to investigate this issue.
Mar 31, 08:49 PDT
Investigating - We are currently investigating this issue.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Notion Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident with Git Operations, Issues and Pull Requests]]></title>
        <id>https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/rmc0cpn9sn8w</id>
        <link href="https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/rmc0cpn9sn8w"/>
        <updated>2023-03-31T02:08:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mar 31, 02:08 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Mar 31, 01:39 UTC
Update - We have identified the issue and are deploying a fix. We will update our status when the fix is fully deployed.
Mar 31, 01:18 UTC
Update - Issues and Pull Requests are experiencing degraded performance. We are continuing to investigate.
Mar 31, 01:16 UTC
Investigating - We are investigating reports of degraded performance for Git Operations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GitHub Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident: Some users may be unable to edit messages]]></title>
        <id>https://status.slack.com//2023-03/a207156392d94ca4</id>
        <link href="https://status.slack.com//2023-03/a207156392d94ca4"/>
        <updated>2023-03-30T19:14:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Issue summary:

On March 28th, 2023 from 2:40 PM to 3:43 PM PDT, some customers may have experienced difficulties editing messages in Slack. 


We identified that this issue was caused by a recent code change. We reverted the code to resolve the issue for all impacted customers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Slack System Status</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident with Actions, Codespaces and Pages]]></title>
        <id>https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/z3c6q056q332</id>
        <link href="https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/z3c6q056q332"/>
        <updated>2023-03-29T19:03:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mar 29, 19:03 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Mar 29, 18:18 UTC
Update - Codespaces is operating normally.
Mar 29, 18:13 UTC
Update - We are still working towards full recovery. Actions jobs still experience delays when being queued.
Mar 29, 18:10 UTC
Update - Pages is operating normally.
Mar 29, 17:41 UTC
Update - We are still working towards full recovery. Actions jobs still experience delays when being queued.
Mar 29, 17:29 UTC
Update - Codespaces is experiencing degraded performance. We are continuing to investigate.
Mar 29, 16:56 UTC
Update - Actions workflows have started running again. We're continuing to work towards full recovery.
Mar 29, 16:47 UTC
Update - Actions is now experiencing degraded performance. We are still investigating and will provide an update when we have one.
Mar 29, 16:22 UTC
Update - We are seeing signs of recovery for Actions and continue to monitor closely. We will continue to post updates about progress as soon as we have them.
Mar 29, 15:42 UTC
Update - We continue to work on mitigating the problems with Actions and Pages with high urgency. We will continue to post updates about our progress.
Mar 29, 15:29 UTC
Update - Pages is experiencing degraded performance. We are continuing to investigate.
Mar 29, 14:56 UTC
Update - We are still investigating the cause of Actions degradation, we will provide an update when we have one.
Mar 29, 14:43 UTC
Update - Actions is now experiencing degraded availability. We are still investigating and will provide an update when we have one.
Mar 29, 14:21 UTC
Investigating - We are investigating reports of degraded performance for Actions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GitHub Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident with Actions]]></title>
        <id>https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/chnz8v3m9dqm</id>
        <link href="https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/chnz8v3m9dqm"/>
        <updated>2023-03-28T17:07:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mar 28, 17:07 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Mar 28, 16:59 UTC
Update - We've applied a mitigation to fix the issues with queuing and running Actions jobs. We are seeing improvements in telemetry and are monitoring for full recovery.
Mar 28, 16:28 UTC
Update - The team continues to investigate issues with some Actions jobs being queued for a long time and a percentage of jobs failing. We will continue to keep users updated on progress towards mitigation.
Mar 28, 15:45 UTC
Investigating - We are investigating reports of degraded performance for Actions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GitHub Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reservation webhooks with $0 price]]></title>
        <id>https://airbnbapi.statuspage.io/incidents/k6xc09dvz8r5</id>
        <link href="https://airbnbapi.statuspage.io/incidents/k6xc09dvz8r5"/>
        <updated>2023-03-27T22:42:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mar 27, 15:42 PDT
Resolved - We have identified and resolved an internal issue that resulted in reservation webhook notifications being sent with $0 price. The incident was active between 13:40 and 14:20 PDT. Reservations payments were processed correctly, but nightly prices and fees appeared as $0 within the webhooks. Please use the GET Reservations API to retrieve the correct reservations prices. Alternatively, please contact the API Integrations team for additional help.
Apologies for the inconvenience.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Airbnb API Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[High latency]]></title>
        <id>https://status.notion.so/incidents/5wgctrsfk12z</id>
        <link href="https://status.notion.so/incidents/5wgctrsfk12z"/>
        <updated>2023-03-27T15:53:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mar 27, 08:53 PDT
Resolved - We have confirmed this issue has been resolved, and Notion should load normally for all users.
Mar 27, 08:42 PDT
Monitoring - We have implemented a fix that has restored normal loading times for most users, and are continuing to monitor.
Mar 27, 07:40 PDT
Investigating - Notion is loading slowly or not at all for some users. We are investigating.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Notion Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident with Actions, API Requests, Codespaces, Git Operations, Issues, Pages and Pull Requests]]></title>
        <id>https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/52z0j6phhnjs</id>
        <link href="https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/52z0j6phhnjs"/>
        <updated>2023-03-27T13:29:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mar 27, 13:29 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Mar 27, 13:27 UTC
Update - We’ve identified an infrastructure change that has been rolled back and we are monitoring recovery.
Mar 27, 13:22 UTC
Update - Codespaces, Git Operations, Issues and Pull Requests are now experiencing degraded performance. We are still investigating and will provide an update when we have one.
Mar 27, 13:08 UTC
Update - We are investigating reports of issues with service(s): multiple services. We will continue to keep users updated on progress towards mitigation.
Mar 27, 12:56 UTC
Update - Issues and Pull Requests are now experiencing degraded availability. We are continuing to investigate.
Mar 27, 12:51 UTC
Update - Pages is experiencing degraded performance. We are continuing to investigate.
Mar 27, 12:50 UTC
Update - Codespaces is now experiencing degraded availability. We are continuing to investigate.
Mar 27, 12:50 UTC
Update - Git Operations is now experiencing degraded availability. We are still investigating and will provide an update when we have one.
Mar 27, 12:35 UTC
Update - Codespaces is experiencing degraded performance. We are continuing to investigate.
Mar 27, 12:33 UTC
Update - API Requests is experiencing degraded performance. We are still investigating and will provide an update when we have one.
Mar 27, 12:26 UTC
Update - Actions is experiencing degraded performance. We are still investigating and will provide an update when we have one.
Mar 27, 12:25 UTC
Update - Issues and Pull Requests are experiencing degraded performance. We are still investigating and will provide an update when we have one.
Mar 27, 12:25 UTC
Investigating - We are investigating reports of degraded performance for Git Operations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GitHub Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident with Packages]]></title>
        <id>https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/ngfhz9jts91q</id>
        <link href="https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/ngfhz9jts91q"/>
        <updated>2023-03-26T22:27:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mar 26, 22:27 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Mar 26, 22:13 UTC
Investigating - We are investigating reports of degraded performance for Packages.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GitHub Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident: Some users may experience issues with using the back/forward in history functionality]]></title>
        <id>https://status.slack.com//2023-03/c91b6fbe5d4397cd</id>
        <link href="https://status.slack.com//2023-03/c91b6fbe5d4397cd"/>
        <updated>2023-03-24T23:33:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The issue with navigation of back/forward in history functionality is now resolved for all users.


Please reload Slack (press Command/Control + Shift + R) and let us know if you are still running into any issues.


Thank you very much for your patience while we worked on getting this fix out the door.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Slack System Status</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident with Pages]]></title>
        <id>https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/x7njwb481j9b</id>
        <link href="https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/x7njwb481j9b"/>
        <updated>2023-03-24T21:10:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mar 24, 21:10 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Mar 24, 21:05 UTC
Update - We are aware of TLS problems related to an expired certificate in our CDN configuration. We are working to resolve this issue.
Mar 24, 20:49 UTC
Investigating - We are investigating reports of degraded performance for Pages.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GitHub Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Increased delay in scenarios executions for users on eu1.make.com since 10:00 CET]]></title>
        <id>https://status.make.com/incidents/0lcg8pdkx5yp</id>
        <link href="https://status.make.com/incidents/0lcg8pdkx5yp"/>
        <updated>2023-03-24T11:04:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mar 24, 12:04 CET
Resolved - The issue was resolved.
Mar 24, 10:42 CET
Monitoring - Scenario processing is stable now. We are closely monitoring the situation.
Mar 24, 10:29 CET
Investigating - We are currently investigating this issue.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Make Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident with Actions]]></title>
        <id>https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/rcjsf188vx7q</id>
        <link href="https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/rcjsf188vx7q"/>
        <updated>2023-03-24T08:42:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mar 24, 08:42 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Mar 24, 08:27 UTC
Investigating - We are investigating reports of degraded performance for Actions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GitHub Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident with Codespaces]]></title>
        <id>https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/yc4d45cp0pxn</id>
        <link href="https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/yc4d45cp0pxn"/>
        <updated>2023-03-23T04:55:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mar 23, 04:55 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Mar 23, 04:51 UTC
Update - We have mitigated the issue and customers should have restored functionality to Codespaces. We are continue to monitor the issue for potential issues before resolving this
Mar 23, 04:08 UTC
Update - We are investigating issues with Codespaces in the Europe West geographic area. Some users may not be able to connect to their Codespaces at this time. We will update you on mitigation progress.
Mar 23, 03:51 UTC
Investigating - We are investigating reports of degraded performance for Codespaces.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GitHub Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident with Codespaces]]></title>
        <id>https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/rzqm3bfcn80x</id>
        <link href="https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/rzqm3bfcn80x"/>
        <updated>2023-03-22T22:41:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mar 22, 22:41 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Mar 22, 22:26 UTC
Update - We are continuing to investigate issues with Codespaces in the US West region.
Mar 22, 21:03 UTC
Update - Some customers are currently unable to resume Codespaces created in the US West region. We are working to restore Codespaces to full functionality for those customers.
Mar 22, 20:31 UTC
Update - We are investigating reports of degraded performance for Codespaces created in our US West 3 cluster.
Mar 22, 20:23 UTC
Investigating - We are investigating reports of degraded performance for Codespaces.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GitHub Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident: “Time when workflow started” variable is missing from Workflow Builder steps]]></title>
        <id>https://status.slack.com//2023-03/851ee18978dd79cc</id>
        <link href="https://status.slack.com//2023-03/851ee18978dd79cc"/>
        <updated>2023-03-22T20:49:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Issue summary:

On March 21, 2023 at 7:32 AM PDT to March 22, 2023 at 8:06 AM PDT, the "Time when workflow started" variable is missing from all steps of the Workflow Builder for new and existing workflows. If the variable was used to publish to a Google Sheet, the cell would be empty.


We discovered a bug that made date fields invisible without any errors displayed, though workflows were still running and had access to the value.


We have released a fix on March 22, 2023 at 8:06 AM PDT. Previously impacted workflows need to retrieve the timestamps from the workflow in the Workflow Builder. We appreciate your patience while we sorted this out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Slack System Status</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TS-2023-003]]></title>
        <id>https://tailscale.com/security-bulletins/#ts-2023-003/</id>
        <link href="https://tailscale.com/security-bulletins/#ts-2023-003/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-22T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Reference: CVE-2023-28436
Severity: Medium
CVSS vector string: CVSS:3.0/AV:A/AC:L/PR:H/UI:R/S:C/C:H/I:N/A:N
Description: A vulnerability identified in the implementation of Tailscale SSH in FreeBSD allowed commands to be run with a higher privilege group ID than that specified by Tailscale SSH access rules.
Affected platforms: FreeBSD
Patched Tailscale client versions: v1.38.2 or later
What happened?
A difference in the behavior of the FreeBSD setgroups system call from POSIX meant that the Tailscale client running on a FreeBSD-based operating system did not appropriately restrict groups on the host when using Tailscale SSH. When accessing a FreeBSD host over Tailscale SSH, the egid of the tailscaled process was used instead of that of the user specified in Tailscale SSH access rules.
Who is affected?
9 tailnets with 22 FreeBSD nodes running Tailscale SSH since Tailscale v1.34 (released on 2022-12-04) may have had Tailscale SSH sessions with a higher privilege group ID than that specified in Tailscale SSH access rules.
We have notified affected organizations where we have security contacts.
What is the impact?
Tailscale SSH commands may have been run with a higher privilege group ID than that specified in Tailscale SSH access rules if they met all of the following criteria:
The destination node was a FreeBSD device with Tailscale SSH enabled;
Tailscale SSH access rules permitted access for non-root users; and
A non-interactive SSH session was used.
What do I need to do?
If you are running Tailscale on FreeBSD, upgrade to v1.38.2 or later to remediate the issue. Admins of a tailnet can view FreeBSD nodes with unpatched versions in the admin console.
To update the local ports tree in advance of what’s available upstream, you can:
cd /usr/ports/security/tailscale
edit the Makefile to set PORTVERSION to 1.38.2
make makesum
make install
Tailscale SSH on other platforms is not affected.
Credits
We would like to thank Ryan Belgrave for reporting this issue.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Security Bulletins on Tailscale</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident with Codespaces]]></title>
        <id>https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/8095qt814fr4</id>
        <link href="https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/8095qt814fr4"/>
        <updated>2023-03-21T17:43:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mar 21, 17:43 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Mar 21, 17:22 UTC
Investigating - We are investigating reports of degraded performance for Codespaces.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GitHub Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident with API Requests, Git Operations, Issues and Pull Requests]]></title>
        <id>https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/z5ykrdm7ykwg</id>
        <link href="https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/z5ykrdm7ykwg"/>
        <updated>2023-03-20T17:01:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mar 20, 17:01 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Mar 20, 16:44 UTC
Update - We continue to investigate the cause of high latency across multiple GitHub services.
Mar 20, 16:02 UTC
Update - We are investigating reports of high latency in issues, pull requests, and git operations.
Mar 20, 15:56 UTC
Investigating - We are investigating reports of degraded performance for API Requests, Git Operations, Issues and Pull Requests.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GitHub Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Performance degradation]]></title>
        <id>https://status.notion.so/incidents/rk7qmfsdj1kb</id>
        <link href="https://status.notion.so/incidents/rk7qmfsdj1kb"/>
        <updated>2023-03-17T20:36:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mar 17, 13:36 PDT
Resolved - This issue has been resolved. Users should be able to successfully load Notion pages now.
Mar 17, 12:13 PDT
Update - We are continuing to work on mitigation and resolution for slow loading times.
Mar 17, 10:52 PDT
Identified - Some users are experiencing slow load times. We have identified the root cause and are working on resolving it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Notion Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident with Actions, Packages and Pages]]></title>
        <id>https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/ybnn77s3lyf8</id>
        <link href="https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/ybnn77s3lyf8"/>
        <updated>2023-03-15T15:27:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mar 15, 15:27 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Mar 15, 15:21 UTC
Update - Packages is continuing to recover well. Error rates are back to normal and request latency continues to drop. Next update in 10 minutes.
Mar 15, 15:17 UTC
Update - Packages is now experiencing degraded performance. We are continuing to investigate.
Mar 15, 15:10 UTC
Update - Our mitigation for Packages is progressing well. We are adding capacity back and beginning to see 5xx error rates reduce. Next update in 10 minutes.
Mar 15, 14:52 UTC
Update - Actions is experiencing degraded performance. We are continuing to investigate.
Mar 15, 14:51 UTC
Update - Users of GitHub Package Registry (except Docker and Maven registries) will be experiencing timeout failures. This includes GitHub Actions, Packages API and Packages UI on GitHub.com.
Mar 15, 14:39 UTC
Update - We have identified the source of the issue with GitHub Packages and are working to mitigate the problem.
Mar 15, 14:22 UTC
Update - Pages is operating normally.
Mar 15, 14:20 UTC
Update - Packages is now experiencing degraded availability. We are continuing to investigate.
Mar 15, 14:09 UTC
Update - Packages is experiencing degraded performance. We are continuing to investigate.
Mar 15, 14:07 UTC
Investigating - We are investigating reports of degraded performance for Pages.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GitHub Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Follow up - Important information regarding your website domain!]]></title>
        <id>260094</id>
        <link href="https://changelog.bookingsync.com/follow-up-important-information-regarding-your-website-domain!-260094"/>
        <updated>2023-03-15T08:17:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Action required
  
As we are doing some improvements on our infrastructure, we have some modifications that are necessary on the way some of your website domains are configured.
To ensure that you have the best configuration, we invite you to review the settings on your registrar to make sure that you have the correct configuration.
What is needed?
Your main domain should be under a **Cname **record with **www **and point to dns1.happystay.com. (the "dot" at the end may be required depending on your domain).
(example for your main domain: www.yourwebsite.com)
You can also add an addon domain without using www if you want your website to be reachable this way, (example: yourwebsite.com).
In order to do that, you can configure an A record (Aname) in your DNS zone pointing to one of the following IP addresses:
13.248.140.34


76.223.14.214


These are the new addresses that are replacing the previous address: (52.210.201.133)
Important note, If you are using 52.210.201.133, you need to change to one of the new IP address as we will not be able to keep supporting this one on March 29th 2023.
If you need assistance doing this change, please contact our support team and we will be happy to assist you with the modifications. Please make sure to have access to your registrar (Gandi, OVH, Godaddy…) so we can assist you in performing this change. 
The details are also available on our manual.
Thanks,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yannick, Customer Care Team Leader - Pro Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident: Some users may experience issues accessing api.slack.com]]></title>
        <id>https://status.slack.com//2023-03/9011b8a984a74042</id>
        <link href="https://status.slack.com//2023-03/9011b8a984a74042"/>
        <updated>2023-03-14T16:57:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We appreciate your patience while we've continued to investigate this issue. Some customers may still be impacted by the SSL certificate changes, however we will closely monitor reports and provide further updates through customer support tickets with the impacted users. Please reach out to our team at feedback@slack.com for further assistance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Slack System Status</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident: Enterprise users see slowness or error messages when signing in on mobile]]></title>
        <id>https://status.slack.com//2023-03/1da534dc3612b14f</id>
        <link href="https://status.slack.com//2023-03/1da534dc3612b14f"/>
        <updated>2023-03-14T06:21:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Issue summary: 

On March 13th, 2023 from 2:00 PM to 5:00 PM PDT, some Enterprise Grid customers using the Slack for Intune mobile app may have experienced errors or latency when logging in to Slack.


We identified that this issue was caused by a conflict between Slack functionality and a Slack for Intune preference. We deployed a manual fix, resolving the issue for all impacted users.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Slack System Status</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Banking partner delay]]></title>
        <id>https://status.rippling.com/incidents/yhm54z3b1wqg</id>
        <link href="https://status.rippling.com/incidents/yhm54z3b1wqg"/>
        <updated>2023-03-13T06:18:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mar 13, 06:18 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Mar 13, 06:18 UTC
Update - We are continuing to work on a fix for this issue.
Mar 10, 23:13 UTC
Update - All payments with a check date of March 10th have been successfully submitted. Some have been completed, and others will complete between Saturday, March 11th and Monday, March 13th.
This morning, Rippling was assured by SVB that all payments would be processed today. However, when SVB fell into receivership with the FDIC, we immediately began working with JPMorgan Chase to find an alternative means to send funds to employees. 
As a result of the actions we took, all employees will receive their payments between today and Monday morning, depending on which bank they use. Rippling has extended our own capital to fund these pay…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rippling Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Notifications are not working]]></title>
        <id>https://status.notion.so/incidents/zyddfgt7nfmw</id>
        <link href="https://status.notion.so/incidents/zyddfgt7nfmw"/>
        <updated>2023-03-12T16:08:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mar 12, 09:08 PDT
Resolved - Engineering has implemented a fix. Notification issue has been resolved.
Mar 12, 09:07 PDT
Update - We are continuing to investigate this issue.
Mar 12, 08:07 PDT
Investigating - We are currently experiencing an issue with notifications. Engineering is investigating the root cause of this issue.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Notion Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Database upgrade]]></title>
        <id>https://status.notion.so/incidents/pxth0clm33h4</id>
        <link href="https://status.notion.so/incidents/pxth0clm33h4"/>
        <updated>2023-03-11T23:55:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mar 11, 15:55 PST
Completed - The scheduled maintenance has been completed.
Mar 11, 15:35 PST
In progress - Scheduled maintenance is currently in progress. We will provide updates as necessary.
Mar 11, 15:34 PST
Scheduled - We are currently undergoing scheduled maintenance. Notifications may be unavailable between 3:30 - 3:40pm Pacific time. Notifications received during that time will be sent when the maintenance is complete.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Notion Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Device actions are slow and the Rippling Admin account may temporarily be out of sync]]></title>
        <id>https://status.rippling.com/incidents/k4qyh9s92rw1</id>
        <link href="https://status.rippling.com/incidents/k4qyh9s92rw1"/>
        <updated>2023-03-10T23:50:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mar 10, 23:50 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Mar 10, 19:13 UTC
Update - A fix has been deployed, recovery efforts are underway.  ETA for resolution is today.
Mar  9, 23:05 UTC
Identified - The issue has been identified and a fix is being implemented.
Mar  9, 18:10 UTC
Investigating - We are currently investigating this issue.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rippling Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident: Some customers are seeing errors when attempting to connect Google Drive]]></title>
        <id>https://status.slack.com//2023-03/452b13772c8c8b7d</id>
        <link href="https://status.slack.com//2023-03/452b13772c8c8b7d"/>
        <updated>2023-03-10T20:12:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Issue summary:

On March 9, 2023 from 8:28 PM to March 10, 2023 8:40 AM PST, some users that were signed into multiple workspaces experienced a redirect issue when signing into the Google Drive app from Slack. 


After the sign-in button was clicked, the user was redirected to a different Slack workspace they were signed into, causing a 400 Bad Request response.


We made a code change to ensure the user was redirected to the proper workspace, fixing the authentication error and resolving the issue.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Slack System Status</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident: Service degradation in Slack]]></title>
        <id>https://status.slack.com//2023-03/dd0ae32c5786a66f</id>
        <link href="https://status.slack.com//2023-03/dd0ae32c5786a66f"/>
        <updated>2023-03-09T22:57:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Issue summary:

On March 9, 2023 from 9:07 AM to 10:06 AM PST, some users experienced trouble with various features in Slack, such as adding bookmarks to channels, using workflows, connecting to Slack, or sending Slack Connect invites.


We discovered the service degradation was prompted by a load test that ran at a higher rate than intended, causing database outages to occur. To remediate the issue, we scaled back the load test to the normal rate which resolved the problem for all impacted users.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Slack System Status</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Issues loading Rippling]]></title>
        <id>https://status.rippling.com/incidents/grbrkfxrz4m1</id>
        <link href="https://status.rippling.com/incidents/grbrkfxrz4m1"/>
        <updated>2023-03-09T21:48:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mar  9, 21:48 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Mar  9, 19:40 UTC
Update - We are continuing to monitor for any further issues.
Mar  9, 19:22 UTC
Monitoring - We've identified a root cause for the issue and have resolved page loading issues. We are continuing to monitor for any further issues.
Mar  9, 18:40 UTC
Investigating - We are currently investigating this issue.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rippling Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Devices app is sending an erroneous email prompting employees to enter their password]]></title>
        <id>https://status.rippling.com/incidents/y9wybwpbgtfd</id>
        <link href="https://status.rippling.com/incidents/y9wybwpbgtfd"/>
        <updated>2023-03-09T17:29:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mar  9, 17:29 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Mar  9, 04:47 UTC
Monitoring - A fix has been implemented and we are monitoring the results.
Mar  9, 04:47 UTC
Identified - The issue has been identified and a fix is being implemented.
Mar  8, 23:23 UTC
Investigating - We are currently investigating this issue.  The email subject is "Action required: Enter your device password in the Rippling Desktop App".  Employees can ignore this email for the time being.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rippling Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident with Webhooks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/dkm3dxjzynxh</id>
        <link href="https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/dkm3dxjzynxh"/>
        <updated>2023-03-09T16:36:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mar  9, 16:36 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Mar  9, 16:07 UTC
Update - We have found the cause of degraded Webhooks performance and are seeing signs of recovery.
Mar  9, 15:08 UTC
Update - We are investigating reports of issues with Webhooks. We will continue to keep users updated on progress towards mitigation.
Mar  9, 14:34 UTC
Investigating - We are investigating reports of degraded performance for Webhooks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GitHub Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Important information regarding your website domain!]]></title>
        <id>259586</id>
        <link href="https://changelog.bookingsync.com/important-information-regarding-your-website-domain!-259586"/>
        <updated>2023-03-09T12:25:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Communications
  
We will be doing some improvements on our website infrastructure which may temporarily affect your websites.
The maintenance will take place on tuesday March 14, 2023 at 06:00am CET and will have a duration of 3 hours max.
What will be the impact?
· Websites may not be unreachable for up to 10 minutes at maintenance time.
· SSL may be unavailable from the beginning of the maintenance for up to 3 hours (website will still be reachable without https)
Do I need to do anything?
This maintenance will impact the DNS zone we are using to link your website to our infrastructure, therefore some changes will be required in the 2 weeks following this update if you are using your own domain name with A records.
We will send a second communication with the information and update our manual to help you with this transition.
Of course our support team will be there to assist you.
Thank you for your comprehension,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yannick, Customer Care Team Leader - Pro Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>