<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2023-03-20T00:24:06.297Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2023-03-20T00:24:06.297Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Performance degradation]]></title>
        <id>https://status.notion.so/incidents/rk7qmfsdj1kb</id>
        <link href="https://status.notion.so/incidents/rk7qmfsdj1kb"/>
        <updated>2023-03-17T20:36:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mar 17, 13:36 PDT
Resolved - This issue has been resolved. Users should be able to successfully load Notion pages now.
Mar 17, 12:13 PDT
Update - We are continuing to work on mitigation and resolution for slow loading times.
Mar 17, 10:52 PDT
Identified - Some users are experiencing slow load times. We have identified the root cause and are working on resolving it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Notion Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident with Actions, Packages and Pages]]></title>
        <id>https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/ybnn77s3lyf8</id>
        <link href="https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/ybnn77s3lyf8"/>
        <updated>2023-03-15T15:27:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mar 15, 15:27 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Mar 15, 15:21 UTC
Update - Packages is continuing to recover well. Error rates are back to normal and request latency continues to drop. Next update in 10 minutes.
Mar 15, 15:17 UTC
Update - Packages is now experiencing degraded performance. We are continuing to investigate.
Mar 15, 15:10 UTC
Update - Our mitigation for Packages is progressing well. We are adding capacity back and beginning to see 5xx error rates reduce. Next update in 10 minutes.
Mar 15, 14:52 UTC
Update - Actions is experiencing degraded performance. We are continuing to investigate.
Mar 15, 14:51 UTC
Update - Users of GitHub Package Registry (except Docker and Maven registries) will be experiencing timeout failures. This includes GitHub Actions, Packages API and Packages UI on GitHub.com.
Mar 15, 14:39 UTC
Update - We have identified the source of the issue with GitHub Packages and are working to mitigate the problem.
Mar 15, 14:22 UTC
Update - Pages is operating normally.
Mar 15, 14:20 UTC
Update - Packages is now experiencing degraded availability. We are continuing to investigate.
Mar 15, 14:09 UTC
Update - Packages is experiencing degraded performance. We are continuing to investigate.
Mar 15, 14:07 UTC
Investigating - We are investigating reports of degraded performance for Pages.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GitHub Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Follow up - Important information regarding your website domain!]]></title>
        <id>260094</id>
        <link href="https://changelog.bookingsync.com/follow-up-important-information-regarding-your-website-domain!-260094"/>
        <updated>2023-03-15T08:17:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Action required
  
As we are doing some improvements on our infrastructure, we have some modifications that are necessary on the way some of your website domains are configured.
To ensure that you have the best configuration, we invite you to review the settings on your registrar to make sure that you have the correct configuration.
What is needed?
Your main domain should be under a **Cname **record with **www **and point to dns1.happystay.com. (the "dot" at the end may be required depending on your domain).
(example for your main domain: www.yourwebsite.com)
You can also add an addon domain without using www if you want your website to be reachable this way, (example: yourwebsite.com).
In order to do that, you can configure an A record (Aname) in your DNS zone pointing to one of the following IP addresses:
13.248.140.34


76.223.14.214


These are the new addresses that are replacing the previous address: (52.210.201.133)
Important note, If you are using 52.210.201.133, you need to change to one of the new IP address as we will not be able to keep supporting this one on March 29th 2023.
If you need assistance doing this change, please contact our support team and we will be happy to assist you with the modifications. Please make sure to have access to your registrar (Gandi, OVH, Godaddy…) so we can assist you in performing this change. 
The details are also available on our manual.
Thanks,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yannick, Customer Care Team Leader - Pro Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident: Some users may experience issues accessing api.slack.com]]></title>
        <id>https://status.slack.com//2023-03/9011b8a984a74042</id>
        <link href="https://status.slack.com//2023-03/9011b8a984a74042"/>
        <updated>2023-03-14T16:57:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We appreciate your patience while we've continued to investigate this issue. Some customers may still be impacted by the SSL certificate changes, however we will closely monitor reports and provide further updates through customer support tickets with the impacted users. Please reach out to our team at feedback@slack.com for further assistance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Slack System Status</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident: Enterprise users see slowness or error messages when signing in on mobile]]></title>
        <id>https://status.slack.com//2023-03/1da534dc3612b14f</id>
        <link href="https://status.slack.com//2023-03/1da534dc3612b14f"/>
        <updated>2023-03-14T06:21:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Issue summary: 

On March 13th, 2023 from 2:00 PM to 5:00 PM PDT, some Enterprise Grid customers using the Slack for Intune mobile app may have experienced errors or latency when logging in to Slack.


We identified that this issue was caused by a conflict between Slack functionality and a Slack for Intune preference. We deployed a manual fix, resolving the issue for all impacted users.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Slack System Status</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Banking partner delay]]></title>
        <id>https://status.rippling.com/incidents/yhm54z3b1wqg</id>
        <link href="https://status.rippling.com/incidents/yhm54z3b1wqg"/>
        <updated>2023-03-13T06:18:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mar 13, 06:18 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Mar 13, 06:18 UTC
Update - We are continuing to work on a fix for this issue.
Mar 10, 23:13 UTC
Update - All payments with a check date of March 10th have been successfully submitted. Some have been completed, and others will complete between Saturday, March 11th and Monday, March 13th.
This morning, Rippling was assured by SVB that all payments would be processed today. However, when SVB fell into receivership with the FDIC, we immediately began working with JPMorgan Chase to find an alternative means to send funds to employees. 
As a result of the actions we took, all employees will receive their payments between today and Monday morning, depending on which bank they use. Rippling has extended our own capital to fund these pay…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rippling Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Notifications are not working]]></title>
        <id>https://status.notion.so/incidents/zyddfgt7nfmw</id>
        <link href="https://status.notion.so/incidents/zyddfgt7nfmw"/>
        <updated>2023-03-12T16:08:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mar 12, 09:08 PDT
Resolved - Engineering has implemented a fix. Notification issue has been resolved.
Mar 12, 09:07 PDT
Update - We are continuing to investigate this issue.
Mar 12, 08:07 PDT
Investigating - We are currently experiencing an issue with notifications. Engineering is investigating the root cause of this issue.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Notion Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Database upgrade]]></title>
        <id>https://status.notion.so/incidents/pxth0clm33h4</id>
        <link href="https://status.notion.so/incidents/pxth0clm33h4"/>
        <updated>2023-03-11T23:55:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mar 11, 15:55 PST
Completed - The scheduled maintenance has been completed.
Mar 11, 15:35 PST
In progress - Scheduled maintenance is currently in progress. We will provide updates as necessary.
Mar 11, 15:34 PST
Scheduled - We are currently undergoing scheduled maintenance. Notifications may be unavailable between 3:30 - 3:40pm Pacific time. Notifications received during that time will be sent when the maintenance is complete.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Notion Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Device actions are slow and the Rippling Admin account may temporarily be out of sync]]></title>
        <id>https://status.rippling.com/incidents/k4qyh9s92rw1</id>
        <link href="https://status.rippling.com/incidents/k4qyh9s92rw1"/>
        <updated>2023-03-10T23:50:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mar 10, 23:50 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Mar 10, 19:13 UTC
Update - A fix has been deployed, recovery efforts are underway.  ETA for resolution is today.
Mar  9, 23:05 UTC
Identified - The issue has been identified and a fix is being implemented.
Mar  9, 18:10 UTC
Investigating - We are currently investigating this issue.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rippling Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident: Some customers are seeing errors when attempting to connect Google Drive]]></title>
        <id>https://status.slack.com//2023-03/452b13772c8c8b7d</id>
        <link href="https://status.slack.com//2023-03/452b13772c8c8b7d"/>
        <updated>2023-03-10T20:12:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Issue summary:

On March 9, 2023 from 8:28 PM to March 10, 2023 8:40 AM PST, some users that were signed into multiple workspaces experienced a redirect issue when signing into the Google Drive app from Slack. 


After the sign-in button was clicked, the user was redirected to a different Slack workspace they were signed into, causing a 400 Bad Request response.


We made a code change to ensure the user was redirected to the proper workspace, fixing the authentication error and resolving the issue.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Slack System Status</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident: Service degradation in Slack]]></title>
        <id>https://status.slack.com//2023-03/dd0ae32c5786a66f</id>
        <link href="https://status.slack.com//2023-03/dd0ae32c5786a66f"/>
        <updated>2023-03-09T22:57:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Issue summary:

On March 9, 2023 from 9:07 AM to 10:06 AM PST, some users experienced trouble with various features in Slack, such as adding bookmarks to channels, using workflows, connecting to Slack, or sending Slack Connect invites.


We discovered the service degradation was prompted by a load test that ran at a higher rate than intended, causing database outages to occur. To remediate the issue, we scaled back the load test to the normal rate which resolved the problem for all impacted users.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Slack System Status</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Issues loading Rippling]]></title>
        <id>https://status.rippling.com/incidents/grbrkfxrz4m1</id>
        <link href="https://status.rippling.com/incidents/grbrkfxrz4m1"/>
        <updated>2023-03-09T21:48:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mar  9, 21:48 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Mar  9, 19:40 UTC
Update - We are continuing to monitor for any further issues.
Mar  9, 19:22 UTC
Monitoring - We've identified a root cause for the issue and have resolved page loading issues. We are continuing to monitor for any further issues.
Mar  9, 18:40 UTC
Investigating - We are currently investigating this issue.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rippling Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RESOLVED: Our team is continuing to investigate this issue. We will provide an update by Mar 9, 2023, 12:00 AM UTC with more information about this problem. Thank you for your patience.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.google.com/appsstatus/dashboard/incidents/PveZwKACdwUHgsRVazR4</id>
        <link href="https://www.google.com/appsstatus/dashboard/incidents/PveZwKACdwUHgsRVazR4"/>
        <updated>2023-03-09T18:32:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p> Incident began at <strong>2023-03-07 15:00</strong> and ended at <strong>2023-03-09 09:03</strong> <span>(times are in <strong>Coordinated Universal Time (UTC)</strong>).</span></p><div class="cBIRi14aVDP__status-update-text"><h1>Mini Incident Report</h1>
<p>We apologize for the inconvenience this service disruption/outage may have caused. We would like to provide some information about this incident below. Please note, this information is based on our best knowledge at the time of posting and is subject to change as our investigation continues. If you have experienced impact outside of what is listed below, please reach out to Google Cloud Support using <a href="https://cloud.google.com/support">https://cloud.google.com/support</a>  or to Google Workspace Support using help article <a href="https://support.google.com/a/answer/1047213">https://support.google.com/a/answer/1047213</a>.</p>
<p>(All Times US/Pacific)</p>
<p><strong>Incident Start:</strong> 7 March, 2023 07:00</p>
<p><strong>Incident End:</strong> 9 March, 2023 01:09</p>
<p><strong>Duration:</strong>  1 day, 18 hours, 9 minutes</p>
<p><strong>Affected Services and Features:</strong></p>
<p>Admin Console</p>
<p><strong>Regions/Zones:</strong> Global</p>
<p><strong>Description:</strong></p>
<p>The Google Workspace Admin Console displayed 0 customer-level storage usage for 1 day, 18 hours, and 9 minutes. This issue only affected Workspace customer admins viewing the Storage page in the Admin Console. From preliminary analysis, the root cause of the issue was a failure in a background process that populates storage usage data.</p>
<p>During this time, admins would have been able to view the correct storage usage in Drive.</p>
<p><strong>Customer Impact:</strong></p>
<p>Workspace customer admins would have observed 0 customer-level storage data in the Admin Console.</p>
</div><hr><p>Affected products: Admin Console</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Workspace Status Dashboard Updates</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Devices app is sending an erroneous email prompting employees to enter their password]]></title>
        <id>https://status.rippling.com/incidents/y9wybwpbgtfd</id>
        <link href="https://status.rippling.com/incidents/y9wybwpbgtfd"/>
        <updated>2023-03-09T17:29:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mar  9, 17:29 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Mar  9, 04:47 UTC
Monitoring - A fix has been implemented and we are monitoring the results.
Mar  9, 04:47 UTC
Identified - The issue has been identified and a fix is being implemented.
Mar  8, 23:23 UTC
Investigating - We are currently investigating this issue.  The email subject is "Action required: Enter your device password in the Rippling Desktop App".  Employees can ignore this email for the time being.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rippling Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident with Webhooks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/dkm3dxjzynxh</id>
        <link href="https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/dkm3dxjzynxh"/>
        <updated>2023-03-09T16:36:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mar  9, 16:36 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Mar  9, 16:07 UTC
Update - We have found the cause of degraded Webhooks performance and are seeing signs of recovery.
Mar  9, 15:08 UTC
Update - We are investigating reports of issues with Webhooks. We will continue to keep users updated on progress towards mitigation.
Mar  9, 14:34 UTC
Investigating - We are investigating reports of degraded performance for Webhooks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GitHub Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Important information regarding your website domain!]]></title>
        <id>259586</id>
        <link href="https://changelog.bookingsync.com/important-information-regarding-your-website-domain!-259586"/>
        <updated>2023-03-09T12:25:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Communications
  
We will be doing some improvements on our website infrastructure which may temporarily affect your websites.
The maintenance will take place on tuesday March 14, 2023 at 06:00am CET and will have a duration of 3 hours max.
What will be the impact?
· Websites may not be unreachable for up to 10 minutes at maintenance time.
· SSL may be unavailable from the beginning of the maintenance for up to 3 hours (website will still be reachable without https)
Do I need to do anything?
This maintenance will impact the DNS zone we are using to link your website to our infrastructure, therefore some changes will be required in the 2 weeks following this update if you are using your own domain name with A records.
We will send a second communication with the information and update our manual to help you with this transition.
Of course our support team will be there to assist you.
Thank you for your comprehension,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yannick, Customer Care Team Leader - Pro Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident: Slowness searching in Slack]]></title>
        <id>https://status.slack.com//2023-03/95e9c4b099d9b5bc</id>
        <link href="https://status.slack.com//2023-03/95e9c4b099d9b5bc"/>
        <updated>2023-03-09T00:40:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Issue summary: 

On March 7, 2023 from 9:15 AM to 6:31 PM PST, some users may have experienced slow search response times or failed searches.


We made a routine adjustment to our infrastructure that inadvertently increased load and decreased response rates for our search servers. New messages sent during this period were not indexed immediately and would not have been searchable.


We restarted the affected server nodes, returning search performance to normal and allowing the system to catch up on the backlogged indexing tasks. Once the system handled the backlog and we confirmed that indexing was complete, full search functionality was restored to all customers.


Thank you for your patience while we worked through this. We apologize for any disruption to your work.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Slack System Status</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Increased latency and intermittent API failures]]></title>
        <id>https://status.rippling.com/incidents/gwz9016ttd80</id>
        <link href="https://status.rippling.com/incidents/gwz9016ttd80"/>
        <updated>2023-03-08T23:58:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mar  8, 23:58 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Mar  8, 21:41 UTC
Monitoring - Starting at 12:20 pacific time, we started seeing increased latency and intermittent API failures across all Rippling products. From 1 pm PT, latencies and API failures have recovered, and we are now continuing to monitor for any further issues.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rippling Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident: Some users are not receiving emails from Slack]]></title>
        <id>https://status.slack.com//2023-03/089dc62cc1ce000a</id>
        <link href="https://status.slack.com//2023-03/089dc62cc1ce000a"/>
        <updated>2023-03-07T20:26:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Issue Summary:

On Sunday March 5, 2023 from 4:00pm PST to March 6, 2023 1:51pm PST, some users weren't receiving sign-in codes, or the codes were delivered to their spam folder. 


Our team determined this wasn't an issue caused by Slack, but a third-party email provider. 


To ensure emails from Slack are successfully routed to the appropriate inbox, impacted users should add the domains @slack.com and @slack-mail.com, to their trusted senders list.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Slack System Status</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident with Git Operations]]></title>
        <id>https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/71v1ws5dkyhx</id>
        <link href="https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/71v1ws5dkyhx"/>
        <updated>2023-03-07T18:54:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mar  7, 18:54 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Mar  7, 18:20 UTC
Investigating - We are investigating reports of degraded performance for Git Operations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GitHub Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Increased web latency and some webhooks might return error for users on eu1.make.com]]></title>
        <id>https://status.make.com/incidents/fj3k6x4509bb</id>
        <link href="https://status.make.com/incidents/fj3k6x4509bb"/>
        <updated>2023-03-07T13:09:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mar  7, 14:09 CET
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Mar  7, 11:52 CET
Monitoring - Issue was resolved and platform is fully operational.
Mar  7, 11:07 CET
Investigating - We are currently investigating the issues.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Make Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Delay in email delivery due to third-party outage]]></title>
        <id>https://status.rippling.com/incidents/m11k5897z9ld</id>
        <link href="https://status.rippling.com/incidents/m11k5897z9ld"/>
        <updated>2023-03-06T22:38:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mar  6, 22:38 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Mar  6, 17:49 UTC
Monitoring - A fix has been implemented and we are monitoring the results.
Mar  6, 17:45 UTC
Investigating - We're seeing elevated errors from our email provider and are working with them to restore service.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rippling Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident with Codespaces]]></title>
        <id>https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/00ymkms22sz7</id>
        <link href="https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/00ymkms22sz7"/>
        <updated>2023-03-06T16:14:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mar  6, 16:14 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Mar  6, 15:54 UTC
Update - We are working to mitigate issues with Codespaces in the Europe West geographic area. Some users may not be able to connect to their Codespaces at this time.
Mar  6, 15:16 UTC
Update - We are investigating issues with Codespaces in the Europe West geographic area. Some users may not be able to resume Codespaces at this time. We will update you on mitigation progress.
Mar  6, 14:43 UTC
Investigating - We are investigating reports of degraded performance for Codespaces.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GitHub Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident with Codespaces]]></title>
        <id>https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/by9x6zbmfx8y</id>
        <link href="https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/by9x6zbmfx8y"/>
        <updated>2023-03-06T09:19:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mar  6, 09:19 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Mar  6, 08:39 UTC
Investigating - We are investigating reports of degraded performance for Codespaces.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GitHub Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Investigating reports of degraded performance.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/sr7zptjd0b07</id>
        <link href="https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/sr7zptjd0b07"/>
        <updated>2023-03-03T21:14:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mar  3, 21:14 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Mar  3, 17:32 UTC
Update - Due to a GitHub Actions outage yesterday, users may see inconsistent or stale workflow runs while the data is fixed. Customers are not being billed for these runs and new runs are not affected.
Mar  3, 17:32 UTC
Investigating - We are currently investigating this issue.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GitHub Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident: Users are experiencing issues connecting to Slack]]></title>
        <id>https://status.slack.com//2023-03/2231b440c182cfde</id>
        <link href="https://status.slack.com//2023-03/2231b440c182cfde"/>
        <updated>2023-03-03T19:47:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Issue summary:


On March 3rd, 2023 from 9:03 AM PST to 9:13 AM PST, some users had trouble logging into Slack, sending messages and completing API requests.


The cause of this issue was in relation to a planned exercise where we removed traffic from an isolated location to simulate failure of a single data center. In our investigation, we discovered that one database experienced an issue causing the exercise to fail. We were able to quickly identify the failure and apply a manual fix which resolved the issue. We determined less than 1% of our customers were affected.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Slack System Status</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident with Actions and Pages]]></title>
        <id>https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/qfby3shb6r3w</id>
        <link href="https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/qfby3shb6r3w"/>
        <updated>2023-03-03T01:55:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mar  3, 01:55 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Mar  3, 01:40 UTC
Update - Pages is operating normally.
Mar  3, 01:11 UTC
Update - We are still working on mitigating the issue
Mar  3, 00:35 UTC
Update - We are actively working on mitigating the issue
Mar  3, 00:27 UTC
Update - Pages is experiencing degraded availability. We are still investigating and will provide an update when we have one.
Mar  3, 00:06 UTC
Update - We have identified the issue and are attempting to mitigate it.
Mar  2, 23:37 UTC
Investigating - We are investigating reports of degraded availability for Actions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GitHub Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident: Some users may experience issues accessing api.slack.com]]></title>
        <id>https://status.slack.com//2023-03/27c0f9229399a532</id>
        <link href="https://status.slack.com//2023-03/27c0f9229399a532"/>
        <updated>2023-03-02T21:46:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Issue summary:

On March 2nd, 2023 from 4:00 AM PST to 7:00 AM PST, some users were receiving errors related to an invalid date on their SSL certificate when calling Slack's APIs.


We discovered that an update we released on our SSL certificate was causing the issues. We've rolled back the update and the issue was resolved.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Slack System Status</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident with Git Operations]]></title>
        <id>https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/z0kj7nzrhrn5</id>
        <link href="https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/z0kj7nzrhrn5"/>
        <updated>2023-03-02T18:43:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mar  2, 18:43 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Mar  2, 18:26 UTC
Investigating - We are investigating reports of degraded performance for Git Operations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GitHub Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident with Packages and Pages]]></title>
        <id>https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/bypf7bqdh4g0</id>
        <link href="https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/bypf7bqdh4g0"/>
        <updated>2023-03-01T15:26:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mar  1, 15:26 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Mar  1, 15:06 UTC
Update - Packages is operating normally.
Mar  1, 14:48 UTC
Update - Packages is now experiencing degraded performance. We are still investigating and will provide an update when we have one.
Mar  1, 14:07 UTC
Update - We have identified the issue with Packages and are working to restore service.  We will continue to keep users updated on progress.
Mar  1, 13:44 UTC
Update - Packages is now experiencing degraded availability. We are still investigating and will provide an update when we have one.
Mar  1, 13:39 UTC
Update - Pages is experiencing degraded performance. We are continuing to investigate.
Mar  1, 13:31 UTC
Update - We are still investigating reports of issues with service(s): Packages. We will continue to keep users updated on progress towards mitigation.
Mar  1, 13:00 UTC
Update - We are still investigating reports of issues with service(s): Packages. We will continue to keep users updated on progress towards mitigation.
Mar  1, 12:19 UTC
Investigating - We are investigating reports of degraded performance for Packages.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GitHub Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident with Codespaces]]></title>
        <id>https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/f4l7jtckk0mx</id>
        <link href="https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/f4l7jtckk0mx"/>
        <updated>2023-02-28T18:08:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Feb 28, 18:08 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Feb 28, 17:57 UTC
Update - We are investigating issues with Codespaces in the US West geographic area. Some users may not be able to connect to their codespaces at this time. We will update you on mitigation progress.
Feb 28, 17:55 UTC
Investigating - We are investigating reports of degraded performance for Codespaces.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GitHub Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident with Actions and Codespaces]]></title>
        <id>https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/d6f6kjk81v33</id>
        <link href="https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/d6f6kjk81v33"/>
        <updated>2023-02-28T17:31:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Feb 28, 17:31 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Feb 28, 17:26 UTC
Update - Codespaces is operating normally.
Feb 28, 17:00 UTC
Update - Actions is now experiencing degraded performance. We are still investigating and will provide an update when we have one.
Feb 28, 17:00 UTC
Update - Actions is now experiencing degraded availability. We are continuing to investigate.
Feb 28, 16:58 UTC
Update - The Actions Larger Runner beta is experiencing issues with VM scale up which will lead to longer queue times for runs using Larger Runners. Hosted and self-hosted runners are not impacted. We're continuing to investigate and work on mitigations.
Feb 28, 16:49 UTC
Update - Actions is experiencing degraded performance. We are still investigating and will provide an update when we have one.
Feb 28, 16:20 UTC
Update - We are investigating issues with Codespaces in the US East geographic area. Users may not be able to create or connect to their codespaces at this time. We will update you on mitigation progress.
Feb 28, 16:18 UTC
Update - Codespaces is now experiencing degraded availability. We are still investigating and will provide an update when we have one.
Feb 28, 16:05 UTC
Investigating - We are investigating reports of degraded performance for Codespaces.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GitHub Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident: Audio files not loading on iOS]]></title>
        <id>https://status.slack.com//2023-02/02601159ddfe8926</id>
        <link href="https://status.slack.com//2023-02/02601159ddfe8926"/>
        <updated>2023-02-28T01:39:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Issue summary:

From February 22nd, 2023 at 2:00 PM until February 24th, 2023 2:16 PM PST, some users experienced issues loading audio files on iOS.


We discovered that the server was returning an unexpected code in response to requests for audio files, causing the app to only partially load the content. We made a change to ensure the server returned the correct response code, resolving the issue for all affected customers.


If you continue to run into any trouble, please feel free to reach out to us at feedback@slack.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Slack System Status</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident with Packages]]></title>
        <id>https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/sn4m3hkqr4vz</id>
        <link href="https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/sn4m3hkqr4vz"/>
        <updated>2023-02-27T23:48:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Feb 27, 23:48 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Feb 27, 22:50 UTC
Update - We are continuing to work on a mitigation for the issue.
Feb 27, 21:37 UTC
Update - We found an issue that impacts a small percentage of customers. We are working on mitigation.
Feb 27, 20:53 UTC
Investigating - We are investigating reports of degraded performance for Packages.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GitHub Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident: Some customers may be experiencing issues with several apps]]></title>
        <id>https://status.slack.com//2023-02/7979b0cca971d61d</id>
        <link href="https://status.slack.com//2023-02/7979b0cca971d61d"/>
        <updated>2023-02-24T13:43:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Issue Summary:

From February 23, 2023 at 4:00 p.m. PST until February 24, 2023 at 12:13 a.m. PST, some customers were not able to use several apps within the workspace. The issue was caused by a certificate, which didn't push online successfully after renewal. The certificate has now been pushed and the issue is resolved.


*The times mentioned above have been updated since our initial posting to accurately reflect the duration of this issue.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Slack System Status</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident: Some customers in the Phillipines may not be able to connect to Slack]]></title>
        <id>https://status.slack.com//2023-02/af03df0d823385ea</id>
        <link href="https://status.slack.com//2023-02/af03df0d823385ea"/>
        <updated>2023-02-24T11:02:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Issue summary:

From February 23, 2023 at 5:24 p.m. PST until February 23, 2023 at 8:23 p.m. PST, some customers in the Phillipines were not able to access Slack. We looked into it and found that the issue was an external factor that we have now addressed it on our end and the impacted users have confirmed that they can now access Slack.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Slack System Status</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[User experience may be degraded, API timing out. Scenario executions not affected.]]></title>
        <id>https://status.make.com/incidents/bfwvl405xdtk</id>
        <link href="https://status.make.com/incidents/bfwvl405xdtk"/>
        <updated>2023-02-23T19:35:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Feb 23, 20:35 CET
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Feb 23, 18:52 CET
Monitoring - A fix has been implemented and we are monitoring the results.
Feb 23, 18:02 CET
Update - We are continuing to investigate this issue.
Feb 23, 17:18 CET
Investigating - Website performance may be degraded and API requests are timing out. Users may not be able to use the web interface to manage their organizations and scenarios. The team is currently investigating the root cause of the issue.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Make Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident: Errors when running workflows]]></title>
        <id>https://status.slack.com//2023-02/613045ca17f01e05</id>
        <link href="https://status.slack.com//2023-02/613045ca17f01e05"/>
        <updated>2023-02-22T20:27:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Issue Summary:

On February 22nd, 2023 from 08:44 AM PST to 09:22 AM PST, some users experienced issues with using workflows.


We discovered an issue that prevented workflow API calls from successfully writing changes to our database. After restarting this process, workflow functionality was restored for all impacted users.


We continued monitoring our metrics and announced the resolution when we were confident the issue was resolved.


If you continue to run into any issues please feel free to reach out to our support team.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Slack System Status</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident: Some customers are experiencing server errors with the GitHub Enterprise Server app]]></title>
        <id>https://status.slack.com//2023-02/8bc92fb069ee6b8a</id>
        <link href="https://status.slack.com//2023-02/8bc92fb069ee6b8a"/>
        <updated>2023-02-22T08:32:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Issue summary:

From Monday February 20th 2023 at 15:00 PST until Tuesday February 21st 2023 22:00 PST, 

A PR that changed the type of an argument used by the Github plugin was pushed to production. This change caused a type mismatch and subsequently HTTP 500 errors. The issue was resolved once the PR was reverted.


We're very sorry for any inconvenience caused.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Slack System Status</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident: Issues with mobile notifications for Enterprise Grid customers]]></title>
        <id>https://status.slack.com//2023-02/c9c747e89bf62116</id>
        <link href="https://status.slack.com//2023-02/c9c747e89bf62116"/>
        <updated>2023-02-21T19:41:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Issue summary:


From Tuesday, February 14th, 2023 at 09:52 AM PST until Tuesday, February 21st, 2023 at 08:56 AM PST, some enterprise customers experienced issues with the delivery of mobile notifications on Android devices.


Our team identified that the cause of the issue was linked to a recent change with notification clearing. We rolled back this change which fixed the issue. 


We're very sorry for any inconvenience caused.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Slack System Status</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident: Some customers are having issues loading the admin page]]></title>
        <id>https://status.slack.com//2023-02/a262a4178e42e17e</id>
        <link href="https://status.slack.com//2023-02/a262a4178e42e17e"/>
        <updated>2023-02-20T21:19:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Issue summary:

From February 14th, 2023 at 10:49AM PST until February 20th, 2023 at 1:16 AM PST some customers were unable to load their workspace's admin page. We traced this issue to a recent code change, which resulted in the workspace token being invalidated when visiting the admin page from a browser. Reverting this code change fixed the issue for all affected customers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Slack System Status</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident with Actions and Pull Requests]]></title>
        <id>https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/pd991fsqrw9s</id>
        <link href="https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/pd991fsqrw9s"/>
        <updated>2023-02-19T14:38:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Feb 19, 14:38 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Feb 19, 14:13 UTC
Update - Actions is experiencing degraded performance. We are continuing to investigate.
Feb 19, 13:54 UTC
Investigating - We are investigating reports of degraded performance for Pull Requests.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GitHub Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>