<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2023-02-08T00:22:17.165Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2023-02-08T00:22:17.165Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US MMS Carrier Partner Maintenance]]></title>
        <id>https://status.twilio.com/incidents/jswbqxvn503k</id>
        <link href="https://status.twilio.com/incidents/jswbqxvn503k"/>
        <updated>2023-02-08T06:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[THIS IS A SCHEDULED EVENT Feb 7, 22:00 PST  -  Feb 8, 05:00 PST
Feb  1, 08:57 PST
Scheduled - Our MMS carrier partner in the US is conducting a planned maintenance from 07 February 2023 at 22:00 PST until 08 February 2023 at 05:00 PST. During the maintenance window, there could be intermittent delays delivering MMS to and from US Verizon handsets via a subset of short codes and long codes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Twilio Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident with Codespaces]]></title>
        <id>https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/cmsz976yn1km</id>
        <link href="https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/cmsz976yn1km"/>
        <updated>2023-02-07T23:58:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Feb  7, 23:58 UTC
Update - We are still investigating issues with Codespaces in the Southeast Asia area and will provide updates.
Feb  7, 23:24 UTC
Update - We are still investigating issues with Codespaces in the Southeast Asia area and will provide updates.
Feb  7, 22:46 UTC
Update - We are still investigating issues with Codespaces in the Southeast Asia area and will provide updates.
Feb  7, 22:12 UTC
Update - We are investigating issues with Codespaces in Southeast Asia. Users in that location may not be able to connect to their Codespaces during this time. We are investigating and will provide updates.
Feb  7, 21:36 UTC
Update - We are investigating issues with Codespaces in Southeast Asia. Users in that location may not be able to connect to their Codespaces during this time. We are investigating and will provide updates.
Feb  7, 21:30 UTC
Investigating - We are investigating reports of degraded performance for Codespaces.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GitHub Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Russia SMS Carrier Maintenance - Beeline]]></title>
        <id>https://status.twilio.com/incidents/fj1f5v6qbjvd</id>
        <link href="https://status.twilio.com/incidents/fj1f5v6qbjvd"/>
        <updated>2023-02-07T21:00:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Feb  7, 13:00 PST
In progress - Scheduled maintenance is currently in progress. We will provide updates as necessary.
Feb  1, 02:02 PST
Scheduled - The Beeline network in Russia is conducting a planned maintenance from 07 February 2023 at 13:00 PST until 07 February 2023 at 20:00 PST. During the maintenance window, there could be intermittent delays delivering SMS to and from Beeline Russia handsets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Twilio Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident with Codespaces]]></title>
        <id>https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/wy9lzdg3ycxn</id>
        <link href="https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/wy9lzdg3ycxn"/>
        <updated>2023-02-07T19:18:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Feb  7, 19:18 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Feb  7, 18:47 UTC
Update - We are investigating issues with Codespaces in the US West region. Users may not be able to connect to their Codespaces during this time. We are investigating and will provide updates.
Feb  7, 18:40 UTC
Investigating - We are investigating reports of degraded performance for Codespaces.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GitHub Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident with Actions]]></title>
        <id>https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/ygpk8m60shzm</id>
        <link href="https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/ygpk8m60shzm"/>
        <updated>2023-02-07T18:17:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Feb  7, 18:17 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Feb  7, 18:05 UTC
Update - We are investigating delays starting workflow runs and delays transitioning workflows from in-progress to completed
Feb  7, 17:26 UTC
Investigating - We are investigating reports of degraded performance for Actions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GitHub Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Inbound Call Failures To A Subset Of Phone Numbers In Brazil]]></title>
        <id>https://status.twilio.com/incidents/lrscjqbhvrt6</id>
        <link href="https://status.twilio.com/incidents/lrscjqbhvrt6"/>
        <updated>2023-02-07T17:30:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Feb  7, 09:30 PST
Resolved - The issue affecting inbound calls to a subset of phone numbers In Brazil phone numbers has been resolved, and the service is functioning normally at this time.
Feb  7, 07:35 PST
Monitoring - We have started seeing recovery for inbound calls to a subset of phone numbers In Brazil phone numbers. We will continue to monitor to ensure a full recovery. We expect to provide another update in 2 hours or as soon as more information becomes available.
Feb  7, 00:00 PST
Update - We are still observing inbound call failures to a subset of phone numbers In Brazil. We are currently working with our carrier partner to resolve the issue. We expect to provide another update in 8 hours or as soon as more information becomes available.
Feb  6, 21:00 PST
Update - We are still observing inbound call failures to a subset of phone numbers In Brazil. We are currently working with our carrier partner to resolve the issue. We expect to provide another update in 4 hours or as soon as more information becomes available.
Feb  6, 19:00 PST
Update - We are still observing inbound call failures to a subset of phone numbers In Brazil. We are currently working with our carrier partner to resolve the issue. We expect to provide another update in 2 hours or as soon as more information becomes available.
Feb  6, 17:58 PST
Investigating - We are observing inbound call failures to a subset of phone numbers In Brazil. We are currently working with our carrier partner to resolve the issue. We expect to provide another update in 1 hour or as soon as more information becomes available.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Twilio Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BIs with incorrect country code metadata resulting in incorrect invoice for December 2022 month end]]></title>
        <id>https://status.twilio.com/incidents/gstrwsc8r0dk</id>
        <link href="https://status.twilio.com/incidents/gstrwsc8r0dk"/>
        <updated>2023-02-07T14:16:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Feb  7, 06:16 PST
Resolved - On January 4th, during a planned BI update to resolve detected configuration issues, 835 BIs were misconfigured. The Month End for December usage was run on January 5th, during which metadata which had been changed during this configuration event was used to produce invoices for 89,097 accounts. The misconfiguration led to invoices assigning BIs to incorrect countries. This led to 5 customer contacts, with some customers delaying paying their invoices pending an updated invoice. The issue was escalated to engineering on January 25th as a single customer incident. Further triage identified the breadth of the problem and causes by February 2nd. The issue was resolved when revised invoices were sent to 5497 Invoiced customers and 6,357 PAYG customers that are configured to have invoices emailed to them on February 6th.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Twilio Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SMS Delivery Delays to AT&T Network]]></title>
        <id>https://status.twilio.com/incidents/xp4fj5ydl96l</id>
        <link href="https://status.twilio.com/incidents/xp4fj5ydl96l"/>
        <updated>2023-02-07T14:14:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Feb  7, 06:14 PST
Resolved - We are no longer experiencing SMS delivery delays when sending messages to AT&T US. This incident has been resolved.
Feb  7, 04:31 PST
Monitoring - We are observing recovery in SMS delivery delays when sending messages to AT&T US. We will continue monitoring the service to ensure a full recovery. We will provide another update in 2 hours or as soon as more information becomes available.
Feb  7, 02:31 PST
Update - We are experiencing MMS/SMS delivery delays when sending messages to AT&T Network US. Our engineers are working with our carrier partner to resolve the issue. We will provide another update in 2 hours or as soon as more information becomes available.
Feb  7, 01:31 PST
Investigating - We are experiencing MMS/SMS delivery delays when sending messages to AT&T Network US. Our engineers are working with our carrier partner to resolve the issue. We will provide another update in 1 hour or as soon as more information becomes available.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Twilio Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[eu1.make.com intermittent issues with web UI]]></title>
        <id>https://status.make.com/incidents/4xvlf500dn4r</id>
        <link href="https://status.make.com/incidents/4xvlf500dn4r"/>
        <updated>2023-02-07T13:24:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Feb  7, 14:24 CET
Resolved - The issue has been resolved.
Feb  7, 13:32 CET
Monitoring - Some users might have experienced intermittent issues with web UI and manual scenario executions between 13:00-13:20 CET. The issue is resolved now and we are monitoring the situation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Make Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SMS Delivery Failures to Vinaphone Network in Vietnam]]></title>
        <id>https://status.twilio.com/incidents/5m9wchb48wjk</id>
        <link href="https://status.twilio.com/incidents/5m9wchb48wjk"/>
        <updated>2023-02-07T10:20:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Feb  7, 02:20 PST
Resolved - We are no longer experiencing MMS/SMS delivery failures to Vinaphone Network in Vietnam. This incident has been resolved.
Feb  7, 01:51 PST
Monitoring - We are observing successful SMS delivery to Vietnam Vinaphone Network. We will continue to monitor to ensure full service recovery. We expect to provide another update in 30 minutes or as soon as more information becomes available.
Feb  6, 23:52 PST
Update - We continue to experience SMS delivery failures to Vinaphone Network in Vietnam. Our engineers are working with our carrier partner to resolve the issue. We expect to provide another update in 2 hours or as soon as more information becomes available.
Feb  6, 22:52 PST
Investigating - We are experiencing SMS delivery failures to Vinaphone Network in Vietnam. Our engineers are working with our carrier partner to resolve the issue. We expect to provide another update in 1 hour or as soon as more information becomes available.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Twilio Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ecuador SMS Carrier Maintenance - Movistar]]></title>
        <id>https://status.twilio.com/incidents/68dqyz2pn5qv</id>
        <link href="https://status.twilio.com/incidents/68dqyz2pn5qv"/>
        <updated>2023-02-07T10:00:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Feb  7, 02:00 PST
Completed - The scheduled maintenance has been completed.
Feb  6, 21:01 PST
In progress - Scheduled maintenance is currently in progress. We will provide updates as necessary.
Feb  1, 01:01 PST
Scheduled - The Movistar network in Ecuador is conducting a planned maintenance from 06 February 2023 at 21:00 PST until 07 February 2023 at 02:00 PST. During the maintenance window, there could be intermittent delays delivering SMS to and from Movistar Ecuador handsets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Twilio Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Issues loading Rippling]]></title>
        <id>https://status.rippling.com/incidents/k51115m431f5</id>
        <link href="https://status.rippling.com/incidents/k51115m431f5"/>
        <updated>2023-02-07T00:32:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Feb  7, 00:32 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Feb  6, 22:25 UTC
Update - We are continuing to monitor for any further issues.
Feb  6, 22:23 UTC
Monitoring - A fix has been implemented and we are monitoring the results.
Feb  6, 22:18 UTC
Identified - The issue has been identified and a fix is being implemented.
Feb  6, 22:17 UTC
Update - We are continuing to investigate this issue.
Feb  6, 22:07 UTC
Investigating - We are currently investigating this issue.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rippling Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RESOLVED: We're investigating reports of an issue with Google Voice. We will provide more information shortly.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.google.com/appsstatus/dashboard/incidents/Uhucy5iie4oyhkDy7XAz</id>
        <link href="https://www.google.com/appsstatus/dashboard/incidents/Uhucy5iie4oyhkDy7XAz"/>
        <updated>2023-02-07T00:31:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p> Incident began at <strong>2023-02-06 17:52</strong> and ended at <strong>2023-02-07 00:20</strong> <span>(times are in <strong>Coordinated Universal Time (UTC)</strong>).</span></p><div class="cBIRi14aVDP__status-update-text"><p>The issue with Google Voice has been resolved for all affected users as of Monday, 2023-02-06 16:20 US/Pacific.</p>
<p>We thank you for your patience while we worked on resolving the issue.</p>
</div><hr><p>Affected products: Google Voice</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Workspace Status Dashboard Updates</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident with Actions]]></title>
        <id>https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/cvhhm9zxcr49</id>
        <link href="https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/cvhhm9zxcr49"/>
        <updated>2023-02-06T22:56:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Feb  6, 22:56 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Feb  6, 22:55 UTC
Update - We have resolved the issue but some old Actions runs may still fail to get displayed.
Feb  6, 22:22 UTC
Update - We are investigating reports of issues with service(s): Actions. We will continue to keep users updated on progress towards mitigation.
Feb  6, 21:49 UTC
Investigating - We are investigating reports of degraded performance for Actions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GitHub Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Issues with new device ordering]]></title>
        <id>https://status.rippling.com/incidents/18r6rkmyggd5</id>
        <link href="https://status.rippling.com/incidents/18r6rkmyggd5"/>
        <updated>2023-02-06T22:11:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Feb  6, 22:11 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Feb  6, 19:19 UTC
Monitoring - A fix has been implemented and we are monitoring the results.
Feb  6, 18:12 UTC
Identified - The issue has been identified and a fix is being implemented.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rippling Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident with Codespaces]]></title>
        <id>https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/dyt4c3n4bqc2</id>
        <link href="https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/dyt4c3n4bqc2"/>
        <updated>2023-02-06T10:55:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Feb  6, 10:55 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Feb  6, 10:25 UTC
Update - We are investigating reports of degraded performance in UK South for Codespaces. We will continue to keep users updated on progress towards mitigation.
Feb  6, 09:50 UTC
Investigating - We are investigating reports of degraded performance for Codespaces.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GitHub Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[500 Errors Across Multiple Endpoints]]></title>
        <id>https://airbnbapi.statuspage.io/incidents/66sdpg5yjbcm</id>
        <link href="https://airbnbapi.statuspage.io/incidents/66sdpg5yjbcm"/>
        <updated>2023-02-04T06:53:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Feb  3, 22:53 PST
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
If you encounter any further technical issues, please open a case via the Support Dashboard which our team will pick up and respond to in good time.
Apologies for the inconvenience caused due to this incident and thank you for your patience and understanding.
Feb  3, 22:29 PST
Monitoring - Error rates have already decreased to normal levels from 22:00 Pacific Time (PT).
We are monitoring the situation and will resolve the incident soon.
Please retry any requests that may have failed with 500 Errors.
Feb  3, 21:54 PST
Identified - From 21:20 Pacific Time (PT), we saw increased 500 errors for multiple API endpoints, including reservations, listings, threads, etc. The issue is now identified and we are actively working on it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Airbnb API Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident: Some customers may be receiving a server error when viewing our Slack App Developer page]]></title>
        <id>https://status.slack.com//2023-02/8e717c690db78d06</id>
        <link href="https://status.slack.com//2023-02/8e717c690db78d06"/>
        <updated>2023-02-03T03:18:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Issue summary:

On February 2, 2023, from 3:00 PM PST to 6:00 PM PST, some customers may have received a Server Error when attempting to view the Slack App Developer page. 


We traced the failures back to a recent infrastructure change. When we rolled back the change, the problem was resolved for all affected customers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Slack System Status</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Investigating reports of degraded performance.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/ll8gxx3svld7</id>
        <link href="https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/ll8gxx3svld7"/>
        <updated>2023-02-02T20:02:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Feb  2, 20:02 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Feb  2, 16:15 UTC
Update - We have found and are mitigating issues that may affect customers accessing some GitHub services.
Feb  2, 16:15 UTC
Investigating - We are currently investigating this issue.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GitHub Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Investigating reports of degraded performance.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/1cdsggtd2q5k</id>
        <link href="https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/1cdsggtd2q5k"/>
        <updated>2023-02-02T11:55:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Feb  2, 11:55 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Feb  2, 11:29 UTC
Update - We are investigating and mitigating intermittent availability issues on some GitHub services.
Feb  2, 11:29 UTC
Investigating - We are currently investigating this issue.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GitHub Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scheduled infrastructure maintenance]]></title>
        <id>https://status.make.com/incidents/j3y9jdx1my7b</id>
        <link href="https://status.make.com/incidents/j3y9jdx1my7b"/>
        <updated>2023-02-02T10:00:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Feb  2, 11:00 CET
Completed - The scheduled maintenance has been completed.
Feb  2, 09:00 CET
In progress - Scheduled maintenance is currently in progress. We will provide updates as necessary.
Jan 26, 16:31 CET
Scheduled - Please note that we will be undergoing scheduled infrastructure maintenance on Thursday February 2nd between 09:00 AM and 11:00 AM CEST on us1.make.celonis.com and us1.make.com. During this maintenance you can expect few short service interruptions.
During the maintenance the us1.make.celonis.com and us1.make.com website login might be temporarily affected.
Some webhooks and shared hooks processed at that time might be temporarily affected as well.
There will be no impact on eu1.make.com and eu1.make.celonis.com.
We do not expect any data loss.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Make Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scheduled infrastructure maintenance]]></title>
        <id>https://status.make.com/incidents/d7f6r1v6n97k</id>
        <link href="https://status.make.com/incidents/d7f6r1v6n97k"/>
        <updated>2023-02-01T06:00:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Feb  1, 07:00 CET
Completed - The scheduled maintenance has been completed.
Feb  1, 05:00 CET
In progress - Scheduled maintenance is currently in progress. We will provide updates as necessary.
Jan 26, 16:26 CET
Scheduled - Please note that we will be undergoing scheduled infrastructure maintenance on Wednesday February 1st between 05:00 AM and 07:00 AM CEST on eu1.make.celonis.com and eu1.make.com. During this maintenance you can expect few short service interruptions.
During the maintenance the eu1.make.celonis.com and eu1.make.com website login might be temporarily affected.
Some webhooks and shared hooks processed at that time might be temporarily affected as well.
There will be no impact on us1.make.com and us1.make.celonis.com.
We do not expect any data loss.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Make Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident: Errors running workflows]]></title>
        <id>https://status.slack.com//2023-01/ebf9da8220a6b05c</id>
        <link href="https://status.slack.com//2023-01/ebf9da8220a6b05c"/>
        <updated>2023-02-01T05:33:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Issue summary: 

On January 31, 2023 from 11:40 AM PST to 11:55 AM PST, customers may have experienced issues with workflows not running as expected or posting duplicate messages. 


A network event prevented access to some of the database servers that support workflows. This disruption meant that the remaining servers were unable to handle the workflow load. 


We restarted the affected servers and manually increased the capacity to resolve the issue, restoring normal workflow behaviour.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Slack System Status</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident: Users unable to enter team name when creating a workspace]]></title>
        <id>https://status.slack.com//2023-01/603fea25b24ecd52</id>
        <link href="https://status.slack.com//2023-01/603fea25b24ecd52"/>
        <updated>2023-02-01T05:20:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Issue summary: 

On January 31, 2023 from 9:44 AM to 3:17 PM PST, some customers may have experienced issues creating new workspaces. 


An error in our onboarding flow meant we were incorrectly assuming new workspaces had completed the onboarding process before any onboarding actually took place, leaving these newly created workspaces in an unusable limbo state. We reverted the change that caused the initial onboarding inconsistencies, then released a fix to resolve some dependencies from the reverted file. 


Everyone should be able to create new workspaces as normal once again, although you may experience some overzealous onboarding prompts as the system resolves any lingering inconsistencies.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Slack System Status</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident with Webhooks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/dg18mmgm4v3n</id>
        <link href="https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/dg18mmgm4v3n"/>
        <updated>2023-02-01T01:11:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Feb  1, 01:11 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Feb  1, 00:54 UTC
Investigating - We are investigating reports of degraded performance for Webhooks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GitHub Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident with Codespaces]]></title>
        <id>https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/zxl9k08m9xwf</id>
        <link href="https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/zxl9k08m9xwf"/>
        <updated>2023-01-31T21:23:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jan 31, 21:23 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Jan 31, 20:51 UTC
Update - We are continuing to see improvement for customers connecting to Codespaces in the us-east region.
Jan 31, 20:03 UTC
Update - We are continuing to see improvement for customers connecting to Codespaces in the us-east region.
Jan 31, 19:19 UTC
Update - We have put mitigations in place for issues connecting to Codespaces in the us-east region and are beginning to see improvement.
Jan 31, 18:37 UTC
Update - We are continuing to work towards mitigating causes of failures connecting to Codespaces in the us-east region.
Jan 31, 17:55 UTC
Update - We are continuing to work towards mitigating causes of failures connecting to Codespaces in the us-east region.
Jan 31, 17:12 UTC
Update - We have identified the ca…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GitHub Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scheduled infrastructure maintenance]]></title>
        <id>https://status.make.com/incidents/vm4fnpsp3q09</id>
        <link href="https://status.make.com/incidents/vm4fnpsp3q09"/>
        <updated>2023-01-31T06:00:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jan 31, 07:00 CET
Completed - The scheduled maintenance has been completed.
Jan 31, 05:00 CET
In progress - Scheduled maintenance is currently in progress. We will provide updates as necessary.
Jan 26, 16:15 CET
Scheduled - Please note there is scheduled infrastructure maintenance on Tuesday 31st of January, between 5 AM and 7 AM CEST, when you can expect few short service interruptions. 
During this maintenance following services might be potentially affected:
- Migrations will not be available
- Shared hooks created within maintenance will not be accepted nor processed
- Logins to platform might be affected
- Registration of new subscribers won't be possible
- Invitations of new team members won't be possible
- E-mails and notifications might be delayed
- Password reset won't be possible
- Payments for subscription plans won't be accepted  
We will inform you once the maintenance is completed.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Make Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident with Packages and Pages]]></title>
        <id>https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/zf2tk6x40gmh</id>
        <link href="https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/zf2tk6x40gmh"/>
        <updated>2023-01-30T22:23:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jan 30, 22:23 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Jan 30, 22:21 UTC
Update - Pages is operating normally.
Jan 30, 22:08 UTC
Update - Packages is now experiencing degraded availability. We are continuing to investigate.
Jan 30, 21:55 UTC
Update - Packages is experiencing degraded performance. We are continuing to investigate.
Jan 30, 21:48 UTC
Investigating - We are investigating reports of degraded performance for Pages.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GitHub Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident with Actions]]></title>
        <id>https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/d1l8lxw26y8k</id>
        <link href="https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/d1l8lxw26y8k"/>
        <updated>2023-01-30T17:12:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jan 30, 17:12 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Jan 30, 16:28 UTC
Update - Actions continues to experience an outage with larger runners affecting a small number of customers, we continue to investigate and work on mitigation. Hosted and self-hosted runners are not impacted.
Jan 30, 15:54 UTC
Update - Actions continues to experience an outage with larger runners, we continue to investigate and work on mitigation. Hosted and self-hosted runners are not impacted.
Jan 30, 15:17 UTC
Update - Actions continues to experience an outage with larger runners, we continue to investigate and work on mitigation. Hosted and self-hosted runners are not impacted.
Jan 30, 14:39 UTC
Update - Actions continues to experience an outage with larger runners, we continue to investigate and work on mitigation. Hosted and self-hosted runners are not impacted.
Jan 30, 14:07 UTC
Update - Actions continues to experience an outage with larger runners, we continue to investigate and work on mitigation. Hosted and self-hosted runners are not impacted.
Jan 30, 13:33 UTC
Update - Actions continues to experience an outage with larger runners, we are currently investigating and working on mitigation. Hosted and self-hosted runners are not impacted.
Jan 30, 12:57 UTC
Update - Actions is experiencing an outage with larger runners. Hosted and self-hosted runners are not impacted.
Jan 30, 12:07 UTC
Investigating - We are investigating reports of degraded performance for Actions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GitHub Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident with Codespaces]]></title>
        <id>https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/96qcsn6qsl7w</id>
        <link href="https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/96qcsn6qsl7w"/>
        <updated>2023-01-28T11:45:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jan 28, 11:45 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Jan 28, 11:33 UTC
Update - We are investigating intermittent connectivity issues with Codespaces in the Europe West region. We do not see any more issues at this time but are continuing to investigate.
Jan 28, 10:59 UTC
Investigating - We are investigating reports of degraded performance for Codespaces.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GitHub Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident with Packages]]></title>
        <id>https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/mxq7707n6gcf</id>
        <link href="https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/mxq7707n6gcf"/>
        <updated>2023-01-28T05:06:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jan 28, 05:06 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Jan 28, 04:28 UTC
Update - Mitigations being put in place. We are monitoring this recovery and will continue to update.
Jan 28, 03:53 UTC
Update - We are investigating issues with Packages. We will continue to update users as we progress towards mitigation.
Jan 28, 03:12 UTC
Update - We are investigating reports of degraded performance of Packages
Jan 28, 02:40 UTC
Investigating - We are investigating reports of degraded performance for Packages.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GitHub Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Notice: Some users having trouble with custom emoji.]]></title>
        <id>https://status.slack.com//2023-01/c9f36143337b1368</id>
        <link href="https://status.slack.com//2023-01/c9f36143337b1368"/>
        <updated>2023-01-26T04:19:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Issue summary:

On January 25, 2023, from 2:41 PM PST to 6:17 PM PST, some customers may have experienced custom emojis failing to load.


We traced this back to a recent configuration change. When we rolled back the configuration, the problem was resolved for all affected customers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Slack System Status</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident with API Requests and Pull Requests]]></title>
        <id>https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/gbtkj97xtb9n</id>
        <link href="https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/gbtkj97xtb9n"/>
        <updated>2023-01-26T00:38:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jan 26, 00:38 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Jan 25, 23:59 UTC
Investigating - We are investigating reports of degraded performance for API Requests and Pull Requests.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GitHub Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Outage: Users having issues loading Slack]]></title>
        <id>https://status.slack.com//2023-01/eea83e5208c66a72</id>
        <link href="https://status.slack.com//2023-01/eea83e5208c66a72"/>
        <updated>2023-01-25T17:00:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Issue summary: On January 25, 2023 from 7:20 AM PDT to 7:46 AM PDT, some users experienced problems loading messages and threads, previewing files and sending messages in Slack. We traced this issue to a recent internal change and started reverting it immediately. Once this was reverted, the issue was resolved for all impacted users.


Note: We've edited the times in this summary to correct an error made in the initial version posted.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Slack System Status</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident: Workflows using 'Message thread' are failing for Japanese users.]]></title>
        <id>https://status.slack.com//2023-01/a3aa541342db6be3</id>
        <link href="https://status.slack.com//2023-01/a3aa541342db6be3"/>
        <updated>2023-01-25T14:26:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Issue summary:

From January 24, 2023 at 5:30 PM PST until January 24, 2023 at 10:20 PM PST, some customers who were using Slack in Japanese experienced a failure when using the "Send message to a thread" workflow step. 


We identified that this was caused by an earlier change we made to workflows and fixed the issue by reverting the earlier change.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Slack System Status</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident with Actions]]></title>
        <id>https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/4hzj8r2jm0mn</id>
        <link href="https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/4hzj8r2jm0mn"/>
        <updated>2023-01-25T10:39:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jan 25, 10:39 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Jan 25, 10:13 UTC
Update - We are investigating reports of issues with Actions. This looks related to Azure networking issue which is impacting multiple regions. We are seeing improvements and will continue to monitor this.
Jan 25, 09:14 UTC
Investigating - We are investigating reports of degraded performance for Actions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GitHub Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident with Actions, API Requests, Codespaces and Copilot]]></title>
        <id>https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/9c941kssjk0q</id>
        <link href="https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/9c941kssjk0q"/>
        <updated>2023-01-25T09:10:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jan 25, 09:10 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Jan 25, 08:30 UTC
Update - We are investigating reports of issues with service(s): multiple services. We will continue to keep users updated on progress towards mitigation.
Jan 25, 08:04 UTC
Update - Actions is experiencing degraded performance. We are still investigating and will provide an update when we have one.
Jan 25, 07:54 UTC
Update - Codespaces is experiencing degraded performance. We are continuing to investigate.
Jan 25, 07:53 UTC
Update - API Requests is experiencing degraded performance. We are still investigating and will provide an update when we have one.
Jan 25, 07:53 UTC
Investigating - We are investigating reports of degraded performance for Copilot.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GitHub Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident: Threads, direct messages, and channels are currently not loading]]></title>
        <id>https://status.slack.com//2023-01/70633bef2f8b2fd1</id>
        <link href="https://status.slack.com//2023-01/70633bef2f8b2fd1"/>
        <updated>2023-01-24T22:37:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Issue summary:

On January 24, 2023, from 5:50 AM to 9:30 AM PST, some customers experienced errors when opening threads and saw blank channels and direct message histories.


We traced this issue to an unexpected spike in a database load. We made a configuration change that restored full functionality to threads and conversations for all impacted users.


We are investigating ways to prevent this from occurring in the future.


You may need to reload Slack (Command/Ctrl + Shift + R) in order for the fix to be reflected on your end. We're sorry for the disruption we brought to your day.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Slack System Status</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident: Some customers may be encountering an error code when opening a workflow in a new window]]></title>
        <id>https://status.slack.com//2023-01/b5ecc9f98de10873</id>
        <link href="https://status.slack.com//2023-01/b5ecc9f98de10873"/>
        <updated>2023-01-24T16:08:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Issue Summary:

From January 23, 2023 at 3:00 PM PST to January 24, 2023 at 7:02 AM PST some customers encountered an error when opening a workflow in a new window.


We determined this issue was caused by a recent change to how Slack handles additional windows. This change was reverted and the issue was corrected.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Slack System Status</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident: Some users may be experiencing issues with workflows]]></title>
        <id>https://status.slack.com//2023-01/9090b27a5ea06bce</id>
        <link href="https://status.slack.com//2023-01/9090b27a5ea06bce"/>
        <updated>2023-01-24T02:34:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Issue summary: 

On January 23, 2023 from 12:41 PM to 1:15 PM PST, some customers may have experienced issues executing workflows. 


A planned upgrade to part of our infrastructure caused an unexpected spike in database load. Our load-balancing system kicked in automatically, restoring normal workflow functionality.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Slack System Status</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident: A small percentage of users may see a delayed response when loading channels and threads]]></title>
        <id>https://status.slack.com//2023-01/bd2fc67bb1474e78</id>
        <link href="https://status.slack.com//2023-01/bd2fc67bb1474e78"/>
        <updated>2023-01-24T02:32:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Issue summary:

On January 23, 2023 from around 12:41 PM to 1:15 PM PST, some customers may have experienced delays when opening channels and threads. 


We made a scheduled improvement to part of our infrastructure which inadvertently caused an increase in database load. Our automated recovery system intervened, balancing the load and resolving the issue for all affected customers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Slack System Status</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TS-2023-002]]></title>
        <id>https://tailscale.com/security-bulletins/#ts-2023-002/</id>
        <link href="https://tailscale.com/security-bulletins/#ts-2023-002/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-24T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Description: An issue in the Tailscale coordination server allowed nodes with expired node keys to continue communicating with other nodes in a tailnet.
What happened?
There was a flaw in Tailscale’s logic for expiring node keys. If the set of nodes that can connect in a tailnet (the netmap) didn’t have any changes, then expired node keys were not immediately removed from the netmap. The longest delay in removal was 19 days, from 2022-12-20 to 2023-01-09.
Who is affected?
All tailnets with nodes whose node keys expired prior to 2023-01-12 may have been affected. Admins of a tailnet can view nodes with expired node keys in the admin console.
What is the impact?
Connections between nodes could continue after a node key expired, both when the expired node key was the source or when it was the destination of a connection. Connections to nodes with expired node keys would only be possible if they met all of the following criteria:
The peer node was in the same tailnet as, or shared into a tailnet with the node with the expired node key;
The peer node and the node with the expired node key were allowed to connect based on the access rules in the tailnet policy file at the time of expiry of the node key;
The tailnet’s netmap, including access rules, nodes added or removed from the tailnet, or connectivity of nodes in the tailnet did not change since the node key expiry; and
Tailscale had not deployed a change to the coordination server since the node key expiry.
What do I need to do?
No action is required. Tailscale has deployed a fix to the coordination server as of 2023-01-11.
Upgrade clients to v1.36 or later for an additional mitigation. In conjunction with the coordination server fix, this mitigation prevents nodes from connecting to nodes with expired node keys if the Tailscale coordination server is offline or unreachable.
Credits
We would like to thank Derek Ellis and Alex Eiser for reporting this issue.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Security Bulletins on Tailscale</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[List your properties on maeva.com and get more bookings !]]></title>
        <id>255657</id>
        <link href="https://changelog.bookingsync.com/list-your-properties-on-maeva-com-and-get-more-bookings-!-255657"/>
        <updated>2023-01-23T09:36:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Partners
  
We are today happy to announce our new partnership with a big French company : maeva !
We have been working closely to the maeva team to offer a new direct integration to our Smily clients. Therefore, you can easily push your properties to the maeva websites and promote your listings to millions of French guests using this channel !

About maeva.com
maeva.com is a tour operator specialized in vacation rentals which promotes properties in leisure and tourist areas.
Acquired by the Pierre et Vacances group in 2001, maeva.com is now appreciated by French travelers for its general vacation rental site presenting more than 50,000 properties and having hosted more than 200,000 travelers in the summer of 2022.
Their offer was initially including tourist residences mainly but they now …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Audrey, Partnerships Development</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Notion page loading]]></title>
        <id>https://status.notion.so/incidents/kxnjf4xw20ty</id>
        <link href="https://status.notion.so/incidents/kxnjf4xw20ty"/>
        <updated>2023-01-20T00:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jan 19, 16:30 PST
Resolved - From approximately 4:45 PM to 6:00 PM Pacific time today, approximately 1% of users were unable to load Notion pages. This issue has been resolved and we are monitoring.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Notion Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident with Actions, Git Operations and Pages]]></title>
        <id>https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/n18j5g7wpg0s</id>
        <link href="https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/n18j5g7wpg0s"/>
        <updated>2023-01-19T20:51:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jan 19, 20:51 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Jan 19, 20:11 UTC
Update - We have applied a mitigation that has reduced impact to Actions, but error rates are still elevated. We continue to work with our dependency team on additional mitigations.
Jan 19, 19:31 UTC
Update - We are aware of an issue that impacts Actions, resulting in slow or failed jobs. Root cause in a dependency is understood and we are working with that team on a mitigation.
Jan 19, 18:49 UTC
Update - We are aware of an issue that impacts Actions, resulting in slow or failed jobs. Root cause in a dependency is understood and we are working with that team on a mitigation.
Jan 19, 18:07 UTC
Update - We are aware of an issue that impacts Actions, resulting in slow or failed jobs. Root cause in a dependency is understood and we are working with that team on a mitigation.
Jan 19, 17:27 UTC
Update - We are aware of an issue that impacts Actions artifact uploads and downloads, causing slow or failed jobs. We are investigating the root cause and will provide updates as we learn more.
Jan 19, 16:54 UTC
Update - We are observing an issue that impacts Actions artifact uploads and downloads, causing slow or failed jobs. We are investigating the root cause and will provide updates as we learn more.
Jan 19, 16:52 UTC
Update - Actions is experiencing degraded performance. We are continuing to investigate.
Jan 19, 16:49 UTC
Update - Git Operations is operating normally.
Jan 19, 16:09 UTC
Update - Pages is experiencing degraded performance. We are continuing to investigate.
Jan 19, 15:57 UTC
Investigating - We are investigating reports of degraded performance for Git Operations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GitHub Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident: Some customers may be missing channels and DMs in their sidebar]]></title>
        <id>https://status.slack.com//2023-01/e7a6c99fb49d6b09</id>
        <link href="https://status.slack.com//2023-01/e7a6c99fb49d6b09"/>
        <updated>2023-01-19T14:35:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Issue summary: 

From January 18th, 2023 7:45AM to 8:46PM PST some users experienced issues with missing channels and DMs in their sidebar. This affected only users of free teams.


This was due to a feature rollout which was rolled back and the issue is now resolved.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Slack System Status</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident with Actions and Pages]]></title>
        <id>https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/z2j6pjg527p6</id>
        <link href="https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/z2j6pjg527p6"/>
        <updated>2023-01-19T02:21:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jan 19, 02:21 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Jan 19, 01:54 UTC
Update - Actions is experiencing degraded performance. We are continuing to investigate.
Jan 19, 01:48 UTC
Investigating - We are investigating reports of degraded performance for Pages.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GitHub Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident with Copilot]]></title>
        <id>https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/tyk95n0z3pql</id>
        <link href="https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/tyk95n0z3pql"/>
        <updated>2023-01-18T20:16:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jan 18, 20:16 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Jan 18, 19:50 UTC
Update - We are investigating reports of issues with service(s): Copilot. We see authentication failures for a small percentage of users. We are investigating the root cause and will update as we learn more.
Jan 18, 19:00 UTC
Update - We are investigating reports of issues with service(s): Copilot. We see authentication failures for a small percentage of users. We are investigating the root cause and will update as we learn more.
Jan 18, 18:16 UTC
Investigating - We are investigating reports of degraded performance for Copilot.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GitHub Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Some users are receiving incorrect block and member limit warnings]]></title>
        <id>https://status.notion.so/incidents/g2jhynfpdlxj</id>
        <link href="https://status.notion.so/incidents/g2jhynfpdlxj"/>
        <updated>2023-01-18T01:25:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jan 17, 17:25 PST
Resolved - We have implemented a fix and confirmed the issue is resolved. Users should no longer be receiving incorrect member and block limit warnings. You may need to refresh Notion to see the fixed version.
Jan 17, 16:29 PST
Update - We are continuing to work on a fix for this issue.
Jan 17, 16:29 PST
Identified - There is currently an issue where some users are incorrectly receiving block and member limit warnings. We have identified the root cause and a fix is in progress.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Notion Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident: Users may experience issues accessing or loading Slack, have trouble creating posts, and using Workflow Builder.]]></title>
        <id>https://status.slack.com//2023-01/592b7776e9a7fdfa</id>
        <link href="https://status.slack.com//2023-01/592b7776e9a7fdfa"/>
        <updated>2023-01-17T23:06:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Issue summary:

From January 16th, 2023 04:59 to 08:38 AM PST, some users experienced issues creating Posts, using workflows, and trouble accessing Slack.  


We traced this back to an issue with our internal DNS configuration. Once this was identified and resolved, functionality was restored to all impacted users.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Slack System Status</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident: Some Android users may be experiencing issues when trying to access a workspace]]></title>
        <id>https://status.slack.com//2023-01/61694d1ccb108116</id>
        <link href="https://status.slack.com//2023-01/61694d1ccb108116"/>
        <updated>2023-01-17T09:55:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Issue summary:

From January 10th 04:11 AM PST to January 16th 07:54 PM PST, some of our fellow Slack colleagues were unable to access their workspaces on Android. We're happy to share that this issue was specifically related to our internal testing app, having no impact on the Slack production app nor our Customers.


This issue has been resolved and will have no impact on our future Android app releases.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Slack System Status</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TS-2023-001]]></title>
        <id>https://tailscale.com/security-bulletins/#ts-2023-001/</id>
        <link href="https://tailscale.com/security-bulletins/#ts-2023-001/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-17T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Description: An issue in the Tailscale coordination server allowed a malicious individual to share nodes from other tailnets to themselves, if they knew the node ID of the target.
What happened?
A bug in Tailscale’s node sharing logic allowed the creation of sharing invitations by unauthorized users. A malicious individual who knew a target node’s database ID could generate and accept a sharing invite for that node without being an admin of the target node’s tailnet.
This was possible for any node in any tailnet, as long as the individual knew the target’s node ID. The node ID is an integer used in the admin panel’s database, and is not related to the node “StableID” that is visible to Tailscale clients. A node’s ID is only visible in the API or admin console, by admins of either the node’s tailnet or a tailnet to which that node has already been shared. IDs are random 64-bit numbers that are not sequential or otherwise easily guessable.
The bug was introduced on 2022-09-14, reported to us on 2023-01-11, and remediated on 2023-01-12.
Who is affected?
All tailnets with nodes are affected.
What is the impact?
This vulnerability was not triggered or exploited. Analysis of tailnet logs shows that no unauthorized shares were created or accepted while the vulnerability was present, except as part of the proof of concept from the individual who reported the vulnerability.
Admins of a tailnet can review nodes that are shared out of their tailnet in the admin console. Sharing invites are logged as events in configuration audit logs. Admins can also review invites created and accepted in their configuration audit logs in the admin console.
What do I need to do?
No action is required. Tailscale has deployed a fix to the coordination server as of 2023-01-12, and verified that the vulnerability was not exploited.
Credits
We would like to thank Benjamin Roberts (tsujamin) for reporting this issue.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Security Bulletins on Tailscale</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Servers down]]></title>
        <id>https://status.notion.so/incidents/l3glrt4dhc6p</id>
        <link href="https://status.notion.so/incidents/l3glrt4dhc6p"/>
        <updated>2023-01-16T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jan 16, 09:00 PST
Resolved - Notion was down between 8:56 - 9:12 AM PT. Service is now recovered.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Notion Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident with Actions]]></title>
        <id>https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/f3kthhhjt9ss</id>
        <link href="https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/f3kthhhjt9ss"/>
        <updated>2023-01-16T16:43:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jan 16, 16:43 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Jan 16, 16:31 UTC
Update - We found an issue that caused high database replication lag, leading to issues visible in multiple services. We have resolved this issue and are expecting services to become healthy once queues drain.
Jan 16, 15:51 UTC
Investigating - We are investigating reports of degraded performance for Actions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GitHub Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident: Some customers may be unable to complete SSO configuration]]></title>
        <id>https://status.slack.com//2023-01/86830b419c5578aa</id>
        <link href="https://status.slack.com//2023-01/86830b419c5578aa"/>
        <updated>2023-01-16T09:47:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Issue summary:

From January 6th at 8:42 AM PST to January 15th at 10:00 PM PST, some users were running into issues when completing their SSO configuration. In the SSO settings the "Test Configuration" button led to an error message page.


We identified a recent code change as the cause of the issue and a fix was launched to correct it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Slack System Status</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident with Codespaces]]></title>
        <id>https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/hzgtxb033mym</id>
        <link href="https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/hzgtxb033mym"/>
        <updated>2023-01-14T16:58:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jan 14, 16:58 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Jan 14, 16:09 UTC
Update - We are investigating issues with Codespaces port forwarding. Users may be able to use the desktop client as a workaround.
Jan 14, 15:13 UTC
Investigating - We are investigating reports of degraded performance for Codespaces.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GitHub Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident with Copilot]]></title>
        <id>https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/n6wxc7xwrk1z</id>
        <link href="https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/n6wxc7xwrk1z"/>
        <updated>2023-01-12T04:55:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jan 12, 04:55 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Jan 12, 04:51 UTC
Update - Some Copilot plans were impacted by a recent backend change causing those users to see an error that access has ended.  We have applied a change to correct this and are seeing full recovery.
Jan 12, 03:59 UTC
Investigating - We are investigating reports of degraded performance for Copilot.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GitHub Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Make intermittent login issues]]></title>
        <id>https://status.make.com/incidents/0zz20hbhy112</id>
        <link href="https://status.make.com/incidents/0zz20hbhy112"/>
        <updated>2023-01-11T16:36:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jan 11, 17:36 CET
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Jan 11, 12:00 CET
Monitoring - The root cause of the issue has been identified and a remedy is already in place . Some users might have experienced troubles with logging in to the platform whilst we can confirm that there was no impact on running scenarios . We are actively monitoring the situation .
Jan 11, 11:37 CET
Investigating - We are currently experiencing intermittent issues when logging in to make zones . We are actively investigating the issue and working on a solution.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Make Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident with Actions and Git Operations]]></title>
        <id>https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/00km0kwpz23b</id>
        <link href="https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/00km0kwpz23b"/>
        <updated>2023-01-10T18:14:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jan 10, 18:14 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Jan 10, 17:54 UTC
Update - Some action hosted runners are experiencing longer than normal run times.
Jan 10, 17:22 UTC
Update - Actions is experiencing degraded performance. We are still investigating and will provide an update when we have one.
Jan 10, 17:04 UTC
Investigating - We are investigating reports of degraded performance for Git Operations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GitHub Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[500 Errors Across Multiple Endpoints]]></title>
        <id>https://airbnbapi.statuspage.io/incidents/dz7fk8vqftbf</id>
        <link href="https://airbnbapi.statuspage.io/incidents/dz7fk8vqftbf"/>
        <updated>2023-01-09T23:10:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jan  9, 15:10 PST
Resolved - From 14:00-15:00 Pacific Time (PT), we saw increased 500 errors for multiple API endpoints, including reservations, listings and threads. The issue is now identified and resolved, please retry any failed requests during this time. Apologies for the inconvenience caused due to this incident and thank you for your patience and understanding.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Airbnb API Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>