<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2022-10-01T00:39:42.086Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2022-10-01T00:39:42.086Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DDoS attack mitigated]]></title>
        <id>https://status.make.com/incidents/hvlj74k8s60q</id>
        <link href="https://status.make.com/incidents/hvlj74k8s60q"/>
        <updated>2022-09-29T09:41:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sep 29, 11:41 CEST
Update - Due to the DDoS attack, Make servers were unable to receive some webhook requests from our customers and as a result, such data couldn't be delivered to scenarios. In some instances data was redelivered at a later point, but in order to be sure, we advise that you reload any data from the app-list below that was uploaded during the following time frames (times shown in CET):
26.9.2022 18:00 - 27.9.2022 15:20
27.9.2022 19:20 - 27.9.2022 23:50
Our investigation revealed webhooks coming from those apps were affected:
Slack, Zoom, Facebook Lead Ads, Intercom, Segment, Todoist, Quickbooks, Square, Instagram, and Box
Sep 28, 15:22 CEST
Monitoring - A fix has been implemented and the service is now stable. The team continues to monitor and proactively manage any potent…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Make Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident: Issues downloading files on Slack Android app version 22.09.30]]></title>
        <id>https://status.slack.com//2022-09/1858cb1fccf03b42</id>
        <link href="https://status.slack.com//2022-09/1858cb1fccf03b42"/>
        <updated>2022-09-28T22:57:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Issue summary:


Starting September 21st around 1:00 PM PDT until September 28th 3:00 PM PDT, users experienced trouble downloading files on Slack's Android app version: 22.09.30. We traced the problem to a permissions check error which caused file downloads to not execute.


We corrected the permissions check error in the latest version of the Android app: 22.09.40, and the file download functionality was restored. Some impacted users may need to update their Slack app to version 22.09.40 from the Google Play Store.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Slack System Status</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Issue Affecting Reservation Related Webhooks]]></title>
        <id>https://airbnbapi.statuspage.io/incidents/xjrh0byz8tlt</id>
        <link href="https://airbnbapi.statuspage.io/incidents/xjrh0byz8tlt"/>
        <updated>2022-09-28T22:36:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sep 28, 15:36 PDT
Resolved - This incident was resolved on September 21st at 1:00 p.m. PDT. If you still see reservations missing webhook notifications, don't hesitate to reach back out.
Sep 21, 14:46 PDT
Update - We are actively working to find a solution to this issue. In the meantime, we have backfilled all the missed reservation webhook notifications since September 15. We will post more updates as soon as we have them.
Sep 21, 10:51 PDT
Identified - We have identified an issue affecting the sending of reservation related webhooks starting on September 15th, we are actively working on it and will post more updates when we have them. This incident does not affect all reservations, only a limited number of them. If you notice that some of your Hosts' reservations webhooks are missing, for example when you accept a make_reservation SAC, but you did not receive a confirmation webhook afterwards, use the GET reservations API to retrieve the reservation status.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Airbnb API Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS service degradation affecting Notion integrations]]></title>
        <id>https://status.notion.so/incidents/k8c9l3h1s7kj</id>
        <link href="https://status.notion.so/incidents/k8c9l3h1s7kj"/>
        <updated>2022-09-28T21:42:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sep 28, 14:42 PDT
Resolved - The AWS issue has been resolved, and external integrations in Notion affecting link previews and database syncs are functioning normally again.
Sep 28, 10:58 PDT
Identified - An AWS service degradation has resulted in users unable to authenticate external integrations in Notion, affecting link previews and database syncs. We are investigating potential mitigations while AWS works to resolve the issue.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Notion Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident: Some Enterprise Grid users are unable to retrieve channel lists when building workflows and webhooks]]></title>
        <id>https://status.slack.com//2022-09/0555cbd5e9833fe3</id>
        <link href="https://status.slack.com//2022-09/0555cbd5e9833fe3"/>
        <updated>2022-09-28T20:10:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Issue summary:

From September 26, 2022 at 7:00 AM PDT until September 27, 2022 at 12:40 PM PDT, some Enterprise Grid users were not able to create new webhooks, share posts to a channel, or select a channel from the dropdown menu in Workflow Builder. We traced this problem to a change that was made to improve how channel objects are loaded into Slack. We disabled this change, restoring functionality to impacted users.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Slack System Status</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident with Codespaces]]></title>
        <id>https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/m574010k9c5l</id>
        <link href="https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/m574010k9c5l"/>
        <updated>2022-09-28T19:56:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sep 28, 19:56 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Sep 28, 19:29 UTC
Update - We are investigating issues with Codespaces in eu-west region. The origin issue is resolved, however customers may experience delays in creation and resumption as we process the backlog of requests.
Sep 28, 18:52 UTC
Update - Codespaces is now experiencing degraded performance. We are still investigating and will provide an update when we have one.
Sep 28, 18:35 UTC
Update - We are investigating issues with Codespaces in all regions due to VMs not coming online. We have applied a mitigation that resolved the underlying issue, and we are processing the backlog of requests.
Sep 28, 17:56 UTC
Update - We are investigating reports of issues with Codespaces in eu-west and se-asia regions. Users may not be able to connect to Codespaces during this time. We will update on progress towards mitigation.
Sep 28, 17:22 UTC
Investigating - We are investigating reports of degraded availability for Codespaces.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GitHub Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident with Codespaces]]></title>
        <id>https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/w29zg5h2chkp</id>
        <link href="https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/w29zg5h2chkp"/>
        <updated>2022-09-28T05:09:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sep 28, 05:09 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Sep 28, 04:42 UTC
Update - We have identified an issue that impacts port forwarding in the Codespaces web client. We are working on mitigation. As a workaround, you can use VS Code Desktop.
Sep 28, 03:53 UTC
Investigating - We are investigating reports of degraded performance for Codespaces.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GitHub Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Droplet Creation in AMS3]]></title>
        <id>https://status.digitalocean.com/incidents/089vkllnb4gw</id>
        <link href="https://status.digitalocean.com/incidents/089vkllnb4gw"/>
        <updated>2022-09-27T20:45:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sep 27, 20:45 UTC
Resolved - As of 19:32 UTC we have confirmed the issue with creation of Droplets and Droplet-based products is fully resolved. Thank you for your patience. If you continue to experience any problems, please open a support ticket from within your account.
Sep 27, 19:46 UTC
Monitoring - Our Engineering team identified the root cause and implemented a fix to resolve the issue with Droplet creation in our AMS3 region. Users should now be able to create Droplets and Droplet-based services in the region. We are monitoring the situation closely and will post an update once the matter is completely resolved.
Sep 27, 19:31 UTC
Investigating - Our Engineering team is investigating an issue with Droplet creation in our AMS3 region. As of 19:15 UTC, users may see latency or errors when creating Droplets and Droplet-based services like Load Balancers, Managed Databases, and Kubernetes clusters, via both our Cloud Control Panel and API. We will provide an update as soon as possible.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>DigitalOcean Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident: Issues with legacy message attachments]]></title>
        <id>https://status.slack.com//2022-09/ca18055bcf82c232</id>
        <link href="https://status.slack.com//2022-09/ca18055bcf82c232"/>
        <updated>2022-09-27T19:09:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Issue summary:


On September 26, 2022 from 12:00 PM PDT to 11:48 PM PDT, link formatting was broken for all Slack apps.


Some messages were showing the URL and not a link itself. We determined that this issue was caused by a recent code change that altered how attachment links in the app were formatted.


We reverted this change which fixed the issue for all users after a force reload of Slack.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Slack System Status</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident with Actions]]></title>
        <id>https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/nbhb2lxyh9bb</id>
        <link href="https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/nbhb2lxyh9bb"/>
        <updated>2022-09-27T15:06:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sep 27, 15:06 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Sep 27, 15:00 UTC
Update - We've applied a mitigation to resolve delayed job updates for running Actions.
Sep 27, 14:33 UTC
Investigating - We are investigating reports of degraded performance for Actions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GitHub Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Droplet Console for New Droplets]]></title>
        <id>https://status.digitalocean.com/incidents/70pbywnkt5fp</id>
        <link href="https://status.digitalocean.com/incidents/70pbywnkt5fp"/>
        <updated>2022-09-27T01:59:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sep 27, 01:59 UTC
Resolved - Our engineering team has fully resolved the issue with console access for new Droplets. If you continue to experience problems, please open a ticket with our support team. We apologize for any inconvenience.
Sep 27, 01:39 UTC
Monitoring - Our Engineering team has implemented a fix to resolve the issue with Droplet console access for new Debian and Ubuntu Droplets. New Droplets will now be able to access the console normally. 
No action is needed to restore console access for Droplets created during this incident. 
If you continue to see issues, please contact our support team for assistance.
Sep 27, 00:42 UTC
Investigating - Our Engineering team is investigating an issue with Droplet console access for new Debian and Ubuntu Droplets. 
Any new Droplets created using Debian or Ubuntu operating systems will not have access to the Droplet console. This impacts only the standard Droplet console - the recovery console will still function normally.  
We apologize for the inconvenience and will share an update once we have more information.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>DigitalOcean Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident: Some customers may not be receiving notifications via the Salesforce for Slack app.]]></title>
        <id>https://status.slack.com//2022-09/5c0916c535d67cec</id>
        <link href="https://status.slack.com//2022-09/5c0916c535d67cec"/>
        <updated>2022-09-26T19:57:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We have rolled out a fix and notifications via Salesforce for Slack app should be now working as expected. We appreciate your patience.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Slack System Status</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RESOLVED: We're experiencing an issue affecting less than an estimated 30% of the Google Workspace Support user base. We will provide an update by Sep 16, 2022, 8:00 PM UTC detailing when we expect to resolve the problem. Please note that this resolution time is an estimate and may change. The affected users are able to access Google Workspace Support, but are seeing error messages, high latency, and/or other unexpected behavior.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.google.com/appsstatus/dashboard/incidents/qNcKhzaPQskm45XZZUqG</id>
        <link href="https://www.google.com/appsstatus/dashboard/incidents/qNcKhzaPQskm45XZZUqG"/>
        <updated>2022-09-23T23:02:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p> Incident began at <strong>2022-09-16 17:23</strong> and ended at <strong>2022-09-17 00:27</strong> <span>(times are in <strong>Coordinated Universal Time (UTC)</strong>).</span></p><div class="cBIRi14aVDP__status-update-text"><h2>Full Incident Report</h2>
<p><strong>SUMMARY:</strong></p>
<p>On Friday, 16 September at 10:23 US/Pacific, Cloud Support Systems, which utilizes a 3rd party product, experienced row-lock errors while updating cases. This preventedSupport agents from being able to update or make changes to some Support cases. Additionally, the send email to customers action was unavailable for some Support cases. Some customers may have seen an error when updating cases from the customer portal. As a workaround, customers and Support agents could successfully update their cases by retrying the action. The issue was mitigated at 17:27 US/Pacific and service was fully restored for both the Support agents and customers. The total duration of the service disruption was 7 hours and 4 minutes.</p>
<p><strong>ROOT CAUSE:</strong></p>
<p>Cloud Support Systems experienced a large backlog of case field update actions pending in the SLO timed actions queue. These timed actions were running in large batches, with updates running in the queue every few minutes. This caused the cases to be locked down from any other update actions while that job was running.</p>
<p>This backlog was caused by the following:</p>
<ul>
<li>There was an increase in the limit of cases being processed every hour by the SLO time queue job.</li>
<li>There was a rollback issue with the 3rd party product while processing time based tasks which caused multiple processing requests of the same tasks.</li>
<li>There was a configuration in the case trigger which created a backlog on large batches which triggered the above bug with the 3rd party product.</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>REMEDIATION AND PREVENTION:</strong></p>
<p>Our engineers were alerted to the issue by an internal support agent&#39;s case on Monday, 12 September 2022. Engineering began investigating and working on a solution. On Tuesday, September 13 there was one report of external impact. The issue progressed and impact became visible externally on Friday, 16 September 2022 at 10:23 US/Pacific, and the row lock issue was confirmed to have widespread external impact. Once the nature and scope of the issue became clear, Google engineers filed a case with the 3rd party product support to address the issue with Cloud Systems. The  backlog actions were purged manually using the 3rd party setup UI which brought the backlog in the queue down by 80%, the issue was completely resolved for the end user on Friday, 16 September at 17:27 US/Pacific.</p>
<p>Google is committed to preventing recurrence by implementing the following action items:</p>
<ul>
<li>Implement a code enhancement with the 3rd party vendor to confirm the error handling code which triggered the issue is fixed.</li>
</ul>
</div><hr><p>Affected products: Google Workspace Support</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Workspace Status Dashboard Updates</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Issue with device actions completing on Mac computers]]></title>
        <id>https://status.rippling.com/incidents/zwvh0cbvpd5c</id>
        <link href="https://status.rippling.com/incidents/zwvh0cbvpd5c"/>
        <updated>2022-09-23T22:00:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sep 23, 22:00 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Sep 23, 18:24 UTC
Identified - The issue has been identified and a fix is being implemented.
Sep 23, 16:43 UTC
Investigating - We are currently investigating this issue.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rippling Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident with Issues and Pull Requests]]></title>
        <id>https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/2n0tnk7tt6q9</id>
        <link href="https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/2n0tnk7tt6q9"/>
        <updated>2022-09-22T22:23:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sep 22, 22:23 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Sep 22, 19:44 UTC
Update - Pull Requests is experiencing degraded performance. We are continuing to investigate.
Sep 22, 19:04 UTC
Investigating - We are investigating reports of degraded performance for Issues.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GitHub Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smily was in Porto at VRWS ! :)]]></title>
        <id>244856</id>
        <link href="https://changelog.bookingsync.com/smily-was-in-porto-at-vrws-!-)-244856"/>
        <updated>2022-09-22T14:52:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Partners
  
As you may know, we were pleased to participate in the Vacation Rental World Summit in Porto last week as a Gold Sponsor !
This was the 6th edition of this event, which is becoming increasingly popular each year.
It provides an opportunity for us to meet our partners and customers. We are also always happy and curious to get to know new players in our amazing industry.
These shared moments exchanging with lots of different actors allow us to stay informed about trends and activity in the vacation rental industry.

This year again, this event dedicated to vacation rentals has boosted our collaboration with, among others, our official partners!
At Smily, the quality of our partnerships matters a lot. We want to offer our customers the smoothest integrations and the best assistance we can, from us and from our partners.
We thank our partners who were present at VRWS a lot for the quality of our discussions and their enthusiasm towards our collaboration! :)
Airbnb - Channel


Beyond - Pricing tool


Booking.com- Channel


Breezeway - Tasks manager


Chekin - Check-ins automation


ENSO connect - Guest communication


Duve - Guest experience


Holidu - Channel


Hometogo - Channel


Igloohome - Smartlocks


Keydata - Data provider


Nuki- Smartlocks


PriceLabs - Pricing tool


Superhog - Check-ins automation


Swikly - Deposit management


TouchStay - Welcome Book


Transparent - Data provider


VRBO - Channel


Yaago - Guest experience


Don't hesitate to contact our support team if you would like more information about any of these partners. We would love you to benefit from the great things we have to come with all of them :)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Audrey, Partnerships Development</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scheduled infrastructure maintenance]]></title>
        <id>https://status.make.com/incidents/wq984gqy4lwc</id>
        <link href="https://status.make.com/incidents/wq984gqy4lwc"/>
        <updated>2022-09-21T05:30:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sep 21, 07:30 CEST
Completed - The scheduled maintenance has been completed.
Sep 21, 05:00 CEST
In progress - Scheduled maintenance is currently in progress. We will provide updates as necessary.
Sep 13, 16:58 CEST
Scheduled - Please note that we will be undergoing scheduled infrastructure maintenance on Wednesday September 21st between 05:00 AM and 07:00 AM CEST on eu1.make.celonis.com and eu1.make.com. During this maintenance you can expect few short service interruptions.
During the maintenance the eu1.make.celonis.com and eu1.make.com website login might be temporarily affected.
Some webhooks and shared hooks processed at that time might be temporarily affected as well.
There will be no impact on us1.make.com and us1.make.celonis.com.
We do not expect any data loss.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Make Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An update from GitHub]]></title>
        <id>https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/v5bcd4pzckky</id>
        <link href="https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/v5bcd4pzckky"/>
        <updated>2022-09-20T14:15:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sep 20, 14:15 UTC
Resolved - Audit log API is operating normally
Sep 20, 12:10 UTC
Investigating - Audit log REST API requests for organizations are currently disabled. We are actively investigating and working on a fix.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GitHub Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scheduled infrastructure maintenance]]></title>
        <id>https://status.make.com/incidents/sjxjlyjy4b7c</id>
        <link href="https://status.make.com/incidents/sjxjlyjy4b7c"/>
        <updated>2022-09-20T10:00:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sep 20, 12:00 CEST
Completed - The scheduled maintenance has been completed.
Sep 20, 10:00 CEST
In progress - Scheduled maintenance is currently in progress. We will provide updates as necessary.
Sep 13, 16:51 CEST
Scheduled - Please note that we will be undergoing scheduled infrastructure maintenance on Tuesday September 20th between 10:00 AM and 12:00 PM CEST on us1.make.celonis.com and us1.make.com. During this maintenance you can expect few short service interruptions.
During the maintenance the us1.make.celonis.com and us1.make.com website login might be temporarily affected.
Some webhooks and shared hooks processed at that time might be temporarily affected as well.
There will be no impact on eu1.make.com and eu1.make.celonis.com.
We do not expect any data loss.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Make Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wordpress plugin - temporary not available]]></title>
        <id>https://status.make.com/incidents/v21whxj91l62</id>
        <link href="https://status.make.com/incidents/v21whxj91l62"/>
        <updated>2022-09-20T09:22:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sep 20, 11:22 CEST
Resolved - This incident was resolved. Plugin is live once again!
Sep  5, 10:45 CEST
Monitoring - Hello, we are having issues with Wordpress plugin. The issue is being worked on and will be resolved shortly once Wordpress approves our plugin currently being under review process.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Make Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident with Actions]]></title>
        <id>https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/6mdt263cpf9q</id>
        <link href="https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/6mdt263cpf9q"/>
        <updated>2022-09-20T08:04:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sep 20, 08:04 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Sep 20, 08:03 UTC
Investigating - We are investigating reports of degraded performance for Actions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GitHub Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Calendar interface!]]></title>
        <id>244470</id>
        <link href="https://changelog.bookingsync.com/new-calendar-interface!-244470"/>
        <updated>2022-09-19T16:00:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New!
  
Good News!
At Smily, we are here to help you to Save time and Book more. That's why we are always thrilled to announce more and more features.
This time the new feature concerns your calendar. After many years of loyal service and in response to many requests, we have overhauled the calendar interface, for aesthetic reasons, of course, but above all to make it more efficient and more intuitive for you.
What are the main changes?
First of all, we are aware that the calendar is your main tool for managing your bookings. So, to ensure a smooth transition, for the moment we have maintained the old calendar view, so that you can switch easily from one to another.
1- Two different views: Planning and Month
We separated the planning and the month views into 2 different sections to have a …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Zahra, Product manager, PMS team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Network Connectivity in LON1]]></title>
        <id>https://status.digitalocean.com/incidents/jznrv97h9dsw</id>
        <link href="https://status.digitalocean.com/incidents/jznrv97h9dsw"/>
        <updated>2022-09-16T00:17:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sep 16, 00:17 UTC
Resolved - Our engineering team has resolved the issue with networking in LON1, and should now be operating normally. If you continue to experience problems, please open a ticket with our support team. We apologize for any inconvenience.
Sep 15, 23:36 UTC
Monitoring - Our Engineering team has identified the root cause of the networking issues in LON1. We are monitoring the situation and will post an update once we confirm this incident is fully resolved.
Sep 15, 22:16 UTC
Identified - Our Engineering team has identified the source of connectivity issues in our LON1 region, and is working on a fix to mitigate the impact.
Users may be experiencing packet loss/latency, timeouts, and related issues with Droplet-based services in LON1, including Droplets, Managed Kubernetes, and Database clusters.
Sep 15, 22:01 UTC
Investigating - Our Engineering team is investigating reports of networking connectivity issues in our LON1 region. Users have reported packet loss/latency and connectivity errors to resources. We will share an update once we have further information.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>DigitalOcean Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rippling Devices web application is not confirming the creation of user accounts and not sending temporary passwords]]></title>
        <id>https://status.rippling.com/incidents/6ks7txt5h14x</id>
        <link href="https://status.rippling.com/incidents/6ks7txt5h14x"/>
        <updated>2022-09-16T00:00:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sep 16, 00:00 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Sep 15, 22:45 UTC
Monitoring - A fix has been deployed and is being rolled out.  Please expect the fix to be available to all computers by 6pm PST, some computers may receive the fix earlier.
Sep 15, 20:17 UTC
Identified - The issue has been identified and a fix is being implemented.
Sep 15, 19:52 UTC
Investigating - We are currently investigating this issue.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rippling Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident: Spreadsheet data added using workflows may be incorrect]]></title>
        <id>https://status.slack.com//2022-09/c3bf22ba48b2930b</id>
        <link href="https://status.slack.com//2022-09/c3bf22ba48b2930b"/>
        <updated>2022-09-15T17:32:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Issue summary:


Starting September 6th, 2022, we identified an issue with the Google Sheet app inside Workflow Builder. This issue caused the app to read the spreadsheet date/time format wrong, inserting the incorrect time value in the timestamp.


We discovered this was due to the app processing the workflow step with a single digit value instead of a double digit value.


Users can continue highlighting the Submission Time column in the spreadsheet and select Format → Number → Custom Number Format and insert: ddd mmm yyyy hh:mm:ss, as a workaround.


We will work to fix this through a bug ticket that has been filed as a result of this incident. Though we have not resolved this issue yet, we will provide further updates through customer support tickets with the impacted users.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Slack System Status</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Delay with Event Processing in All Regions]]></title>
        <id>https://status.digitalocean.com/incidents/g4wkfk7jxx6m</id>
        <link href="https://status.digitalocean.com/incidents/g4wkfk7jxx6m"/>
        <updated>2022-09-15T15:55:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sep 15, 15:55 UTC
Resolved - From 13:50 - 14:50 UTC, our Engineering team observed issues with event processing in all regions. During this time, users may have experienced delays or failures when attempting to process events, such as creation, deletion, resizing, assigning of Reserved IP's, Snapshots, and other Droplet-based events.
Our Engineering team has resolved the issue. As of 14:50 UTC, events should not be delayed and should be successful.  We apologize for the inconvenience. If you are still experiencing any problems or have additional questions, please open a support ticket within your account.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>DigitalOcean Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Issue Setting PASS_THROUGH_CLEANING_FEE on Pricing Settings Standard Fees Array]]></title>
        <id>https://airbnbapi.statuspage.io/incidents/cvjp3lxj20n0</id>
        <link href="https://airbnbapi.statuspage.io/incidents/cvjp3lxj20n0"/>
        <updated>2022-09-15T09:38:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sep 15, 02:38 PDT
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Please retry the PUT pricing_settings requests with the desired Standard Fees if you have not already done so.
If you have any further queries related to this incident, please submit a ticket via the Partner Support Portal and our team will get back to you as soon as possible.
Apologies for the inconvenience caused and thank you for your understanding.
Sep 14, 22:39 PDT
Monitoring - Please attempt to retry the PUT pricing_settings requests with the desired Standard Fees.
This should re-populate the listings' Standard Fees array as intended, namely the PASS_THROUGH_CLEANING_FEE fee.
We are monitoring the situation.
Sep 14, 22:38 PDT
Identified - The issue has been identified and mitigated.
Please attempt to send a PUT pricing_settings request with the desired Standard Fees as required.
This should re-populate the listings' Standard Fees array as intended.
Sep 14, 20:45 PDT
Investigating - We are currently investigating reports where the PASS_THROUGH_CLEANING_FEE standard fee is not being able to be set via the Pricing Settings API.
We will provide updates as soon as we can. We apologise for the inconvenience caused.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Airbnb API Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident: Some users might have trouble with posts]]></title>
        <id>https://status.slack.com//2022-09/29f29ddbaf35791a</id>
        <link href="https://status.slack.com//2022-09/29f29ddbaf35791a"/>
        <updated>2022-09-15T00:42:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Thank you for your patience while we were working on this. For now, we will track this internally as a bug while we continue to find resolution. If you’re still experiencing this behaviour, please reach out to us at feedback@slack.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Slack System Status</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Network Connectivity in LON1]]></title>
        <id>https://status.digitalocean.com/incidents/yhz9frgy4ngl</id>
        <link href="https://status.digitalocean.com/incidents/yhz9frgy4ngl"/>
        <updated>2022-09-14T20:46:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sep 14, 20:46 UTC
Resolved - Our engineering team has resolved the issue with LON1 network connectivity, and should now be operating normally. If you continue to experience problems, please open a ticket with our support team. We apologize for any inconvenience.
Sep 14, 18:54 UTC
Monitoring - Our Engineering team has deployed a fix to resolve the issues with network connectivity in our LON1 region. At this time, users should be seeing the restoration of network connectivity to and from the resources in LON1. We are monitoring the situation and will post an update as soon as we confirm the issue is fully resolved.
Sep 14, 17:54 UTC
Identified - Our Engineering team has investigated reports of connectivity issues beginning around 15:40 UTC in our LON1 region and has taken action to mitigate the impact. 
Users may have experienced packet loss/latency, timeouts, and related issues with Droplet-based services in LON1, including Droplets, Managed Kubernetes, and Database clusters. 
We are seeing some recovery after taking action and are continuing to investigate and monitor the situation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>DigitalOcean Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident on 2022-09-13]]></title>
        <id>https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/8blgv351d71j</id>
        <link href="https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/8blgv351d71j"/>
        <updated>2022-09-14T18:05:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sep 14, 18:05 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Sep 13, 15:57 UTC
Investigating - We are investigating and mitigating intermittent availability issues on some GitHub services.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GitHub Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident: Direct Messages with three or more people are missing from the Direct Message list for all workspaces]]></title>
        <id>https://status.slack.com//2022-09/abdf34f4cfab096e</id>
        <link href="https://status.slack.com//2022-09/abdf34f4cfab096e"/>
        <updated>2022-09-14T06:21:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Issue summary:


On September 13, 2022 from 10:33 AM PDT to 3:21 PM PDT, some customers were unable to see group direct messages in their sidebars due to a recent update. Reverting the update fixed the issue for all affected customers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Slack System Status</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident with Issues]]></title>
        <id>https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/3z36qpp2c0z1</id>
        <link href="https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/3z36qpp2c0z1"/>
        <updated>2022-09-13T16:08:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sep 13, 16:08 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Sep 13, 15:10 UTC
Investigating - We are investigating reports of degraded performance for Issues.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GitHub Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Server Errors On Attempt to API-connect Listings]]></title>
        <id>https://airbnbapi.statuspage.io/incidents/8l22crftlsb3</id>
        <link href="https://airbnbapi.statuspage.io/incidents/8l22crftlsb3"/>
        <updated>2022-09-13T04:09:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sep 12, 21:09 PDT
Resolved - Some Partners may have encountered 500 Errors on the Listings API when attempting to API-connect listings to their applications earlier today.
We have identified the cause for which a fix has already been implemented. We are not expecting any further errors of such.
Thank you for your understanding and apologies for any inconvenience caused!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Airbnb API Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scheduled infrastructure maintenance]]></title>
        <id>https://status.make.com/incidents/cycp8kwzzx7q</id>
        <link href="https://status.make.com/incidents/cycp8kwzzx7q"/>
        <updated>2022-09-13T04:00:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sep 13, 06:00 CEST
Completed - The scheduled maintenance has been completed.
Sep 13, 05:00 CEST
In progress - Scheduled maintenance is currently in progress. We will provide updates as necessary.
Sep  7, 16:12 CEST
Scheduled - Please note there is scheduled infrastructure maintenance on Tuesday 13th of September, between 5 AM and 6 AM CEST, when you can expect few short service interruptions. During this maintenance following services will be affected:
- Migrations will not be available
- Shared hooks created within maintenance will not be accepted nor processed
- Logins to platform might be affected
- Registration of new subscribers won’t be possible
- Invitations of new team members won’t be possible
- E-mails and notifications might be delayed
- Password reset won’t be possible
- Payments for subscription plans won’t be accepted  
We will inform you once the maintenance is completed.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Make Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident with Pull Requests]]></title>
        <id>https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/p38y9j23bt7b</id>
        <link href="https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/p38y9j23bt7b"/>
        <updated>2022-09-09T01:12:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sep  9, 01:12 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Sep  9, 00:53 UTC
Update - Mitigation efforts are continuing and we are seeing signs of recovery for some affected users.
Sep  8, 23:41 UTC
Update - We are continuing to mitigate the issue impacting some of our customers.
Sep  8, 22:10 UTC
Update - We have identified the source of the issue impacting some of our customers. We continue to mitigate the issue.
Sep  8, 21:04 UTC
Update - We found an issue that impacts some customers. We are working on a mitigation.
Sep  8, 19:44 UTC
Investigating - We are investigating reports of degraded performance for Pull Requests.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GitHub Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident: Windows Store app users may experience an error when launching Slack]]></title>
        <id>https://status.slack.com//2022-09/f4273fe54d4adbcb</id>
        <link href="https://status.slack.com//2022-09/f4273fe54d4adbcb"/>
        <updated>2022-09-08T22:09:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Issue summary:

On September 1st, 2022 from around 6:28 am to September 7th, 2022 around 3:00 pm PDT, some users on the Slack desktop app version 4.28.171 installed via the Windows Store were receiving an error when attempting to connect to Slack. 


We determined the cached information typically used to launch the app became corrupted, and subsequently caused the app to not load through a network request, prompting an error instead of re-trying the connection. We then launched a fix that allowed the app to re-attempt a network request, which solved the issue.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Slack System Status</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident: Some users may experience issues drafting a message that contains a link/hyperlink]]></title>
        <id>https://status.slack.com//2022-09/80573d91231d5ea0</id>
        <link href="https://status.slack.com//2022-09/80573d91231d5ea0"/>
        <updated>2022-09-08T19:46:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Issue summary:

On September 8th, 2022 from around 6:44 AM to 7:10 AM PDT some users on desktop clients experienced issues with drafting their messages and saw unexpected character replacements when links with quotes were used. This was caused by an update that was launched and reverting it fixed the issue for all affected users.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Slack System Status</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident on 2022-09-07 15:04 UTC]]></title>
        <id>https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/pz0bvrjx9ztp</id>
        <link href="https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/pz0bvrjx9ztp"/>
        <updated>2022-09-08T00:00:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sep  8, 00:00 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Sep  7, 15:04 UTC
Investigating - We are investigating and mitigating intermittent availability issues on some GitHub services.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GitHub Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mongo Managed Databases Creation]]></title>
        <id>https://status.digitalocean.com/incidents/lm2sv23vw0bx</id>
        <link href="https://status.digitalocean.com/incidents/lm2sv23vw0bx"/>
        <updated>2022-09-07T20:49:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sep  7, 20:49 UTC
Resolved - Our Engineering team has confirmed that the issue affecting the creation of Mongo Managed Database clusters has been fully resolved. We appreciate your patience throughout the process and if you continue to experience problems, please open a ticket with our support team for further review.
Sep  7, 20:27 UTC
Monitoring - Our Engineering team has identified the root cause of the issue with creation of Mongo Managed Database clusters and a fix has been deployed as of 20:07 UTC. We are monitoring the situation and will post an update once we confirm this incident is fully resolved.
Sep  7, 19:50 UTC
Investigating - Our Engineering team is investigating an issue with creation of Mongo Managed Database clusters. At this time, users may experience errors in creating clusters, both via Cloud Control Panel and API requests.
We apologize for the inconvenience and will share an update once we have more information.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>DigitalOcean Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Container Registry Errors]]></title>
        <id>https://status.digitalocean.com/incidents/hq7fylkxs9f3</id>
        <link href="https://status.digitalocean.com/incidents/hq7fylkxs9f3"/>
        <updated>2022-09-07T20:30:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sep  7, 20:30 UTC
Resolved - Our engineering team has confirmed that the issue affecting DigitalOcean Container Registry has been fully resolved. We appreciate your patience throughout the process and if you continue to experience problems, please open a ticket with our support team for further review.
Sep  7, 19:55 UTC
Monitoring - As of 19:18 UTC, our Engineering team has implemented a fix to resolve the issue with DigitalOcean Container Registry. Users should no longer experience errors while interacting and authenticating with the DigitalOcean Container Registry, creating new container registries, and pushing/deleting images to/from registries.
App Platform builds should now be succeeding. 
During this time users may have experienced errors while creating Spaces keys.
We are continuing to monitor the situation for stability and will post an update once we confirm the issue is fully resolved. Thank you for your patience.
Sep  7, 19:20 UTC
Investigating - As of 17:20 UTC, our Engineering team is investigating an issue with DigitalOcean Container Registry. At this time, users may experience errors while interacting and authenticating with the DigitalOcean Container Registry, creating new container registries, and pushing/deleting images to/from registries.
App Platform users may experience build failures.
We apologize for the inconvenience and will share an update once we have more information.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>DigitalOcean Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Upstream Maintenance Impacting App Platform]]></title>
        <id>https://status.digitalocean.com/incidents/rsj14bmv86q8</id>
        <link href="https://status.digitalocean.com/incidents/rsj14bmv86q8"/>
        <updated>2022-09-07T16:52:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sep  7, 16:52 UTC
Completed - The scheduled maintenance has been completed. If you have any questions or concerns regarding this maintenance, please send us a ticket from your Cloud support page.
Sep  7, 16:01 UTC
In progress - Scheduled maintenance is currently in progress. We will provide updates as necessary.
Sep  7, 15:11 UTC
Scheduled - Start: 2022-09-07 16:00 UTC
End: 2022-09-07 17:00 UTC
During the above window, upstream maintenance will take place that may impact DigitalOcean App Platform.
Expected Impact:
During this period, App Platform users may experience new App creation failing or being delayed, as well as domain updates to existing Apps failing or being delayed. Our Engineering team will be monitoring throughout the maintenance window for any issues.
If you have any questions or concerns regarding this maintenance, please send us a ticket from your Cloud support page.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>DigitalOcean Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident with Actions]]></title>
        <id>https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/sqcs1d0yk16q</id>
        <link href="https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/sqcs1d0yk16q"/>
        <updated>2022-09-07T16:16:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sep  7, 16:16 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Sep  7, 15:02 UTC
Investigating - We are investigating reports of degraded performance for Actions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GitHub Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident with Issues]]></title>
        <id>https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/1nyvf21q5dn7</id>
        <link href="https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/1nyvf21q5dn7"/>
        <updated>2022-09-07T12:21:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sep  7, 12:21 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Sep  7, 11:55 UTC
Investigating - We are investigating reports of degraded performance for Issues.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GitHub Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scheduled infrastructure maintenance]]></title>
        <id>https://status.make.com/incidents/x51vhf4cwzzt</id>
        <link href="https://status.make.com/incidents/x51vhf4cwzzt"/>
        <updated>2022-09-07T09:00:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sep  7, 11:00 CEST
Completed - The scheduled maintenance has been completed.
Sep  7, 10:00 CEST
In progress - Scheduled maintenance is currently in progress. We will provide updates as necessary.
Aug 25, 12:16 CEST
Update - We will be undergoing scheduled maintenance during this time.
Aug 25, 12:05 CEST
Update - We will be undergoing scheduled maintenance during this time.
Aug 25, 11:57 CEST
Scheduled - Please note that we will be undergoing scheduled infrastructure maintenance on Wednesday September 7th between 10:00 AM and 11:00 AM CEST on us1.make.com.  During this maintenance you can expect few short service interruptions.
During the maintenance the us1.make.com website login will not work.
All webhooks and shared hooks processed at that time will be rejected.
There will be no impact on eu1.make.com, eu1.make.celonis.com and us1.make.celonis.com.
We do not expect any data loss.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Make Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident with Packages]]></title>
        <id>https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/d181frs643d4</id>
        <link href="https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/d181frs643d4"/>
        <updated>2022-09-07T08:45:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sep  7, 08:45 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Sep  7, 07:59 UTC
Update - We continuing to identify an issue that impacts Package customers using Actions and are working on mitigation. We will continue to keep you updated on progress.
Sep  7, 07:16 UTC
Update - Packages is still experiencing degraded availability. We are continuing to investigate.
Sep  7, 06:39 UTC
Update - We are investigating reports of issues with service(s): Packages accessed from GitHub Actions. We will continue to keep users updated on progress towards mitigation.
Sep  7, 05:56 UTC
Investigating - We are investigating reports of degraded performance for Packages.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GitHub Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident on 2022-09-06 22:56 UTC]]></title>
        <id>https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/wl09fvhb20x8</id>
        <link href="https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/wl09fvhb20x8"/>
        <updated>2022-09-07T00:08:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sep  7, 00:08 UTC
Resolved - Everything is operating normally.
Sep  6, 22:56 UTC
Investigating - We are investigating reports of degraded performance for all GitHub Services.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GitHub Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Devices page not accessible]]></title>
        <id>https://status.rippling.com/incidents/5lqwzddl4s93</id>
        <link href="https://status.rippling.com/incidents/5lqwzddl4s93"/>
        <updated>2022-09-06T23:22:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sep  6, 23:22 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Sep  6, 22:48 UTC
Identified - The issue has been identified and a fix is being implemented.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rippling Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident on 2022-09-06 22:05 UTC]]></title>
        <id>https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/cwp52gsftl5n</id>
        <link href="https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/cwp52gsftl5n"/>
        <updated>2022-09-06T22:20:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sep  6, 22:20 UTC
Resolved - Everything is operating normally.
Sep  6, 22:05 UTC
Investigating - We are investigating reports of degraded performance for all GitHub Services.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GitHub Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Notice: Email ticket creation may not be working.]]></title>
        <id>https://status.slack.com//2022-09/ea1c1840310f6593</id>
        <link href="https://status.slack.com//2022-09/ea1c1840310f6593"/>
        <updated>2022-09-06T20:05:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our service provider has resolved the issue and email ticket creation is now working as expected. 


Thank you for your patience while we sorted this out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Slack System Status</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Networking in LON1]]></title>
        <id>https://status.digitalocean.com/incidents/kp648z6hmzjp</id>
        <link href="https://status.digitalocean.com/incidents/kp648z6hmzjp"/>
        <updated>2022-09-06T16:34:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sep  6, 16:34 UTC
Resolved - Our Engineering team has confirmed full resolution of the issue with networking in our LON1 region. From 12:57 - 15:33 UTC, a subset of Droplet-based services in LON1 experienced network connectivity issues. All services are now operating normally. If you continue to experience problems, please open a ticket with our support team. We apologize for any inconvenience.
Sep  6, 15:14 UTC
Monitoring - Our Engineering team was able to take action to mitigate the issue with network connectivity in our LON1 region. At this time, users should be seeing restoration of network connectivity to and from Droplet-based resources in LON1. We are monitoring the situation and will post an update as soon as we confirm the issue is fully resolved.
Sep  6, 13:42 UTC
Investigating - Our Engineering team is investigating reports of connectivity issues in our LON1 region. At this time, users may see timeouts and/or errors with connectivity to and from Droplet-based resources in LON1, including Droplets, Managed Databases, and Kubernetes clusters. We will post an update with further information as soon as possible.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>DigitalOcean Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[New feature] Brand new Dashboard section to easily manage your daily tasks from Smily 🚀]]></title>
        <id>243150</id>
        <link href="https://changelog.bookingsync.com/new-feature-brand-new-dashboard-section-to-easily-manage-your-daily-tasks-from-smily-243150"/>
        <updated>2022-09-06T09:29:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New!
  
Today, we are glad to announce yet a new feature: a brand new Dashboard section that will allow you to easily manage your daily tasks, directly from your Smily account.
Here is a sneak peek at what the new Dashboard looks like:

In the past, managing day to day operations may have been complicated. Tasks such as keeping track of payments, approving pending tentatives and others were time consuming.
Thanks to the Dashboard, you now have access to the following information:
List of pending tentatives: to help you convert them into confirmed bookings, or cancel them to free up the dates in your calendar
List of bookings with missing payments: to help you get all your payments on time and never miss a payment again
List of arrivals of the day: to help you plan the check-in of your guests
List of departures of the day: to help you plan the check-out of your guests
You can find more details in the dedicated manual article, and a video guided tour of the new Dashboard section will soon be added there as well.
We invite you to explore this new Dashboard, and hope it will help you save time and better manage your daily operations. Some improvements will also be made in the future, such as adding performance metrics to help you manage your business more easily.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>JB, FinOps Product Dept. Director &amp; Core CS Team Lead</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scheduled infrastructure maintenance]]></title>
        <id>https://status.make.com/incidents/ccwj75wldsk7</id>
        <link href="https://status.make.com/incidents/ccwj75wldsk7"/>
        <updated>2022-09-06T04:00:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sep  6, 06:00 CEST
Completed - The scheduled maintenance has been completed.
Sep  6, 04:01 CEST
In progress - Scheduled maintenance is currently in progress. We will provide updates as necessary.
Sep  1, 11:13 CEST
Update - We will be undergoing scheduled maintenance during this time.
Aug 25, 11:55 CEST
Scheduled - Please note that we will be undergoing scheduled infrastructure maintenance on Tuesday September 6th between 04:00 AM and 06:00 AM CEST on eu1.make.com and eu1.make.celonis.com.  During this maintenance you can expect few short service interruptions.
During the maintenance the eu1.make.com eu1.make.celonis.com website login will not work.
All webhooks and shared hooks processed at that time will be rejected.
There will be no impact on us1.make.com, us1.make.celonis.com.
We do not expect any data loss.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Make Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident: Issues with the Slack interface]]></title>
        <id>https://status.slack.com//2022-08/aeda713fb0151d46</id>
        <link href="https://status.slack.com//2022-08/aeda713fb0151d46"/>
        <updated>2022-09-03T00:22:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Issue summary:

From August 31, 2022 at 7:24 PM PDT to September 1, 2022 at 12:15 AM PDT, some customers experienced visual trouble with the Slack interface. Multiple message attachments overlapped, making them inaccessible. 


We traced this to a recent code change, which we reversed — resolving trouble for all affected users.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Slack System Status</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cloud Control Panel]]></title>
        <id>https://status.digitalocean.com/incidents/sgz90cmyw28j</id>
        <link href="https://status.digitalocean.com/incidents/sgz90cmyw28j"/>
        <updated>2022-09-02T09:13:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sep  2, 09:13 UTC
Resolved - Our engineering team has confirmed that the issues affecting access to the Cloud Control Panel have been fully resolved. We appreciate your patience throughout the process and if you continue to experience problems, please open a ticket with our support team for further review.
Sep  2, 08:42 UTC
Monitoring - Our engineering team has implemented a fix to resolve the issue with accessing our Cloud Control Panel and is monitoring the situation. We will post an update as soon as the issue is fully resolved.
Sep  2, 06:36 UTC
Identified - Our Engineering team has identified the cause of the issue with accessing the Cloud Control Panel and is actively working on a fix. During this time, users in India might face issues with receiving the authorization code to login to the Cloud Control Panel. We will post an update as soon as additional information is available
Sep  2, 05:19 UTC
Investigating - Beginning 04:00 UTC, our Engineering team is investigating an issue with accessing our Cloud Control Panel. During this time, users may experience intermittent errors while trying to login and receive authorization codes to the phone. We apologize for the inconvenience and will share an update once we have more information.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>DigitalOcean Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cloud Control Panel]]></title>
        <id>https://status.digitalocean.com/incidents/z7z5dn5grkf2</id>
        <link href="https://status.digitalocean.com/incidents/z7z5dn5grkf2"/>
        <updated>2022-09-01T19:09:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sep  1, 19:09 UTC
Resolved - Our engineering team has confirmed that the issues affecting access to the Cloud Control Panel have been fully resolved. We appreciate your patience throughout the process and if you continue to experience problems, please open a ticket with our support team for further review.
Sep  1, 17:40 UTC
Monitoring - Our engineering team has completed the rollback and we can confirm that the Cloud Control Panel is now accessible. We are continuing to monitor the situation for stability and will post an update once we confirm the issue is fully resolved. Thank you for your patience.
Sep  1, 17:10 UTC
Identified - Our engineering team has identified an issue with accessing our Cloud Control Panel. During this time, users may experience intermittent errors while trying to login or interact with the Cloud Control Panel. Our team has initiated a rollback to mitigate the issue and we will post an update as soon as possible. We apologize for the inconvenience.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>DigitalOcean Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>