<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2022-11-12T00:27:56.848Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2022-11-12T00:27:56.848Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mexico SMS Carrier Partner Maintenance]]></title>
        <id>https://status.twilio.com/incidents/f7svzbpv223b</id>
        <link href="https://status.twilio.com/incidents/f7svzbpv223b"/>
        <updated>2022-11-12T06:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[THIS IS A SCHEDULED EVENT Nov 11, 22:00 PST  -  Nov 12, 03:00 PST
Nov 10, 20:35 PST
Scheduled - Our SMS carrier partner in Mexico is conducting an emergency maintenance on 11 November 2022 22:00 PST until 12 November 2022 03:00 PST During the maintenance window, there could be intermittent delays delivering SMS to and from Mexico handsets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Twilio Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[On Call Engineers are Investigating]]></title>
        <id>https://status.twilio.com/incidents/25mdthynl33m</id>
        <link href="https://status.twilio.com/incidents/25mdthynl33m"/>
        <updated>2022-11-12T00:05:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nov 11, 16:05 PST
Update - We are continuing to investigate a potential issue with SMS delivery delays to MTN Afghanistan.
Nov 11, 15:07 PST
Investigating - Our monitoring systems have detected a potential issue with SMS delivery delays to MTN Afghanistan. Our engineering team has been alerted and is actively investigating. We will update as soon as we have more information.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Twilio Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SMS Delivery Failures Over a Subset of Short Codes to Sprint Spectrum Network in the US]]></title>
        <id>https://status.twilio.com/incidents/gdfrqyfrtdvr</id>
        <link href="https://status.twilio.com/incidents/gdfrqyfrtdvr"/>
        <updated>2022-11-11T20:57:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nov 11, 12:57 PST
Resolved - We are no longer experiencing SMS delivery failures to Sprint Spectrum network in the US. This incident has been resolved.
Nov 11, 11:02 PST
Monitoring - We are observing successful SMS delivery over a subset of short codes to Sprint Spectrum network in the US. We will continue to monitor to ensure full service recovery. We expect to provide another update in 2 hours or as soon as more information becomes available.
Nov 11, 09:26 PST
Update - We are still experiencing SMS delivery failures over a subset of short codes to Sprint Spectrum network in the US. Our engineers are working with our carrier partner to resolve the issue. We expect to provide another update in 2 hours or as soon as more information becomes available.
Nov 11, 08:28 PST
Investigating - We are experiencing SMS delivery failures over a subset of short codes to Sprint Spectrum network in the US. Our engineers are working with our carrier partner to resolve the issue. We expect to provide another update in 1 hour or as soon as more information becomes available.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Twilio Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Delays and Errors for Outbound SMS Messages]]></title>
        <id>https://status.twilio.com/incidents/8ck6gq7hb3d5</id>
        <link href="https://status.twilio.com/incidents/8ck6gq7hb3d5"/>
        <updated>2022-11-11T14:47:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nov 11, 06:47 PST
Resolved - The issue causing delays and errors for outbound SMS messages has been resolved and the service is operating normally at this time.
Nov 11, 05:55 PST
Monitoring - We have started seeing recovery for the issue causing delays and errors for outbound SMS messages. We will continue to monitor to ensure a full recovery. We expect to provide another update in 30 minutes or as soon as more information becomes available.
Nov 11, 05:17 PST
Investigating - Our monitoring systems have detected a potential issue with delays and errors for outbound SMS messages. Our engineering team has been alerted and is actively investigating. We will provide another update in 1 hour or as soon as more information becomes available.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Twilio Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SMS Delivery Delays to Far EasTone Network in Taiwan]]></title>
        <id>https://status.twilio.com/incidents/059jwgjc7l6g</id>
        <link href="https://status.twilio.com/incidents/059jwgjc7l6g"/>
        <updated>2022-11-11T13:41:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nov 11, 05:41 PST
Resolved - We are no longer experiencing SMS delivery delays when sending messages to Far EasTone Network in Taiwan. This incident has been resolved.
Nov 11, 03:59 PST
Update - We are observing recovery in SMS delivery delays when sending messages to Far EasTone Network in Taiwan. We will continue monitoring the service to ensure a full recovery. We will provide another update in 2 hour or as soon as more information becomes available.
Nov 11, 02:12 PST
Monitoring - We are observing recovery in SMS delivery delays when sending messages to Far EasTone Network in Taiwan. We will continue monitoring the service to ensure a full recovery. We will provide another update in 2 hour or as soon as more information becomes available.
Nov 11, 00:23 PST
Update - We are continue to experience SMS delivery delays when sending messages to Far EasTone Network in Taiwan. Our engineers are investigating the issue. We will provide another update in 2 hour or as soon as more information becomes available.
Nov 10, 23:35 PST
Update - We are experiencing SMS delivery delays when sending messages to Far EasTone Network in Taiwan. Our engineers are investigating the issue. We will provide another update in 1 hour or as soon as more information becomes available.
Nov 10, 23:19 PST
Investigating - Our monitoring systems have detected a potential issue with SMS Delivery Delays To Far EasTone Network In Taiwan. Our engineering team has been alerted and is actively investigating. We will update as soon as we have more information.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Twilio Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[On Call Engineers are Investigating]]></title>
        <id>https://status.twilio.com/incidents/d4pf7m92w3sk</id>
        <link href="https://status.twilio.com/incidents/d4pf7m92w3sk"/>
        <updated>2022-11-11T13:26:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nov 11, 05:26 PST
Resolved - The issue causing higher latency for email sent via SendGrid has been resolved, and the service is functioning normally at this time.
Nov 11, 05:02 PST
Investigating - Our monitoring systems have detected a potential issue with our service, Verify is experiencing higher latency for email sent via SendGrid. Our engineering team has been alerted and is actively investigating. We will update as soon as we have more information.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Twilio Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[500 When Getting Reservations]]></title>
        <id>https://airbnbapi.statuspage.io/incidents/pbsb4zmdbd0j</id>
        <link href="https://airbnbapi.statuspage.io/incidents/pbsb4zmdbd0j"/>
        <updated>2022-11-10T22:08:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nov 10, 14:08 PST
Resolved - The incident has been resolved
Nov 10, 09:19 PST
Monitoring - A fix has been implemented and we are monitoring the results. The get Reservations endpoint was recovered at 8:55 AM PDT.
Nov 10, 09:16 PST
Update - We are continuing to investigate this issue.
Nov 10, 07:52 PST
Investigating - We are currently investigating an issue related to increased error rate on the reservation endpoints. The increase started around 7:05 AM PDT. We'll post updates as we have more information.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Airbnb API Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rippling Devices Agent installation fails with "Error: Could not install the agent"]]></title>
        <id>https://status.rippling.com/incidents/mf94j7bygffg</id>
        <link href="https://status.rippling.com/incidents/mf94j7bygffg"/>
        <updated>2022-11-10T00:57:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nov 10, 00:57 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Nov  9, 18:30 UTC
Update - We are continuing to monitor for any further issues.
Nov  9, 18:29 UTC
Monitoring - A fix has been implemented and we are monitoring the results.
Nov  9, 18:15 UTC
Identified - The issue has been identified and a fix is being implemented.
Nov  9, 17:02 UTC
Investigating - We are currently investigating this issue.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rippling Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident with Actions, API Requests, Codespaces, Copilot, Git Operations, Issues, Packages, Pages, Pull Requests and Webhooks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/74y4xlr09qll</id>
        <link href="https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/74y4xlr09qll"/>
        <updated>2022-11-09T01:53:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nov  9, 01:53 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Nov  9, 01:45 UTC
Investigating - We are investigating reports of degraded performance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GitHub Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RESOLVED: We're aware of a problem with Google Meet affecting a significant subset of users. We will provide an update by Oct 31, 2022, 2:00 AM UTC detailing when we expect to resolve the problem. Please note that this resolution time is an estimate and may change.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.google.com/appsstatus/dashboard/incidents/P5p24TrPaTRq3cYo1WJ8</id>
        <link href="https://www.google.com/appsstatus/dashboard/incidents/P5p24TrPaTRq3cYo1WJ8"/>
        <updated>2022-11-08T19:29:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p> Incident began at <strong>2022-10-28 16:22</strong> and ended at <strong>2022-11-04 18:05</strong> <span>(times are in <strong>Coordinated Universal Time (UTC)</strong>).</span></p><div class="cBIRi14aVDP__status-update-text"><h1>Mini Incident Report</h1>
<p>We apologize for the inconvenience this service disruption/outage may have caused. We would like to provide some information about this incident below. Please note, this information is based on our best knowledge at the time of posting and is subject to change as our investigation continues. If you have experienced impact outside of what is listed below, please reach out to Google Workspace Support using the help article <a href="https://support.google.com/a/answer/1047213">https://support.google.com/a/answer/1047213</a>.</p>
<p>(All Times US/Pacific)</p>
<p><strong>Incident Start:</strong> 28 October 2022 09:22</p>
<p><strong>Incident End:</strong> 04 November 2022 11:05</p>
<p><strong>Duration:</strong>  7 days, 1hour, 43 minutes</p>
<p><strong>Affected Services and Features:</strong></p>
<p>Google Meet - iOS App</p>
<p><strong>Regions/Zones:</strong> Global</p>
<p><strong>Description:</strong></p>
<p>A subset of Google Meet iOS App users experienced issues with Phone Number registration.  From preliminary analysis, the root cause is a latent issue at the time of registration.
The latest version of Google Meet iOS App which contains the fix was released to the AppStore on 04 November 2022.</p>
<p><strong>Customer Impact:</strong></p>
<p>Google Meet iOS App users may have encountered an “unable to add calling” error which resulted in Phone number registration failures.</p>
</div><hr><p>Affected products: Google Meet</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Workspace Status Dashboard Updates</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident on 2022-11-07 19:07 UTC]]></title>
        <id>https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/jrzkpt9g8zm6</id>
        <link href="https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/jrzkpt9g8zm6"/>
        <updated>2022-11-08T01:21:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nov  8, 01:21 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Nov  7, 20:29 UTC
Investigating - We are investigating and mitigating intermittent availability issues on some GitHub services.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GitHub Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident with Issues]]></title>
        <id>https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/ysp25kyy4lz2</id>
        <link href="https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/ysp25kyy4lz2"/>
        <updated>2022-11-07T20:06:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nov  7, 20:06 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Nov  7, 19:07 UTC
Investigating - We are investigating reports of degraded performance for Issues.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GitHub Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident with Git Operations and Pull Requests]]></title>
        <id>https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/6j4vyplhgy51</id>
        <link href="https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/6j4vyplhgy51"/>
        <updated>2022-11-07T05:12:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nov  7, 05:12 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Nov  7, 04:41 UTC
Investigating - We are investigating reports of degraded performance for Git Operations and Pull Requests.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GitHub Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident with Issues]]></title>
        <id>https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/mcb7n71zvlgb</id>
        <link href="https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/mcb7n71zvlgb"/>
        <updated>2022-11-06T09:13:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nov  6, 09:13 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Nov  6, 08:54 UTC
Investigating - We are investigating reports of degraded performance for Issues.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GitHub Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident with Codespaces]]></title>
        <id>https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/9x0hxrdj9crr</id>
        <link href="https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/9x0hxrdj9crr"/>
        <updated>2022-11-04T23:56:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nov  4, 23:56 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Nov  4, 23:41 UTC
Investigating - We are investigating reports of degraded performance for Codespaces.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GitHub Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scheduled infrastructure maintenance]]></title>
        <id>https://status.make.com/incidents/0sv2pz949kv3</id>
        <link href="https://status.make.com/incidents/0sv2pz949kv3"/>
        <updated>2022-11-04T05:05:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nov  4, 06:05 CET
Completed - The scheduled maintenance has been completed.
Nov  4, 05:00 CET
In progress - Scheduled maintenance is currently in progress. We will provide updates as necessary.
Nov  2, 12:39 CET
Scheduled - Please note there is scheduled infrastructure maintenance on Friday 4th of November, between 5 AM and 7 AM CET, when you can expect a few short service interruptions. During this maintenance following services will be affected:
- Migrations will not be available
- Shared hooks created within maintenance will not be accepted nor processed
- Logins to the platform might be affected
- Registration of new subscribers won't be possible
- Invitations of new team members won't be possible
- E-mails and notifications might be delayed
- Password reset won't be possible
- Payments for subscription plans won't be accepted  
We will inform you once the maintenance is completed.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Make Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Importer Maintenance]]></title>
        <id>https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/3ktldkb3r6f8</id>
        <link href="https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/3ktldkb3r6f8"/>
        <updated>2022-11-04T04:01:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nov  4, 04:01 UTC
Completed - The scheduled maintenance has been completed.
Nov  4, 03:00 UTC
In progress - Scheduled maintenance is currently in progress. We will provide updates as necessary.
Oct 27, 17:00 UTC
Scheduled - GitHub Importer—namely the “Import repository” (https://github.com/new/import) UI on GitHub.com and the "Source Imports" (https://docs.github.com/en/rest/migrations/source-imports) REST API—will be undergoing scheduled maintenance. During this time, no new source imports will be processed. You will not be able to start new source imports until the end of the maintenance window.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GitHub Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Issues loading Rippling]]></title>
        <id>https://status.rippling.com/incidents/szycrhr9zqy6</id>
        <link href="https://status.rippling.com/incidents/szycrhr9zqy6"/>
        <updated>2022-11-04T00:23:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nov  4, 00:23 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Nov  3, 23:56 UTC
Monitoring - A fix has been implemented and we are monitoring the results.
Nov  3, 23:50 UTC
Identified - The issue has been identified and a fix is being implemented.
Nov  3, 23:48 UTC
Investigating - We are currently investigating this issue.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rippling Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident with Actions]]></title>
        <id>https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/9hvtdt3pn3z6</id>
        <link href="https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/9hvtdt3pn3z6"/>
        <updated>2022-11-03T17:12:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nov  3, 17:12 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Nov  3, 16:54 UTC
Investigating - We are investigating reports of degraded performance for Actions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GitHub Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident with Actions]]></title>
        <id>https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/zbr492f1vzcy</id>
        <link href="https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/zbr492f1vzcy"/>
        <updated>2022-11-03T16:38:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nov  3, 16:38 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Nov  3, 16:11 UTC
Update - Actions is now experiencing degraded performance. We are still investigating and will provide an update when we have one.
Nov  3, 16:10 UTC
Investigating - We are investigating reports of degraded availability for Actions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GitHub Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident: Users having trouble creating a workflow in Workflow Builder]]></title>
        <id>https://status.slack.com//2022-11/a9c8a1cd80c387cc</id>
        <link href="https://status.slack.com//2022-11/a9c8a1cd80c387cc"/>
        <updated>2022-11-03T00:53:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Issue Summary: 

On Wednesday, November 2nd at 2:12 PM PST to 4:34 PM PST, some users were running into issues with publishing a workflow when using Workflow Builder. Clicking the “Next” button would not return any response, and would cause a workflow to remain in its unpublished state. A new code change had been deployed that caused us to exit early in workflow creation and this is now fixed.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Slack System Status</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Issues loading Rippling]]></title>
        <id>https://status.rippling.com/incidents/42d41g40gbzz</id>
        <link href="https://status.rippling.com/incidents/42d41g40gbzz"/>
        <updated>2022-11-02T13:02:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nov  2, 13:02 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Nov  2, 13:01 UTC
Update - We are continuing to monitor for issues.
Nov  2, 12:52 UTC
Monitoring - A fix has been implemented and we are monitoring the results.
Nov  2, 12:45 UTC
Identified - The issue has been identified and a fix is being implemented.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rippling Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident with Issues and Pull Requests]]></title>
        <id>https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/gw33xm0hbl00</id>
        <link href="https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/gw33xm0hbl00"/>
        <updated>2022-11-01T21:25:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nov  1, 21:25 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Nov  1, 20:25 UTC
Update - We continue to investigate the cause of incorrect results on issue and pull requests search pages.
Nov  1, 19:48 UTC
Update - We are investigating reports of incorrect results on issue and pull requests search pages.
Nov  1, 19:46 UTC
Investigating - We are investigating reports of degraded performance for Issues and Pull Requests.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GitHub Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident: For an emoji sent as a standalone message, the emoji code is not displayed on hover]]></title>
        <id>https://status.slack.com//2022-10/b9c4899413601fcc</id>
        <link href="https://status.slack.com//2022-10/b9c4899413601fcc"/>
        <updated>2022-11-01T21:09:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Issue Summary:

On Wednesday, October 26th at 2:15 PM PST Friday to October 28th 9:12 PM PST, some users were unable to view emoji/code previews when hovering their cursor over messages containing emojis. Upon investigation, we discovered that an error had occurred with the jumbomoji (a message with just an emoji) previewer during the process of a backend code-change we were performing related to emoji. Once we learned this, we were able to deploy a fix which rectified this issue for all affected users.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Slack System Status</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident: Some users may be experiencing issues sending messages, loading threads, and saving bookmarks]]></title>
        <id>https://status.slack.com//2022-10/7044d8ee169bde14</id>
        <link href="https://status.slack.com//2022-10/7044d8ee169bde14"/>
        <updated>2022-10-29T00:23:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Issue summary:

On October 28, 2022 from about 1:06 PM PDT to 1:17 PM PDT, some customers experienced trouble loading threads, sending messages, and saving bookmarks.


This issue occurred when we deployed a web app change resulting in an increased database load. We have since rolled back the deploy, restoring functionality for all affected users.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Slack System Status</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Issues signing in to Rippling]]></title>
        <id>https://status.rippling.com/incidents/mt8g5lsc611x</id>
        <link href="https://status.rippling.com/incidents/mt8g5lsc611x"/>
        <updated>2022-10-28T20:27:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Oct 28, 20:27 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Oct 28, 20:23 UTC
Update - We are continuing to monitor for any further issues.
Oct 28, 20:15 UTC
Update - We are continuing to monitor for any further issues
Oct 28, 19:55 UTC
Monitoring - A fix has been implemented and we are monitoring the results.
Oct 28, 19:55 UTC
Update - We are continuing to investigate this issue.
Oct 28, 19:38 UTC
Investigating - We are currently investigating this issue.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rippling Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Windows computers are being displayed as Apple computers]]></title>
        <id>https://status.rippling.com/incidents/1mfc8wyjff17</id>
        <link href="https://status.rippling.com/incidents/1mfc8wyjff17"/>
        <updated>2022-10-28T19:21:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Oct 28, 19:21 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Oct 28, 18:46 UTC
Monitoring - A fix has been implemented and we are monitoring the results.
Oct 28, 17:27 UTC
Identified - The issue has been identified and a fix is being implemented.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rippling Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Emergency Infrastructure Upgrade on EU1]]></title>
        <id>https://status.make.com/incidents/vb5m7t5l1yps</id>
        <link href="https://status.make.com/incidents/vb5m7t5l1yps"/>
        <updated>2022-10-28T04:29:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Oct 28, 06:29 CEST
Completed - The scheduled maintenance has been completed.
Oct 28, 05:00 CEST
In progress - Scheduled maintenance is currently in progress. We will provide updates as necessary.
Oct 27, 12:57 CEST
Scheduled - Please note that there will be an emergency infrastructure maintenance on 28th of October, between 5 AM and 7 AM CEST on EU1 Instance . 
During the maintenance some scenarios processed at that time might be temporarily delayed . 
We do not expect any data loss. We apologise for any inconvenience caused.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Make Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Importer Maintenance]]></title>
        <id>https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/lpslbfcw2czs</id>
        <link href="https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/lpslbfcw2czs"/>
        <updated>2022-10-27T16:00:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Oct 27, 16:00 UTC
Completed - The scheduled maintenance has been completed.
Oct 27, 15:00 UTC
In progress - Scheduled maintenance is currently in progress. We will provide updates as necessary.
Oct 20, 16:54 UTC
Scheduled - GitHub Importer—namely the “Import repository” (https://github.com/new/import) UI on GitHub.com and the "Source Imports" (https://docs.github.com/en/rest/migrations/source-imports) REST API—will be undergoing scheduled maintenance. During this time, no new source imports will be processed. You will not be able to start new source imports until the end of the maintenance window.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GitHub Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident with Pull Requests]]></title>
        <id>https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/z9dd32bvfgp3</id>
        <link href="https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/z9dd32bvfgp3"/>
        <updated>2022-10-27T06:31:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Oct 27, 06:31 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Oct 27, 06:08 UTC
Update - We have identified a potential fix for the issue where users were experiencing unresponsive code blob views.
Oct 27, 05:36 UTC
Update - We found an issue that impacts some customers when looking at code blob view. We are currently investigating the root cause.
Oct 27, 04:59 UTC
Investigating - We are investigating reports of degraded performance for Pull Requests.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GitHub Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rippling Devices Agent will not install/update 3rd party software on Windows computers when a 3rd party Anti-Virus program is present.]]></title>
        <id>https://status.rippling.com/incidents/hs6bzfm17lh7</id>
        <link href="https://status.rippling.com/incidents/hs6bzfm17lh7"/>
        <updated>2022-10-26T23:51:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Oct 26, 23:51 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Oct 26, 21:55 UTC
Monitoring - A fix has been implemented and we are monitoring the results.
Oct 26, 19:59 UTC
Identified - The issue has been identified and a fix is being implemented.
Oct 26, 19:19 UTC
Investigating - We are currently investigating this issue.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rippling Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Delayed processing of the scenarios and scenario history unavailability]]></title>
        <id>https://status.make.com/incidents/3k9bw2bvpb7k</id>
        <link href="https://status.make.com/incidents/3k9bw2bvpb7k"/>
        <updated>2022-10-26T16:10:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Oct 26, 18:10 CEST
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Oct 26, 17:20 CEST
Identified - Please note we are currently investigating the issue of delayed scenario processing and scenario history being unavailable at the moment.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Make Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident with Issues]]></title>
        <id>https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/dzd955kb7tsb</id>
        <link href="https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/dzd955kb7tsb"/>
        <updated>2022-10-26T14:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Oct 26, 14:40 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Oct 26, 14:07 UTC
Investigating - We are investigating reports of degraded performance for Issues.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GitHub Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scheduled infrastructure maintenance]]></title>
        <id>https://status.make.com/incidents/ngwg3gjjqk51</id>
        <link href="https://status.make.com/incidents/ngwg3gjjqk51"/>
        <updated>2022-10-26T05:00:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Oct 26, 07:00 CEST
Completed - The scheduled maintenance has been completed.
Oct 26, 05:00 CEST
In progress - Scheduled maintenance is currently in progress. We will provide updates as necessary.
Oct 18, 15:33 CEST
Scheduled - Please note there is scheduled infrastructure maintenance on Wednesday 26th of October, between 5 AM and 6 AM CEST, when you can expect few short service interruptions. During this maintenance following services will be affected:
- Migrations will not be available
- Shared hooks created within maintenance will not be accepted nor processed
- Logins to platform might be affected
- Registration of new subscribers won't be possible
- Invitations of new team members won't be possible
- E-mails and notifications might be delayed
- Password reset won't be possible
- Payments for subscription plans won't be accepted  
We will inform you once the maintenance is completed.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Make Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident with Codespaces and Issues]]></title>
        <id>https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/qd7z2cytghrd</id>
        <link href="https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/qd7z2cytghrd"/>
        <updated>2022-10-26T04:34:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Oct 26, 04:34 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Oct 26, 04:23 UTC
Update - Codespaces is now experiencing degraded performance. We are continuing to investigate.
Oct 26, 04:00 UTC
Update - Codespaces is still experiencing degraded availability in US East. To change regions: https://docs.github.com/en/codespaces/customizing-your-codespace/setting-your-default-region-for-github-codespaces
Oct 26, 03:13 UTC
Update - Codespaces is still experiencing degraded availability. We are continuing to investigate.
Oct 26, 02:34 UTC
Update - Codespaces is now experiencing degraded availability. We are continuing to investigate.
Oct 26, 02:33 UTC
Update - Issues is operating normally.
Oct 26, 02:33 UTC
Update - We have resolved Issues performance, and are continuing to investigate degraded performance for Codespaces in US East.
Oct 26, 01:55 UTC
Update - We are investigating Codespace degraded performance in US East. To change region
https://docs.github.com/en/codespaces/customizing-your-codespace/setting-your-default-region-for-github-codespaces
Oct 26, 01:25 UTC
Update - We are continuing to investigate reports of issues with service(s): Issues, Codespaces. We will continue to keep users updated on progress towards mitigation.
Oct 26, 00:52 UTC
Update - Codespaces is experiencing degraded performance. We are still investigating and will provide an update when we have one.
Oct 26, 00:47 UTC
Investigating - We are investigating reports of degraded performance for Issues.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GitHub Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident with Issues and Pull Requests]]></title>
        <id>https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/83yg2mk1cx3c</id>
        <link href="https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/83yg2mk1cx3c"/>
        <updated>2022-10-25T18:44:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Oct 25, 18:44 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Oct 25, 18:11 UTC
Update - We found an issue that impacts roughly 5% of customers of customers. We are working on mitigation.
Oct 25, 17:37 UTC
Update - We are investigating reports of issues with service(s): Issues, Pull Requests. We will continue to keep users updated on progress towards mitigation.
Oct 25, 17:19 UTC
Investigating - We are investigating reports of degraded performance for Issues and Pull Requests.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GitHub Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[500 Error Across All APIs]]></title>
        <id>https://airbnbapi.statuspage.io/incidents/rkg63bw3czj4</id>
        <link href="https://airbnbapi.statuspage.io/incidents/rkg63bw3czj4"/>
        <updated>2022-10-24T17:27:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Oct 24, 10:27 PDT
Resolved - This incident has been resolved. The increase in 500 errors occurred between 4:00 a.m. and 7:00 a.m. PDT. Please reach out to us via the Support Portal if you are still experiencing 500 errors.
Oct 24, 05:40 PDT
Investigating - We are having a site wide issue causing 500 errors across all APIs. We are currently investigating, and we will post updates as we have more information.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Airbnb API Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident with Codespaces]]></title>
        <id>https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/mjcj3l3s160q</id>
        <link href="https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/mjcj3l3s160q"/>
        <updated>2022-10-23T17:36:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Oct 23, 17:36 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Oct 23, 17:22 UTC
Update - We are actively working on mitigations for Codespace creation failures in East US.
Oct 23, 16:46 UTC
Update - We are investigating Codespace creation failures in East US. Users may change region https://docs.github.com/en/codespaces/customizing-your-codespace/setting-your-default-region-for-github-codespaces
Oct 23, 15:39 UTC
Update - We are investigating Codespace creation failures in East US. Users may change region https://docs.github.com/en/codespaces/customizing-your-codespace/setting-your-default-region-for-github-codespaces
Oct 23, 14:40 UTC
Update - We are experiencing issues with codespace creation in the East US region. All other regions are continuing to function without issue.
Oct 23, 14:18 UTC
Investigating - We are investigating reports of degraded performance for Codespaces.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GitHub Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident with Git Operations]]></title>
        <id>https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/5kjgx4x2frkw</id>
        <link href="https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/5kjgx4x2frkw"/>
        <updated>2022-10-21T23:59:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Oct 21, 23:59 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Oct 21, 23:40 UTC
Update - We are investigating reports of issues with service(s): Git Operations. We will continue to keep users updated on progress towards mitigation.
Oct 21, 23:06 UTC
Investigating - We are investigating reports of degraded performance for Git Operations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GitHub Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Requests to create room amenity photos failing (Listing Photos POST Request)]]></title>
        <id>https://airbnbapi.statuspage.io/incidents/38xzd1p2437x</id>
        <link href="https://airbnbapi.statuspage.io/incidents/38xzd1p2437x"/>
        <updated>2022-10-21T23:03:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Oct 21, 16:03 PDT
Resolved - We have identified an issue with creating room amenity photos. The issue would cause POST requests to fail with either a 404 error or a 500 error. This issue approximately started from last Friday, October 14th, 2022. The photo creations are successful in most cases but the requests fail at a later stage resulting in error responses.
We have fixed this issue at 3:30pm PT today, but there can be duplicate photos created for room amenities during this time. We advise you to review room amenity photos and use the DELETE endpoint to remove duplicate photos.
We are sorry for the inconvenience.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Airbnb API Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rippling Devices application is not loading some pages]]></title>
        <id>https://status.rippling.com/incidents/krrbdgtdrrg4</id>
        <link href="https://status.rippling.com/incidents/krrbdgtdrrg4"/>
        <updated>2022-10-21T22:34:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Oct 21, 22:34 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Oct 21, 19:45 UTC
Update - We are continuing to monitor for any further issues.
Oct 21, 19:44 UTC
Monitoring - A fix has been implemented and we are monitoring the results.
Oct 21, 15:32 UTC
Identified - The issue has been identified and a fix has been deployed, we anticipate that pages will be restored soon.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rippling Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[High latency performing certain operations]]></title>
        <id>https://status.notion.so/incidents/d01rgbshld38</id>
        <link href="https://status.notion.so/incidents/d01rgbshld38"/>
        <updated>2022-10-21T18:31:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Oct 21, 11:31 PDT
Resolved - We have resolved the issue. All import, export and duplication work as expected.
Oct 21, 09:39 PDT
Identified - We have implemented a partial fix to unblock key functions, and users should see significant improvement in import, export, and duplication times. We continue to work toward full resolution.
Oct 21, 08:21 PDT
Investigating - Some customers may be experiencing high latency when attempting to export or import content, or duplicate blocks or pages. We are investigating.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Notion Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident with API Requests]]></title>
        <id>https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/4vr2qz8lgdmq</id>
        <link href="https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/4vr2qz8lgdmq"/>
        <updated>2022-10-19T20:23:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Oct 19, 20:23 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Oct 19, 19:52 UTC
Update - Issues related to out-of-date notifications have been resolved.
Oct 19, 19:35 UTC
Update - A small percentage of requests to the audit log APIs are failing. We are continuing to apply additional mitigations.
Oct 19, 19:28 UTC
Update - We are resolving an issue related to out-of-date notifications on GitHub.com. We will provide further updates as we continue resolving the issue.
Oct 19, 18:50 UTC
Update - We are investigating an issue with failing audit log API requests. We are actively working on mitigations.
Oct 19, 17:45 UTC
Update - We are investigating an issue related to the audit logs API
Oct 19, 17:39 UTC
Investigating - We are investigating reports of degraded performance for API Requests.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GitHub Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident: Some users are having issues searching in Slack, seeing the "Something went wrong" message.]]></title>
        <id>https://status.slack.com//2022-10/98da79c75137b53e</id>
        <link href="https://status.slack.com//2022-10/98da79c75137b53e"/>
        <updated>2022-10-19T19:58:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Issue summary:

On October 19, 2022, from 8:17 AM to 10:13 PM PDT, some users saw a "Something went wrong" error when attempting a search query.


This issue was caused by a recent code change that resulted in searches failing. 


We reverted this change, which fixed the issue for all users after a reload of Slack.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Slack System Status</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident with Actions]]></title>
        <id>https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/w0q17vf0dzjr</id>
        <link href="https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/w0q17vf0dzjr"/>
        <updated>2022-10-18T16:16:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Oct 18, 16:16 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Oct 18, 16:05 UTC
Update - Actions is experiencing capacity constraints with hosted ubuntu-22, leading to high wait times. Other hosted labels and self-hosted runners are not impacted. We are actively working on mitigations.
Oct 18, 15:53 UTC
Investigating - We are investigating reports of degraded performance for Actions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GitHub Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident: Some users are experiencing issues loading Slack, including the Threads view, Saved items, notifications, API hyperlinks, and group DMs/channels]]></title>
        <id>https://status.slack.com//2022-10/d2fb7d99fe53f228</id>
        <link href="https://status.slack.com//2022-10/d2fb7d99fe53f228"/>
        <updated>2022-10-14T02:02:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Issue summary:

On October 13, 2022 from 3:00 a.m. to 2:00 p.m. PDT, a number of customers had trouble loading and receiving thread notifications. Some customers may have also had trouble with loading channels, adding users to group direct messages, API hyperlink rendering, and missing Saved items.


A mass de-provisioning event inadvertently increased load across our infrastructure, causing issues with Threads for many users. 


As an immediate mitigation strategy, we temporarily deactivated the Threads view for all users. 


In parallel, we ended the long running de-provisioning jobs, and significantly scaled up the systems that handle those jobs. We also made several code changes to reduce the effect a de-provisioning job of this scale would have on our infrastructure, and redistributed some of the load across other parts of the system. 


The optimisation and redistribution work brought error rates down, which resolved most of the issues with channel loading, group direct messages, hyperlinks, and Saved items that users were experiencing. 


At this point, we made the call not to re-enable the Threads view in order to give our recovery efforts more time to restore balance to the system. 


Once the load was appropriately balanced across our infrastructure, and we were able to confirm that our up-scaling systems were prepared to handle any future spikes, we re-enabled the Threads view for all users.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Slack System Status</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Issue with template duplication]]></title>
        <id>https://status.notion.so/incidents/rg61f5m0hz0r</id>
        <link href="https://status.notion.so/incidents/rg61f5m0hz0r"/>
        <updated>2022-10-14T00:47:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Oct 13, 17:47 PDT
Resolved - This incident has been resolved; users should no longer be experiencing issues with template duplication.
Oct 13, 16:05 PDT
Identified - Some users are continuing to experience issues with template duplication. We have identified the source of the issue and are currently implementing the fix.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Notion Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident with Issues]]></title>
        <id>https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/298l2r792bl7</id>
        <link href="https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/298l2r792bl7"/>
        <updated>2022-10-13T21:30:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Oct 13, 21:30 UTC
Resolved - Everything is operating normally.
Oct 13, 20:47 UTC
Investigating - We are investigating reports of degraded availability for Issues.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GitHub Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>