<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2023-01-14T00:21:41.515Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2023-01-14T00:21:41.515Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Delay on Programmable Messaging on Ireland Environment]]></title>
        <id>https://status.twilio.com/incidents/r1zvgx9nt7lj</id>
        <link href="https://status.twilio.com/incidents/r1zvgx9nt7lj"/>
        <updated>2023-01-13T23:51:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jan 13, 15:51 PST
Update - Delays in Chat/Conversations in Programmable Messaging is now operating normally. We will continue to monitor for system stability. We'll provide another update in 2 hours or as soon as more information becomes available.
Jan 13, 13:28 PST
Monitoring - Delays in Chat/Conversations in Programmable Messaging is now operating normally. We will continue to monitor for system stability. We'll provide another update in 2 hours or as soon as more information becomes available.
Jan 13, 12:41 PST
Update - We are still investigating delays in Programable messaging. Customers in Europe Region may experience latency connection issues with Chat/Conversations features. We expect to provide another update in 1 hour or as soon as more information becomes available.
Jan 13, 12:17 PST
Update - We are investigating delays in Programable messaging. Customers in Europe Region may experience latency connection issues with Chat/Conversations features. We expect to provide another update in 30 minutes or as soon as more information becomes available.
Jan 13, 11:56 PST
Investigating - Our monitoring systems have detected a potential issue with E2E testing. Our engineering team has been alerted and is actively investigating. We will update as soon as we have more information.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Twilio Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Egypt SMS Carrier Maintenance - Vodafone]]></title>
        <id>https://status.twilio.com/incidents/npckcr0j02yy</id>
        <link href="https://status.twilio.com/incidents/npckcr0j02yy"/>
        <updated>2023-01-13T23:00:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jan 13, 15:00 PST
In progress - Scheduled maintenance is currently in progress. We will provide updates as necessary.
Jan 10, 13:13 PST
Scheduled - The Vodafone network in Egypt is conducting an emergency maintenance from 13 January 2023 at 15:00 PST until 13 January 2023 at 20:00 PST. During the maintenance window, there could be intermittent delays delivering SMS to and from Vodafone Egypt handsets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Twilio Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Russia SMS Carrier Maintenance - Beeline]]></title>
        <id>https://status.twilio.com/incidents/7pxlnr7hbqm3</id>
        <link href="https://status.twilio.com/incidents/7pxlnr7hbqm3"/>
        <updated>2023-01-13T22:01:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jan 13, 14:01 PST
In progress - Scheduled maintenance is currently in progress. We will provide updates as necessary.
Dec 29, 04:54 PST
Scheduled - The Beeline network in Russia is conducting a planned maintenance from 13 January 2023 at 14:00 PST until 13 January 2023 at 17:00 PST. During the maintenance window, there could be intermittent delays delivering SMS to and from Beeline Russia handsets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Twilio Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MMS Delivery Report Delays From a Subset of Shortcodes to Multiple Networks in US]]></title>
        <id>https://status.twilio.com/incidents/706dyvywmj0m</id>
        <link href="https://status.twilio.com/incidents/706dyvywmj0m"/>
        <updated>2023-01-13T21:21:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jan 13, 13:21 PST
Update - We are still observing delays in receiving MMS delivery reports to multiple networks in USA from a subset of short codes. Our engineering team has been alerted and is actively investigating. We will update in the next 4 hours or as soon as we have more information.
Jan 13, 11:19 PST
Update - We are still observing delay in receiving MMS delivery reports to multiple networks in USA from a sub-set of short code. Our engineering team has been alerted and is actively investigating. We will update in the next 2 hours or as soon as we have more information.
Jan 13, 10:21 PST
Investigating - We are observing delay in receiving MMS delivery reports to multiple networks in USA from a sub-set of short code. Our engineering team has been alerted and is actively investigating. We will update in the next 1 hour or as soon as we have more information.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Twilio Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mexico SMS Carrier Maintenance - Telcel]]></title>
        <id>https://status.twilio.com/incidents/4y57knnp2j80</id>
        <link href="https://status.twilio.com/incidents/4y57knnp2j80"/>
        <updated>2023-01-13T10:01:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jan 13, 02:01 PST
Completed - The scheduled maintenance has been completed.
Jan 11, 20:00 PST
In progress - Scheduled maintenance is currently in progress. We will provide updates as necessary.
Jan  6, 22:15 PST
Scheduled - The Telcel network in Mexico is conducting a planned maintenance from 11 January 2023 at 20:00 PDT until 11 January 2023 at 20:30 PDT. During the maintenance window, there could be intermittent delays delivering SMS to and from Telcel Mexico handsets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Twilio Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SMS Delivery Delays to Telenor Network in Myanmar]]></title>
        <id>https://status.twilio.com/incidents/lg20hcrp0m4y</id>
        <link href="https://status.twilio.com/incidents/lg20hcrp0m4y"/>
        <updated>2023-01-13T09:18:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jan 13, 01:18 PST
Resolved - We are no longer experiencing SMS delivery delays when sending messages to Telenor Network in Myanmar. This incident has been resolved.
Jan 13, 00:48 PST
Update - We have observed a recovery from the SMS delivery delays and failures when sending messages to Telenor Network in Myanmar. We are monitoring the service to ensure a full recovery, and we will provide another update in 30 minutes or as soon as more information becomes available.
Jan 13, 00:15 PST
Update - We have observed a recovery from the SMS delivery delays and failures when sending messages to Telenor Network in Myanmar. We are monitoring the service to ensure a full recovery, and we will provide another update in 30 minutes or as soon as more information becomes available.
Jan 12, 23:43 PST
Monitoring - We have observed a recovery from the SMS delivery delays and failures when sending messages to Telenor Network in Myanmar. We are monitoring the service to ensure a full recovery, and we will provide another update in 30 minutes or as soon as more information becomes available.
Jan 12, 23:00 PST
Update - We are experiencing SMS delivery delays when sending messages to Telenor Network in Myanmar. Our engineers are working with our carrier partner to resolve the issue. We will provide another update in 1 hour or as soon as more information becomes available.
Jan 12, 22:12 PST
Investigating - Our monitoring systems have detected a potential issue with SMS Delivery Delay with Telenor Network. Our engineering team has been alerted and is actively investigating. We will update as soon as we have more information.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Twilio Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US SMS Carrier Maintenance - Verizon]]></title>
        <id>https://status.twilio.com/incidents/78nxsxzhq4hc</id>
        <link href="https://status.twilio.com/incidents/78nxsxzhq4hc"/>
        <updated>2023-01-13T08:00:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jan 13, 00:00 PST
Completed - The scheduled maintenance has been completed.
Jan 12, 21:00 PST
In progress - Scheduled maintenance is currently in progress. We will provide updates as necessary.
Jan  7, 07:36 PST
Scheduled - The Verizon network in the US is conducting a planned maintenance from 12 January 2023 at 21:00 PST until 13 January 2023 at 00:00 PST. During the maintenance window, there could be intermittent delays delivering SMS to and from Verizon US handsets when sending via US shortcode, US longcode and US Toll-free numbers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Twilio Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident with Copilot]]></title>
        <id>https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/n6wxc7xwrk1z</id>
        <link href="https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/n6wxc7xwrk1z"/>
        <updated>2023-01-12T04:55:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jan 12, 04:55 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Jan 12, 04:51 UTC
Update - Some Copilot plans were impacted by a recent backend change causing those users to see an error that access has ended.  We have applied a change to correct this and are seeing full recovery.
Jan 12, 03:59 UTC
Investigating - We are investigating reports of degraded performance for Copilot.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GitHub Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Make intermittent login issues]]></title>
        <id>https://status.make.com/incidents/0zz20hbhy112</id>
        <link href="https://status.make.com/incidents/0zz20hbhy112"/>
        <updated>2023-01-11T16:36:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jan 11, 17:36 CET
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Jan 11, 12:00 CET
Monitoring - The root cause of the issue has been identified and a remedy is already in place . Some users might have experienced troubles with logging in to the platform whilst we can confirm that there was no impact on running scenarios . We are actively monitoring the situation .
Jan 11, 11:37 CET
Investigating - We are currently experiencing intermittent issues when logging in to make zones . We are actively investigating the issue and working on a solution.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Make Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident with Actions and Git Operations]]></title>
        <id>https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/00km0kwpz23b</id>
        <link href="https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/00km0kwpz23b"/>
        <updated>2023-01-10T18:14:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jan 10, 18:14 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Jan 10, 17:54 UTC
Update - Some action hosted runners are experiencing longer than normal run times.
Jan 10, 17:22 UTC
Update - Actions is experiencing degraded performance. We are still investigating and will provide an update when we have one.
Jan 10, 17:04 UTC
Investigating - We are investigating reports of degraded performance for Git Operations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GitHub Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[500 Errors Across Multiple Endpoints]]></title>
        <id>https://airbnbapi.statuspage.io/incidents/dz7fk8vqftbf</id>
        <link href="https://airbnbapi.statuspage.io/incidents/dz7fk8vqftbf"/>
        <updated>2023-01-09T23:10:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jan  9, 15:10 PST
Resolved - From 14:00-15:00 Pacific Time (PT), we saw increased 500 errors for multiple API endpoints, including reservations, listings and threads. The issue is now identified and resolved, please retry any failed requests during this time. Apologies for the inconvenience caused due to this incident and thank you for your patience and understanding.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Airbnb API Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident with Actions]]></title>
        <id>https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/ffwkvn9j77d1</id>
        <link href="https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/ffwkvn9j77d1"/>
        <updated>2023-01-07T23:30:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jan  7, 23:30 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Jan  7, 23:25 UTC
Update - We are investigating reports of timeouts with Actions. We will continue to keep users updated on progress towards mitigation.
Jan  7, 22:50 UTC
Investigating - We are investigating reports of degraded performance for Actions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GitHub Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Delay in email delivery due to third-party outage]]></title>
        <id>https://status.rippling.com/incidents/mbk89dt1vc41</id>
        <link href="https://status.rippling.com/incidents/mbk89dt1vc41"/>
        <updated>2023-01-05T15:49:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jan  5, 15:49 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Jan  5, 02:25 UTC
Monitoring - A fix has been implemented and we are monitoring the results.
Jan  5, 01:45 UTC
Update - We are continuing to monitor our third-party service provider for updates. Service has not been restored by the third-party email provider. Once service is restored, the majority of emails that were not sent during the outage will be resent.
Jan  5, 01:14 UTC
Update - We are continuing to monitor our third-party service provider for updates. Service has not been restored by the third-party email provider. Once service is restored, the majority of emails that were not sent during the outage will be resent.
Jan  5, 00:38 UTC
Update - Service has not been restored by the third-party email provider. Once service is restored, the majority of emails that were not sent during the outage will be resent.
Jan  5, 00:17 UTC
Identified - A fix has been implemented by the third-party service. We are working to confirm service has been restored.
Jan  4, 23:31 UTC
Investigating - Our third-party email delivery provider has been experiencing an outage since Jan 4th, 2:10 PM PST, causing a delay in notification delivery for all Rippling emails (including password resets). We are investigating this issue with the third-party provider.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rippling Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Issues completing a MFA authenticator challenge]]></title>
        <id>https://status.rippling.com/incidents/zgg7pyzjl7tr</id>
        <link href="https://status.rippling.com/incidents/zgg7pyzjl7tr"/>
        <updated>2023-01-03T23:07:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jan  3, 23:07 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Jan  3, 21:33 UTC
Monitoring - A fix has been implemented and we are monitoring the results.
Jan  3, 20:35 UTC
Identified - The issue has been identified and a fix is being implemented.
Jan  3, 20:27 UTC
Investigating - Users asked to complete an MFA challenge are unable to advance past the page. We are investigating this issue]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rippling Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RESOLVED: We are experiencing an issue with Gmail, Google Chat, Google Voice. Our engineering team continues to investigate the issue. We will provide an update by Tuesday, 2022-12-13 10:30 US/Pacific with current details.
Users may be facing unavailability for Gmail, Google Chat and Google Voice]]></title>
        <id>https://www.google.com/appsstatus/dashboard/incidents/tLjnxF7DdVTCicccdQtj</id>
        <link href="https://www.google.com/appsstatus/dashboard/incidents/tLjnxF7DdVTCicccdQtj"/>
        <updated>2023-01-03T20:28:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p> Incident began at <strong>2022-12-13 15:34</strong> and ended at <strong>2022-12-13 18:04</strong> <span>(times are in <strong>Coordinated Universal Time (UTC)</strong>).</span></p><div class="cBIRi14aVDP__status-update-text"><p>A combined Incident Report has been published on our Google Workspace Status Dashboard for this Incident - <a href="https://www.google.com/appsstatus/dashboard/incidents/AzeVS1iCHxhtzgi8r3mc">https://www.google.com/appsstatus/dashboard/incidents/AzeVS1iCHxhtzgi8r3mc</a></p>
</div><hr><p>Affected products: Gmail</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Workspace Status Dashboard Updates</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident with Codespaces]]></title>
        <id>https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/srn4b1fjxp8h</id>
        <link href="https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/srn4b1fjxp8h"/>
        <updated>2023-01-01T18:28:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jan  1, 18:28 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Jan  1, 17:28 UTC
Update - We have identified the issue and are deploying a fix. We will update our status when the fix is fully deployed.
Jan  1, 16:44 UTC
Update - Codespaces is experiencing issues with web connectivity from GitHub.com. The desktop client can still be used to launch or connect to codespaces."
Jan  1, 16:33 UTC
Investigating - We are investigating reports of degraded performance for Codespaces.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GitHub Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident with Codespaces]]></title>
        <id>https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/1whd66ydswnx</id>
        <link href="https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/1whd66ydswnx"/>
        <updated>2022-12-31T01:47:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dec 31, 01:47 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Dec 31, 01:39 UTC
Update - We are continuing mitigation for an issue impacting some Codespaces customers. We will keep you updated on progress.
Dec 31, 01:12 UTC
Update - We are continuing to work on mitigation for an issue impacting some Codespaces customers. We will continue to keep you updated on progress.
Dec 31, 00:39 UTC
Update - We identified an issue that impacts some Codespaces customers and are working on mitigation.We will continue to keep you updated on progress.
Dec 31, 00:07 UTC
Investigating - We are investigating reports of degraded performance for Codespaces.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GitHub Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MDM Enrollment not available for new macOS computers]]></title>
        <id>https://status.rippling.com/incidents/gmll739frv3b</id>
        <link href="https://status.rippling.com/incidents/gmll739frv3b"/>
        <updated>2022-12-22T19:55:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dec 22, 19:55 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Dec 22, 18:13 UTC
Update - We are continuing to monitor for any further issues.
Dec 22, 18:13 UTC
Monitoring - A fix has been implemented and we are monitoring the results.
Dec 22, 17:35 UTC
Identified - The issue has been identified and a fix is being implemented.
Dec 22, 17:12 UTC
Investigating - We are currently investigating this issue.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rippling Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Missing Workspace section in sidebar]]></title>
        <id>https://status.notion.so/incidents/3py88r008jjg</id>
        <link href="https://status.notion.so/incidents/3py88r008jjg"/>
        <updated>2022-12-21T18:31:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dec 21, 10:31 PST
Resolved - We have implemented the fix and confirmed the issue is resolved. Workspace section and pages have been restored to the sidebar for affected users.
Dec 21, 10:06 PST
Identified - Since ~3:30pm Pacific time yesterday, some users on Free and Plus plans have been unable to see pages in the Workspace section of the sidebar. We have identified the root cause and a fix is in progress.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Notion Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident: Messages on iOS are automatically marked as read]]></title>
        <id>https://status.slack.com//2022-12/4db4ec459abdd159</id>
        <link href="https://status.slack.com//2022-12/4db4ec459abdd159"/>
        <updated>2022-12-20T14:36:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Issue summary:

From Monday December 12, 2022 at 10:27 AM PST to Monday December 19, 2022 at 1:30 PM PST, we began investigating reports of messages being marked as read when backgrounding the iOS app while in a conversation. As a result, the sidebar would not show unread messages next to the DM/Channel/Threads view. 


We have now made a change on our end that resolved the issue and released a fix on iOS app version 22.12.21. Users on the iOS app should now be able to receive messages without them being marked as read automatically.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Slack System Status</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident with Actions]]></title>
        <id>https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/cb6ljbzhktxd</id>
        <link href="https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/cb6ljbzhktxd"/>
        <updated>2022-12-20T07:58:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dec 20, 07:58 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Dec 20, 07:23 UTC
Update - We are seeing delayed workflow job status updates for Actions. We are seeing the status update events being backed up and have applied a mitigation. We continue to monitor the delay.
Dec 20, 06:55 UTC
Investigating - We are investigating reports of degraded performance for Actions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GitHub Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident with Actions]]></title>
        <id>https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/3y3y8nnbyt2d</id>
        <link href="https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/3y3y8nnbyt2d"/>
        <updated>2022-12-20T01:38:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dec 20, 01:38 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Dec 20, 01:02 UTC
Update - We have identified the issue with manual workflow invocations from the UI. A mitigation will be deployed shortly.
Dec 20, 00:09 UTC
Investigating - We are investigating reports of degraded performance for Actions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GitHub Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Partial search failres]]></title>
        <id>https://status.notion.so/incidents/vwnxl4hd436q</id>
        <link href="https://status.notion.so/incidents/vwnxl4hd436q"/>
        <updated>2022-12-19T03:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dec 18, 19:00 PST
Resolved - From approximately 5pm Pacific time yesterday to 8:30am today, Notion experienced an issue that caused some search results to fail. This issue has been resolved.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Notion Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New feature - Check-in types !]]></title>
        <id>253029</id>
        <link href="https://changelog.bookingsync.com/new-feature-check-in-types-!-253029"/>
        <updated>2022-12-16T14:02:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New!
  
At Smily, we are here to help you Save time and Book more! That's why we are always thrilled to announce new features 🎉
Over the past few years, more and more channels have allowed you to set the check-in instructions, to coordinate a smooth and seamless arrival with your guests.
The check-in types were not synchronized with Smily, preventing you from adding this critical information to your listings.
After several requests and feedback, we created a new field on the rental base where you can add your check-in type. 

This feature is now synchronized with your website and our top partners, Airbnb, Booking.com, VRBO, and Expedia.
Add your check-in types in Smily and provide your guests with a smoother check-in experience!
For more details please follow the steps in this article
We invite you to discover all these new features, and we hope it will help you manage better your bookings, save time, and book more!
Wishing you all a pleasant day!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Zahra, Product manager, PMS team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Investigating reports of degraded performance.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/d5158f5wh1ly</id>
        <link href="https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/d5158f5wh1ly"/>
        <updated>2022-12-15T20:37:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dec 15, 20:37 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Dec 15, 20:31 UTC
Update - We are working on mitigating the issues loading content from raw.github.com
Dec 15, 20:00 UTC
Update - We are investigating issues loading content from raw.github.com
Dec 15, 20:00 UTC
Investigating - We are currently investigating this issue.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GitHub Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident with API Requests]]></title>
        <id>https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/pkbqcn8dp6dy</id>
        <link href="https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/pkbqcn8dp6dy"/>
        <updated>2022-12-15T20:00:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dec 15, 20:00 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Dec 15, 19:47 UTC
Update - We are investigating issues loading content from raw.github.com
Dec 15, 19:42 UTC
Investigating - We are investigating reports of degraded performance for API Requests.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GitHub Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident: Some users having trouble playing videos]]></title>
        <id>https://status.slack.com//2022-12/ddd9879de59fd9d1</id>
        <link href="https://status.slack.com//2022-12/ddd9879de59fd9d1"/>
        <updated>2022-12-15T18:39:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Issue summary: From December 13, 2022 at 11:46 AM PST to December 14, 2022 at 7:30 AM PST some customers may have experienced issues while playing videos.


We determined this issue was caused by a recent frontend change that caused a failure to load videos via the streaming protocol HLS (Hypertext Live Streaming), for which no fallback existed. 


To resolve this issue, we introduced a fallback to HLS allowing users to play video files with a slightly degraded experience, such as longer load times. 


Additionally, we disabled a code optimization technique which fully restored HLS functionality for all users.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Slack System Status</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>