<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2022-09-10T00:28:38.680Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2022-09-10T00:28:38.680Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RESOLVED: We're investigating reports of an issue with Gmail. We will provide more information shortly.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.google.com/appsstatus/dashboard/incidents/u1oUmFdFBEzL46WC3SYZ</id>
        <link href="https://www.google.com/appsstatus/dashboard/incidents/u1oUmFdFBEzL46WC3SYZ"/>
        <updated>2022-09-09T17:58:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p> Incident began at <strong>2022-09-07 16:04</strong> and ended at <strong>2022-09-08 06:29</strong> <span>(times are in <strong>Coordinated Universal Time (UTC)</strong>).</span></p><div class="cBIRi14aVDP__status-update-text"><h1>Mini Incident Report</h1>
<p>We apologize for the inconvenience this service disruption/outage may have caused. We would like to provide some information about this incident below. Please note, this information is based on our best knowledge at the time of posting and is subject to change as our investigation continues. If you have experienced impact outside of what is listed below, please reach out to Google Workspace Support using the help article: <a href="https://support.google.com/a/answer/1047213">https://support.google.com/a/answer/1047213</a>.</p>
<p>(All Times US/Pacific)</p>
<p><strong>Incident Start:</strong> 07 September 2022 09:04</p>
<p><strong>Incident End:</strong> 07 September 2022 23:29</p>
<p><strong>Duration:</strong> 14 hours, 25 minutes</p>
<p><strong>Affected Services and Features:</strong></p>
<p>Google Workspace - Gmail</p>
<p><strong>Regions/Zones:</strong> Global</p>
<p><strong>Description:</strong></p>
<p>Newly created Google Workspace users experienced a temporary error while accessing their Gmail account for a total duration of 14 hours, 25 minutes. From preliminary analysis, the root cause of the issue is due to a large number of compilation queue messages in one domain which slowed compilation in other domains for other users.</p>
<p><strong>Customer Impact:</strong></p>
<p>New Google Workspace user accounts which were created after 07 September 2022 09:00 US/Pacific or whose domain policies/subscriptions were modified since that time, experienced the following error while trying to access Gmail:</p>
<p>“ We’re sorry, but your account is temporarily unavailable. We apologize for the inconvenience and suggest trying again in a few minutes. You can view the Google Workspace Status Dashboard for the current status of the service. Numeric Code: 7354 “</p>
<p>Affected users may have experienced issues while accessing other Workspace services.</p>
<p><strong>Additional details:</strong></p>
<p>The issue was resolved once the backlog of queued compilation messages was cleared.</p>
<hr>
</div><hr><p>Affected products: Gmail</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Workspace Status Dashboard Updates</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident with Pull Requests]]></title>
        <id>https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/p38y9j23bt7b</id>
        <link href="https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/p38y9j23bt7b"/>
        <updated>2022-09-09T01:12:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sep  9, 01:12 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Sep  9, 00:53 UTC
Update - Mitigation efforts are continuing and we are seeing signs of recovery for some affected users.
Sep  8, 23:41 UTC
Update - We are continuing to mitigate the issue impacting some of our customers.
Sep  8, 22:10 UTC
Update - We have identified the source of the issue impacting some of our customers. We continue to mitigate the issue.
Sep  8, 21:04 UTC
Update - We found an issue that impacts some customers. We are working on a mitigation.
Sep  8, 19:44 UTC
Investigating - We are investigating reports of degraded performance for Pull Requests.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GitHub Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident: Windows Store app users may experience an error when launching Slack]]></title>
        <id>https://status.slack.com//2022-09/f4273fe54d4adbcb</id>
        <link href="https://status.slack.com//2022-09/f4273fe54d4adbcb"/>
        <updated>2022-09-08T22:09:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Issue summary:

On September 1st, 2022 from around 6:28 am to September 7th, 2022 around 3:00 pm PDT, some users on the Slack desktop app version 4.28.171 installed via the Windows Store were receiving an error when attempting to connect to Slack. 


We determined the cached information typically used to launch the app became corrupted, and subsequently caused the app to not load through a network request, prompting an error instead of re-trying the connection. We then launched a fix that allowed the app to re-attempt a network request, which solved the issue.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Slack System Status</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident: Some users may experience issues drafting a message that contains a link/hyperlink]]></title>
        <id>https://status.slack.com//2022-09/80573d91231d5ea0</id>
        <link href="https://status.slack.com//2022-09/80573d91231d5ea0"/>
        <updated>2022-09-08T19:46:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Issue summary:

On September 8th, 2022 from around 6:44 AM to 7:10 AM PDT some users on desktop clients experienced issues with drafting their messages and saw unexpected character replacements when links with quotes were used. This was caused by an update that was launched and reverting it fixed the issue for all affected users.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Slack System Status</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident on 2022-09-07 15:04 UTC]]></title>
        <id>https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/pz0bvrjx9ztp</id>
        <link href="https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/pz0bvrjx9ztp"/>
        <updated>2022-09-08T00:00:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sep  8, 00:00 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Sep  7, 15:04 UTC
Investigating - We are investigating and mitigating intermittent availability issues on some GitHub services.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GitHub Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mongo Managed Databases Creation]]></title>
        <id>https://status.digitalocean.com/incidents/lm2sv23vw0bx</id>
        <link href="https://status.digitalocean.com/incidents/lm2sv23vw0bx"/>
        <updated>2022-09-07T20:49:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sep  7, 20:49 UTC
Resolved - Our Engineering team has confirmed that the issue affecting the creation of Mongo Managed Database clusters has been fully resolved. We appreciate your patience throughout the process and if you continue to experience problems, please open a ticket with our support team for further review.
Sep  7, 20:27 UTC
Monitoring - Our Engineering team has identified the root cause of the issue with creation of Mongo Managed Database clusters and a fix has been deployed as of 20:07 UTC. We are monitoring the situation and will post an update once we confirm this incident is fully resolved.
Sep  7, 19:50 UTC
Investigating - Our Engineering team is investigating an issue with creation of Mongo Managed Database clusters. At this time, users may experience errors in creating clusters, both via Cloud Control Panel and API requests.
We apologize for the inconvenience and will share an update once we have more information.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>DigitalOcean Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Container Registry Errors]]></title>
        <id>https://status.digitalocean.com/incidents/hq7fylkxs9f3</id>
        <link href="https://status.digitalocean.com/incidents/hq7fylkxs9f3"/>
        <updated>2022-09-07T20:30:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sep  7, 20:30 UTC
Resolved - Our engineering team has confirmed that the issue affecting DigitalOcean Container Registry has been fully resolved. We appreciate your patience throughout the process and if you continue to experience problems, please open a ticket with our support team for further review.
Sep  7, 19:55 UTC
Monitoring - As of 19:18 UTC, our Engineering team has implemented a fix to resolve the issue with DigitalOcean Container Registry. Users should no longer experience errors while interacting and authenticating with the DigitalOcean Container Registry, creating new container registries, and pushing/deleting images to/from registries.
App Platform builds should now be succeeding. 
During this time users may have experienced errors while creating Spaces keys.
We are continuing to monitor the situation for stability and will post an update once we confirm the issue is fully resolved. Thank you for your patience.
Sep  7, 19:20 UTC
Investigating - As of 17:20 UTC, our Engineering team is investigating an issue with DigitalOcean Container Registry. At this time, users may experience errors while interacting and authenticating with the DigitalOcean Container Registry, creating new container registries, and pushing/deleting images to/from registries.
App Platform users may experience build failures.
We apologize for the inconvenience and will share an update once we have more information.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>DigitalOcean Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Upstream Maintenance Impacting App Platform]]></title>
        <id>https://status.digitalocean.com/incidents/rsj14bmv86q8</id>
        <link href="https://status.digitalocean.com/incidents/rsj14bmv86q8"/>
        <updated>2022-09-07T16:52:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sep  7, 16:52 UTC
Completed - The scheduled maintenance has been completed. If you have any questions or concerns regarding this maintenance, please send us a ticket from your Cloud support page.
Sep  7, 16:01 UTC
In progress - Scheduled maintenance is currently in progress. We will provide updates as necessary.
Sep  7, 15:11 UTC
Scheduled - Start: 2022-09-07 16:00 UTC
End: 2022-09-07 17:00 UTC
During the above window, upstream maintenance will take place that may impact DigitalOcean App Platform.
Expected Impact:
During this period, App Platform users may experience new App creation failing or being delayed, as well as domain updates to existing Apps failing or being delayed. Our Engineering team will be monitoring throughout the maintenance window for any issues.
If you have any questions or concerns regarding this maintenance, please send us a ticket from your Cloud support page.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>DigitalOcean Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident with Actions]]></title>
        <id>https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/sqcs1d0yk16q</id>
        <link href="https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/sqcs1d0yk16q"/>
        <updated>2022-09-07T16:16:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sep  7, 16:16 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Sep  7, 15:02 UTC
Investigating - We are investigating reports of degraded performance for Actions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GitHub Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident with Issues]]></title>
        <id>https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/1nyvf21q5dn7</id>
        <link href="https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/1nyvf21q5dn7"/>
        <updated>2022-09-07T12:21:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sep  7, 12:21 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Sep  7, 11:55 UTC
Investigating - We are investigating reports of degraded performance for Issues.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GitHub Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident with Packages]]></title>
        <id>https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/d181frs643d4</id>
        <link href="https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/d181frs643d4"/>
        <updated>2022-09-07T08:45:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sep  7, 08:45 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Sep  7, 07:59 UTC
Update - We continuing to identify an issue that impacts Package customers using Actions and are working on mitigation. We will continue to keep you updated on progress.
Sep  7, 07:16 UTC
Update - Packages is still experiencing degraded availability. We are continuing to investigate.
Sep  7, 06:39 UTC
Update - We are investigating reports of issues with service(s): Packages accessed from GitHub Actions. We will continue to keep users updated on progress towards mitigation.
Sep  7, 05:56 UTC
Investigating - We are investigating reports of degraded performance for Packages.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GitHub Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident on 2022-09-06 22:56 UTC]]></title>
        <id>https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/wl09fvhb20x8</id>
        <link href="https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/wl09fvhb20x8"/>
        <updated>2022-09-07T00:08:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sep  7, 00:08 UTC
Resolved - Everything is operating normally.
Sep  6, 22:56 UTC
Investigating - We are investigating reports of degraded performance for all GitHub Services.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GitHub Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Devices page not accessible]]></title>
        <id>https://status.rippling.com/incidents/5lqwzddl4s93</id>
        <link href="https://status.rippling.com/incidents/5lqwzddl4s93"/>
        <updated>2022-09-06T23:22:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sep  6, 23:22 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Sep  6, 22:48 UTC
Identified - The issue has been identified and a fix is being implemented.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rippling Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident on 2022-09-06 22:05 UTC]]></title>
        <id>https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/cwp52gsftl5n</id>
        <link href="https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/cwp52gsftl5n"/>
        <updated>2022-09-06T22:20:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sep  6, 22:20 UTC
Resolved - Everything is operating normally.
Sep  6, 22:05 UTC
Investigating - We are investigating reports of degraded performance for all GitHub Services.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GitHub Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Notice: Email ticket creation may not be working.]]></title>
        <id>https://status.slack.com//2022-09/ea1c1840310f6593</id>
        <link href="https://status.slack.com//2022-09/ea1c1840310f6593"/>
        <updated>2022-09-06T20:05:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our service provider has resolved the issue and email ticket creation is now working as expected. 


Thank you for your patience while we sorted this out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Slack System Status</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Networking in LON1]]></title>
        <id>https://status.digitalocean.com/incidents/kp648z6hmzjp</id>
        <link href="https://status.digitalocean.com/incidents/kp648z6hmzjp"/>
        <updated>2022-09-06T16:34:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sep  6, 16:34 UTC
Resolved - Our Engineering team has confirmed full resolution of the issue with networking in our LON1 region. From 12:57 - 15:33 UTC, a subset of Droplet-based services in LON1 experienced network connectivity issues. All services are now operating normally. If you continue to experience problems, please open a ticket with our support team. We apologize for any inconvenience.
Sep  6, 15:14 UTC
Monitoring - Our Engineering team was able to take action to mitigate the issue with network connectivity in our LON1 region. At this time, users should be seeing restoration of network connectivity to and from Droplet-based resources in LON1. We are monitoring the situation and will post an update as soon as we confirm the issue is fully resolved.
Sep  6, 13:42 UTC
Investigating - Our Engineering team is investigating reports of connectivity issues in our LON1 region. At this time, users may see timeouts and/or errors with connectivity to and from Droplet-based resources in LON1, including Droplets, Managed Databases, and Kubernetes clusters. We will post an update with further information as soon as possible.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>DigitalOcean Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[New feature] Brand new Dashboard section to easily manage your daily tasks from Smily 🚀]]></title>
        <id>243150</id>
        <link href="https://changelog.bookingsync.com/new-feature-brand-new-dashboard-section-to-easily-manage-your-daily-tasks-from-smily-243150"/>
        <updated>2022-09-06T09:29:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New!
  
Today, we are glad to announce yet a new feature: a brand new Dashboard section that will allow you to easily manage your daily tasks, directly from your Smily account.
Here is a sneak peek at what the new Dashboard looks like:

In the past, managing day to day operations may have been complicated. Tasks such as keeping track of payments, approving pending tentatives and others were time consuming.
Thanks to the Dashboard, you now have access to the following information:
List of pending tentatives: to help you convert them into confirmed bookings, or cancel them to free up the dates in your calendar
List of bookings with missing payments: to help you get all your payments on time and never miss a payment again
List of arrivals of the day: to help you plan the check-in of your guests
List of departures of the day: to help you plan the check-out of your guests
You can find more details in the dedicated manual article, and a video guided tour of the new Dashboard section will soon be added there as well.
We invite you to explore this new Dashboard, and hope it will help you save time and better manage your daily operations. Some improvements will also be made in the future, such as adding performance metrics to help you manage your business more easily.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>JB, FinOps Product Dept. Director &amp; Core CS Team Lead</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident: Issues with the Slack interface]]></title>
        <id>https://status.slack.com//2022-08/aeda713fb0151d46</id>
        <link href="https://status.slack.com//2022-08/aeda713fb0151d46"/>
        <updated>2022-09-03T00:22:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Issue summary:

From August 31, 2022 at 7:24 PM PDT to September 1, 2022 at 12:15 AM PDT, some customers experienced visual trouble with the Slack interface. Multiple message attachments overlapped, making them inaccessible. 


We traced this to a recent code change, which we reversed — resolving trouble for all affected users.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Slack System Status</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cloud Control Panel]]></title>
        <id>https://status.digitalocean.com/incidents/sgz90cmyw28j</id>
        <link href="https://status.digitalocean.com/incidents/sgz90cmyw28j"/>
        <updated>2022-09-02T09:13:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sep  2, 09:13 UTC
Resolved - Our engineering team has confirmed that the issues affecting access to the Cloud Control Panel have been fully resolved. We appreciate your patience throughout the process and if you continue to experience problems, please open a ticket with our support team for further review.
Sep  2, 08:42 UTC
Monitoring - Our engineering team has implemented a fix to resolve the issue with accessing our Cloud Control Panel and is monitoring the situation. We will post an update as soon as the issue is fully resolved.
Sep  2, 06:36 UTC
Identified - Our Engineering team has identified the cause of the issue with accessing the Cloud Control Panel and is actively working on a fix. During this time, users in India might face issues with receiving the authorization code to login to the Cloud Control Panel. We will post an update as soon as additional information is available
Sep  2, 05:19 UTC
Investigating - Beginning 04:00 UTC, our Engineering team is investigating an issue with accessing our Cloud Control Panel. During this time, users may experience intermittent errors while trying to login and receive authorization codes to the phone. We apologize for the inconvenience and will share an update once we have more information.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>DigitalOcean Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cloud Control Panel]]></title>
        <id>https://status.digitalocean.com/incidents/z7z5dn5grkf2</id>
        <link href="https://status.digitalocean.com/incidents/z7z5dn5grkf2"/>
        <updated>2022-09-01T19:09:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sep  1, 19:09 UTC
Resolved - Our engineering team has confirmed that the issues affecting access to the Cloud Control Panel have been fully resolved. We appreciate your patience throughout the process and if you continue to experience problems, please open a ticket with our support team for further review.
Sep  1, 17:40 UTC
Monitoring - Our engineering team has completed the rollback and we can confirm that the Cloud Control Panel is now accessible. We are continuing to monitor the situation for stability and will post an update once we confirm the issue is fully resolved. Thank you for your patience.
Sep  1, 17:10 UTC
Identified - Our engineering team has identified an issue with accessing our Cloud Control Panel. During this time, users may experience intermittent errors while trying to login or interact with the Cloud Control Panel. Our team has initiated a rollback to mitigate the issue and we will post an update as soon as possible. We apologize for the inconvenience.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>DigitalOcean Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[400 Error on Pricing Settings Endpoint When Updating Standard Fees]]></title>
        <id>https://airbnbapi.statuspage.io/incidents/ll2yf40bkbfr</id>
        <link href="https://airbnbapi.statuspage.io/incidents/ll2yf40bkbfr"/>
        <updated>2022-09-01T09:46:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sep  1, 02:46 PDT
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
If required, please re-push any Pricing Settings Standard Fees updates that may have failed during the incident.
Apologies for any inconvenience caused and thank you for your understanding.
Aug 31, 19:24 PDT
Monitoring - The cause has been identified and mitigated; the errors should no longer be thrown.
We are monitoring the situation.
Apologies for any inconvenience caused.
Aug 30, 23:33 PDT
Investigating - We have noticed an elevated rate of 400 Errors on the Pricing Settings endpoint when attempting to update Standard Fees.
We are investigating the issue.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Airbnb API Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident: Issues setting up SSO for some users.]]></title>
        <id>https://status.slack.com//2022-08/ed2b06a765317908</id>
        <link href="https://status.slack.com//2022-08/ed2b06a765317908"/>
        <updated>2022-08-31T22:32:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Issue summary:

From Monday August 29 at 10:11 AM PDT to Wednesday August 31st at 12:42 PM PDT, some Grid customers were running into errors when configuring SSO settings for their workspaces. Upon investigation, we identified an issue that was resulting in empty SAML configuration files. These empty files triggered the errors seen by users.


Removing the offending file fixed the issue for all affected users.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Slack System Status</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident: Mark as Read preferences not being respected]]></title>
        <id>https://status.slack.com//2022-08/09a013b17a720bc4</id>
        <link href="https://status.slack.com//2022-08/09a013b17a720bc4"/>
        <updated>2022-08-31T02:40:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Issue summary: 

From August 29, 2022 at 11:26 AM PDT to August 30, 2022 at 3:56 PM PDT, some customers may have experienced issues with their Mark as Read preferences, and intermittent issues loading channel history.


When you view a channel, Slack remembers your last scroll position so we can take you back to the same place. A recent feature update inadvertently bypassed the check for this scroll position, creating the impression that Slack wasn't respecting your Mark as Read preference. Additionally, this incorrectly prevented channel history from loading for some users.


We identified the root cause and rolled this code change back, resolving the issue for all affected customers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Slack System Status</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident with Codespaces]]></title>
        <id>https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/hjxtlk3fvr09</id>
        <link href="https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/hjxtlk3fvr09"/>
        <updated>2022-08-29T18:31:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Aug 29, 18:31 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Aug 29, 18:24 UTC
Update - We identified an issue that impacts most Codespaces customers. We have fully deployed a mitigation and are observing improved success rates for Codespaces creation and resumption operations.
Aug 29, 18:21 UTC
Update - Codespaces is now experiencing degraded performance. We are continuing to investigate.
Aug 29, 17:48 UTC
Update - We identified an issue that impacts most Codespaces customers. We have authored a mitigation that will be deployed within 30 minutes. We will continue to keep you updated on progress.
Aug 29, 17:16 UTC
Update - We identified an issue that impacts most Codespaces customers. We are authoring a mitigation that will be deployed within one hour. We will continue to keep you updated on progress.
Aug 29, 16:34 UTC
Update - We identified an issue that impacts most Codespaces customers. We are authoring a mitigation that will be deployed within 90 minutes. We will continue to keep you updated on progress.
Aug 29, 16:02 UTC
Update - We identified an issue that impacts most Codespaces customers. We are authoring a mitigation that will be deployed within two hours. We will continue to keep you updated on progress.
Aug 29, 15:21 UTC
Update - We continuing to identify an issue that impacts most Codespaces customers and are working on mitigation. We will continue to keep you updated on progress.
Aug 29, 14:19 UTC
Update - Codespaces is now experiencing degraded availability. We are continuing to investigate.
Aug 29, 13:37 UTC
Update - We identified an issue that impacts many Codespaces customers and are working on mitigation. We will continue to keep you updated on progress.
Aug 29, 12:51 UTC
Investigating - We are investigating reports of degraded performance for Codespaces.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GitHub Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[App Platform Deployments]]></title>
        <id>https://status.digitalocean.com/incidents/pf9hyyx5rkbc</id>
        <link href="https://status.digitalocean.com/incidents/pf9hyyx5rkbc"/>
        <updated>2022-08-26T20:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Aug 26, 20:30 UTC
Resolved - Beginning 14:21 UTC, App Platform deployments in all regions were degraded. Users may have experienced up to 90 minutes of delay in Apps deploying, seeing "Deploy pending" messages in the control panel. Existing Apps were not impacted and remained online. As of 16:05 UTC, our team has fully resolved this issue and all stuck deployments were pushed through. No action is required from users. If you continue to experience any issues, please open a support ticket from within your account.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>DigitalOcean Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident with Actions and Pages]]></title>
        <id>https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/qjf5mzdcp335</id>
        <link href="https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/qjf5mzdcp335"/>
        <updated>2022-08-25T23:35:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Aug 25, 23:35 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Aug 25, 23:32 UTC
Update - Pages is operating normally.
Aug 25, 23:11 UTC
Update - Pages is experiencing degraded performance. We are continuing to investigate.
Aug 25, 23:11 UTC
Investigating - We are investigating reports of degraded performance for Actions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GitHub Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident: Workflow Builder screen not loading]]></title>
        <id>https://status.slack.com//2022-08/1afbcbaeecc2f6a8</id>
        <link href="https://status.slack.com//2022-08/1afbcbaeecc2f6a8"/>
        <updated>2022-08-25T23:06:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Issue Summary: 

On August 25, 2022 between 11:31 AM PDT and 12:37 PM PDT, some customers experienced trouble loading the Workflow Builder screen.


We traced the problem to a change in the front-end Workflow Builder components which prevented the Workflow Builder from starting up successfully. We reverted this, resolving the issue for all affected customers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Slack System Status</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Block Storage Volumes]]></title>
        <id>https://status.digitalocean.com/incidents/798hgn4bv6dh</id>
        <link href="https://status.digitalocean.com/incidents/798hgn4bv6dh"/>
        <updated>2022-08-25T20:04:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Aug 25, 20:04 UTC
Resolved - Our Engineering team has resolved the issue with Block Storage Volumes. All the operations including creation, deletion, and listing should now be succeeding. We appreciate your patience throughout the process and if you continue to experience problems, please open a ticket with our support team for further review.
Aug 25, 18:59 UTC
Monitoring - Our engineering team has implemented a fix to resolve the issue with Block Storage Volumes. We are currently monitoring the results and will post an update as soon as the matter is resolved completely.
Aug 25, 17:35 UTC
Investigating - Our engineering team is investigating an issue with Block Storage Volumes. During this time users may experience issues while creating, listing, and deleting the Block Storage Volumes in all regions. We apologize for the inconvenience and will share an update once we have more information.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>DigitalOcean Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident with Actions]]></title>
        <id>https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/v7x4r4mplb4t</id>
        <link href="https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/v7x4r4mplb4t"/>
        <updated>2022-08-25T15:29:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Aug 25, 15:29 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Aug 25, 15:12 UTC
Update - We've applied a mitigation to resolve the identified issue. Will update further when confirmed that this has resolved the issue.
Aug 25, 14:45 UTC
Update - GitHub Actions is experiencing degraded job execution throughput for a subset of users. We are working to resolve this as quickly as possible.
Aug 25, 14:10 UTC
Investigating - We are investigating reports of degraded performance for Actions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GitHub Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[New feature] Manage all your reviews from your BookingSync Account !]]></title>
        <id>241989</id>
        <link href="https://changelog.bookingsync.com/new-feature-manage-all-your-reviews-from-your-bookingsync-account-!-241989"/>
        <updated>2022-08-25T13:49:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New!
  
At BookingSync, we are here to make you Save time and Book more. That's why we are always thrilled to announce more and more features.
This time the new feature concerns the reviews management, you can now manage all your reviews on BookingSync. Yes ! all the reviews posted on the biggest channels : Airbnb, Booking.com plus your direct bookings.
When accessing the Reviews section, you will see 2 different sub-menus:
Guest Reviews: This section will allow you to see the different reviews posted by the guests for each property, the rating plus the message posted by the guest, if you need more detail you can click on the review, a new page will appear with the Review details, the Booking details, the complete guest review message, and the host review if it’s already posted, and you have the possibility to reply to the review message.


Host Reviews: This section will allow you to evaluate your guest and share a detailed rating and a review message.


For each of these section you will be able to filter the reviews by Rating, Rentals and Source.
Please find here the video demo explaining step by step the feature.
We invite you to discover all these new features, and hope it will help you to have a better management of your reviews, save more time, and have a better ranking and visibility on the channels !
Don’t hesitate to contact our customer care if you have any questions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yannick, Customer Care Team Leader - Pro Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident with Actions]]></title>
        <id>https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/pmw828sz2w7k</id>
        <link href="https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/pmw828sz2w7k"/>
        <updated>2022-08-24T18:26:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Aug 24, 18:26 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Aug 24, 18:09 UTC
Update - Actions is experiencing degraded performance. We are continuing to investigate.
Aug 24, 18:09 UTC
Investigating - We are investigating reports of degraded performance for Actions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GitHub Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident: Some users are encountering a "Reload required" message]]></title>
        <id>https://status.slack.com//2022-08/fffc131e21aa14a4</id>
        <link href="https://status.slack.com//2022-08/fffc131e21aa14a4"/>
        <updated>2022-08-24T18:00:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Issue Summary:

From August 22, 2022 5:15 PM PDT to August 23, 2022 01:15 AM PDT, some customers experienced a persistent reload prompt when when their user account was converted from a member account to a guest account, even after a reload was completed.


A recent change made to our code resulted in the removal of a mechanism for indicating when a reload dialogue should appear. We have pushed a fix for this problem by reinstating the mechanism to ensure this only occurs for users once.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Slack System Status</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident: Trouble loading and sending messages in Slack]]></title>
        <id>https://status.slack.com//2022-08/477ba9fefe50a765</id>
        <link href="https://status.slack.com//2022-08/477ba9fefe50a765"/>
        <updated>2022-08-24T16:07:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Issue Summary:


On August 23, 2022 between 12:17 PM PDT and 1:32 PM PDT, some customers experienced difficulty with loading Slack and sending messages. This occurred when a group of database servers became overloaded and failed.


We first reduced the load on our infrastructure manually. The issue was then resolved when our automated processes kicked in, replacing the damaged server with a healthy one. While the issue is resolved, we will continue to investigate the root cause to avoid these problems in the future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Slack System Status</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Issues Loading Listings and Images on Airbnb.com]]></title>
        <id>https://airbnbapi.statuspage.io/incidents/r4t46rrly1zx</id>
        <link href="https://airbnbapi.statuspage.io/incidents/r4t46rrly1zx"/>
        <updated>2022-08-23T22:35:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Aug 23, 15:35 PDT
Resolved - This incident has been resolved. If you come across this issue again, don't hesitate to reach out through the Support Portal.
Aug 22, 16:10 PDT
Monitoring - We have implemented a fix, and are monitoring the results. If you come across this issue, don't hesitate to reach out through the Support Portal.
Aug 22, 15:21 PDT
Investigating - We are investigating an issue that is preventing some images and listings from loading on Airbnb's homepage on airbnb.com, as well as the ability for Hosts to complete some listings. We will post more updates as soon as we have it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Airbnb API Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Performance Degradation]]></title>
        <id>https://status.notion.so/incidents/39kmxh87vh8j</id>
        <link href="https://status.notion.so/incidents/39kmxh87vh8j"/>
        <updated>2022-08-23T19:25:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Aug 23, 12:25 PDT
Resolved - This incident has been resolved. Users should no longer experience performance degradation.
Aug 22, 17:15 PDT
Update - Our engineers are continuing to investigate the root cause of the issue. Currently, we expect the issue to be resolved for all users.
Aug 22, 12:01 PDT
Investigating - Notion is experiencing degradation in performance and preventing some users from accessing their content. We are currently investigating this issue.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Notion Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cloud Control Panel, API, Event Processing]]></title>
        <id>https://status.digitalocean.com/incidents/4y1rgp5qlxyl</id>
        <link href="https://status.digitalocean.com/incidents/4y1rgp5qlxyl"/>
        <updated>2022-08-23T02:54:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Aug 23, 02:54 UTC
Resolved - Our engineering team has confirmed full resolution of the issue with the Cloud Control Panel, API, and Event Processing, and all services should now be operating normally. If you continue to experience problems, please open a ticket with our support team. We apologize for any inconvenience.
Aug 23, 02:20 UTC
Monitoring - Our Engineering team identified an issue impacting the Cloud Control Panel, API, and event processing in all regions. From 2:01 - 2:12 UTC, users may have experienced high error rates with issuing event and API requests and been unable to load the Control Panel. A fix has been implemented and we are monitoring the situation. We will post an update once we confirm the issue is fully resolved.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>DigitalOcean Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Managed Database Clusters.]]></title>
        <id>https://status.digitalocean.com/incidents/8s0lbx5kq4n0</id>
        <link href="https://status.digitalocean.com/incidents/8s0lbx5kq4n0"/>
        <updated>2022-08-23T00:36:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Aug 23, 00:36 UTC
Resolved - Our engineering team has resolved the issue with Managed Database Clusters. All database systems should now be operating normally. If you continue to experience problems, please open a ticket with our support team. We apologize for any inconvenience.
Aug 22, 23:58 UTC
Monitoring - Our engineering team has implemented a fix to resolve the issue with Managed Database Clusters and is monitoring the situation. We will post an update as soon as the issue is fully resolved.
Aug 22, 23:02 UTC
Investigating - Our engineering team is investigating an issue with Managed Database Clusters. At this time, users will be unable to list or modify clusters in the control panel and will not be able to check the status of a cluster via monitoring. This should not impact the functionality of a currently running database cluster. 
We apologize for the inconvenience and will share an update once we have more information.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>DigitalOcean Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Popup appearing every 2 minutes on Windows computers managed by Rippling]]></title>
        <id>https://status.rippling.com/incidents/76kltvl4gcbh</id>
        <link href="https://status.rippling.com/incidents/76kltvl4gcbh"/>
        <updated>2022-08-22T19:44:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Aug 22, 19:44 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Aug 22, 18:28 UTC
Monitoring - A fix has been implemented and we are monitoring the results.
Aug 22, 17:04 UTC
Identified - The issue has been identified and a fix is being implemented.
Aug 22, 16:57 UTC
Investigating - We are currently investigating this issue.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rippling Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident: Errors with interactive messages]]></title>
        <id>https://status.slack.com//2022-08/1e5a17ebecd2bda4</id>
        <link href="https://status.slack.com//2022-08/1e5a17ebecd2bda4"/>
        <updated>2022-08-22T17:11:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Issue Summary: 

From August 19, 2022 11:55 AM PDT to August 22, 2022 2:52 AM PDT some users experienced issues using the buttons on interactive messages. 


We traced the issue to a recent code change, which we rolled back, resolving the issue for all impacted users.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Slack System Status</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Notion outage]]></title>
        <id>https://status.notion.so/incidents/lc049xb3mnq4</id>
        <link href="https://status.notion.so/incidents/lc049xb3mnq4"/>
        <updated>2022-08-22T11:11:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Aug 22, 04:11 PDT
Resolved - Notion experienced an outage between 3:18am PT and 3:57am PT, but has recovered.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Notion Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident with Codespaces]]></title>
        <id>https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/fhx2r88mzbyv</id>
        <link href="https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/fhx2r88mzbyv"/>
        <updated>2022-08-21T19:18:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Aug 21, 19:18 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Aug 21, 19:02 UTC
Update - We have partially restored Codespaces port forwarding and are working to fully resolve the impact in all regions.
Aug 21, 17:57 UTC
Update - We are continuing to investigate impact to Codespaces port forwarding.
Aug 21, 17:07 UTC
Investigating - We are investigating reports of degraded performance for Codespaces.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GitHub Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident with API Requests]]></title>
        <id>https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/mqmzg413z93k</id>
        <link href="https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/mqmzg413z93k"/>
        <updated>2022-08-20T03:24:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Aug 20, 03:24 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Aug 20, 03:04 UTC
Investigating - We are investigating reports of degraded performance for API Requests.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GitHub Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Managed Kubernetes Dashboard]]></title>
        <id>https://status.digitalocean.com/incidents/sgld81wmh9gz</id>
        <link href="https://status.digitalocean.com/incidents/sgld81wmh9gz"/>
        <updated>2022-08-19T14:28:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Aug 19, 14:28 UTC
Resolved - Between 9:50 - 13:00 UTC, users were unable to load the Managed Kubernetes page in the Cloud Panel. Our Engineering team has fully resolved this issue and all services are functioning correctly. 
If you continue to experience problems, please open a ticket with our support team. We apologise for any inconvenience.
Aug 19, 13:16 UTC
Monitoring - Our Engineering team has implemented a fix to resolve the issue with functionality of the Managed Kubernetes page in the Cloud Panel and is monitoring the situation. We will post an update as soon as the issue is fully resolved.
Aug 19, 13:05 UTC
Investigating - Our Engineering team is investigating an issue with the functionality of the Managed Kubernetes page in the Cloud Panel. During this time, users will experience a white page while accessing the Kubernetes dashboard. Cluster functionality remains unaffected and users may utilize the API to manage their clusters. We apologize for the inconvenience and will share an update once we have more information.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>DigitalOcean Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Issues connecting to Google Workspace]]></title>
        <id>https://status.rippling.com/incidents/27rtqmdvry5f</id>
        <link href="https://status.rippling.com/incidents/27rtqmdvry5f"/>
        <updated>2022-08-18T20:39:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Aug 18, 20:39 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved. Any reconnections should be successful.
Aug 18, 00:06 UTC
Monitoring - We've rolled back updates to our OAuth library and we're currently monitoring reconnections. If you reconnected your installation prior to 4:45pm PST August 17, 2022, you may receive an additional reconnection notice.
Aug 17, 23:43 UTC
Identified - We've identified the underlying issue and are currently releasing the corresponding fix.
Aug 17, 17:58 UTC
Investigating - Some customers are reporting issues connecting Rippling to Google Workspace. We are currently investigating this issue.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rippling Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident with Actions]]></title>
        <id>https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/8gpymn7rystj</id>
        <link href="https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/8gpymn7rystj"/>
        <updated>2022-08-18T17:36:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Aug 18, 17:36 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Aug 18, 16:38 UTC
Update - We are continuing to work to restore Actions to full health.
Aug 18, 15:58 UTC
Update - We are continuing to work to mitigate intermittent job failures.
Aug 18, 15:25 UTC
Update - We are investigating reports of issues with service(s): Actions, API Requests. We will continue to keep users updated on progress towards mitigation.
Aug 18, 15:17 UTC
Update - API Requests is experiencing degraded performance. We are continuing to investigate.
Aug 18, 14:33 UTC
Investigating - We are investigating reports of degraded performance for Actions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GitHub Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Listing Amenities Improvements]]></title>
        <id>https://airbnbapi.statuspage.io/incidents/s0xq759f69m5</id>
        <link href="https://airbnbapi.statuspage.io/incidents/s0xq759f69m5"/>
        <updated>2022-08-18T07:00:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Aug 18, 00:00 PDT
Completed - The scheduled maintenance has been completed.
Jul 19, 00:00 PDT
In progress - Scheduled maintenance is currently in progress. We will provide updates as necessary.
Jul 18, 15:13 PDT
Scheduled - We are currently rolling out improvements to the backend of our Set Listing endpoint for amenities. This will be done in phases over the course of the next month. 
Please subscribe for deployment updates. We don't expect any change in behavior, but if you come across any issues, please submit an API support request through your Partner Support Portal and link this post.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Airbnb API Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident with Pull Requests]]></title>
        <id>https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/2nd6fyb4drjx</id>
        <link href="https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/2nd6fyb4drjx"/>
        <updated>2022-08-17T17:27:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Aug 17, 17:27 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Aug 17, 17:19 UTC
Investigating - We are investigating reports of degraded performance for Pull Requests.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GitHub Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cloud Control Panel and WWW sites]]></title>
        <id>https://status.digitalocean.com/incidents/gg754r0r67xv</id>
        <link href="https://status.digitalocean.com/incidents/gg754r0r67xv"/>
        <updated>2022-08-16T18:42:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Aug 16, 18:42 UTC
Resolved - Our Engineering team has confirmed resolution of the issue with the Cloud Control Panel and DigitalOcean sites. Our team also confirmed API requests were impacted as a result of this incident and users may have seen API failures between 17:53 - 18:03 UTC. All services should now be operating normally. 
If you continue to experience problems, please open a ticket with our support team. We apologize for any inconvenience.
Aug 16, 18:11 UTC
Monitoring - As of 17:53 UTC, our Engineering team identified an issue with the Cloud Control Panel and some other DigitalOcean webpages, such as marketplace.digitalocean.com. Users were unable to reach cloud.digitalocean.com and may have seen a maintenance page, as well as have been unable to reach other DigitalOcean sites, like the Marketplace. 
Our team deployed a fix at 18:03 UTC and are now monitoring the situation. We will post an update once we confirm the issue is fully resolved. We apologize for any inconvenience.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>DigitalOcean Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident with Codespaces]]></title>
        <id>https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/bdtztmrydlwz</id>
        <link href="https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/bdtztmrydlwz"/>
        <updated>2022-08-16T16:32:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Aug 16, 16:32 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Aug 16, 16:01 UTC
Update - We are still verifying our hotfix for Codespaces web client us-east outage.  Note:  Workaround is to use VS Code desktop client.  ETA ~45m
Aug 16, 15:13 UTC
Update - We are testing a hotfix for our Codespaces web client us-east outage.  Note:  Workaround is to use VS Code desktop client.  ETA ~1h.
Aug 16, 14:28 UTC
Update - We have identified the issue with Codespaces in the us-east region preventing web client use.  Please use the VS Code desktop client as a workaround.   Hotfix is underway, ETA 1h.
Aug 16, 13:51 UTC
Update - We identified an issue that impacts some Codespaces customers and are working on mitigation.We will continue to keep you updated on progress.
The VS Code desktop client can be used as a workaround.
Aug 16, 13:38 UTC
Investigating - We are investigating reports of degraded performance for Codespaces.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GitHub Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident: Issues with sending messages with custom emoji]]></title>
        <id>https://status.slack.com//2022-08/0418b1f6208d547a</id>
        <link href="https://status.slack.com//2022-08/0418b1f6208d547a"/>
        <updated>2022-08-16T03:54:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Issue summary:

From 1:13  PM PDT to 6:56 PM PDT on August 15, 2022 some customers experienced issues in the desktop app when sending messages or reactions with Japanese character emojis.


We identified the issue was the result of a code change to how emojis were validated. We reverted the change which resolved the issue for all affected users.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Slack System Status</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident with Codespaces]]></title>
        <id>https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/0hkbgpcpbkc6</id>
        <link href="https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/0hkbgpcpbkc6"/>
        <updated>2022-08-15T13:18:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Aug 15, 13:18 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Aug 15, 10:55 UTC
Update - We are investigating reports of issues with Codespaces in the eu-west region(s). Users in that location may not be able to connect to their Codespaces during this time. We are investigating contributing factors and will update you on progress towards mitigation.
Aug 15, 10:50 UTC
Investigating - We are investigating reports of degraded performance for Codespaces.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GitHub Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Enforcing Content Validation Policies]]></title>
        <id>https://airbnbapi.statuspage.io/incidents/lml6f9s27wyk</id>
        <link href="https://airbnbapi.statuspage.io/incidents/lml6f9s27wyk"/>
        <updated>2022-08-14T16:00:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Aug 14, 09:00 PDT
Completed - The scheduled maintenance has been completed.
Jul 15, 09:00 PDT
In progress - Scheduled maintenance is currently in progress. We will provide updates as necessary.
Jul 14, 16:01 PDT
Scheduled - Starting on August 15, 2022, the API will respond with `400 validation` errors all requests that violate our content validation policies. This enforcement affects the entire listing description and the instant book welcome message.
Please refer to the Content Validation Enforcement changelog for additional details. Link: https://developer.airbnb.com/changelog/new-content-validation-enforcement]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Airbnb API Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Email Notifications]]></title>
        <id>https://status.digitalocean.com/incidents/x0gvb39624ct</id>
        <link href="https://status.digitalocean.com/incidents/x0gvb39624ct"/>
        <updated>2022-08-12T01:34:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Aug 12, 01:34 UTC
Resolved - Our Engineering team has completed work to identify remaining emails impacted by this incident. At this time, there remains a small subset of emails not being delivered to users, including some billing emails like finalized invoices and billing threshold alerts, App Platform alerts, and DBaaS alerts. Multiple teams are working together to ensure that these emails are able to be sent out correctly and that work will continue. 
At this time, we are going to resolve the incident due to critical email functionality being restored. If you have any concerns about the remaining emails impacted, or any questions about this incident, please open a support ticket from within your account. 
Thank you for your patience throughout this process and we apologize for the exten…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>DigitalOcean Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Transit Network connectivity in SGP1 region]]></title>
        <id>https://status.digitalocean.com/incidents/0t7lvzkd1hv0</id>
        <link href="https://status.digitalocean.com/incidents/0t7lvzkd1hv0"/>
        <updated>2022-08-11T15:15:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Aug 11, 15:15 UTC
Resolved - Our Engineering team has observed mitigated impact for this issue, due to actions taken upstream. Users should no longer experience any network latency/packet loss on Droplets and Droplet-based services from SGP to the EU region. App Platform health checks should now pass as expected. 
We apologize for the inconvenience. If you're still experiencing any issues, please open a support ticket.
Aug 11, 14:26 UTC
Investigating - Our Engineering team is aware of an upstream issue impacting network connectivity from SGP to the EU region. During this time, users may experience network latency/packet loss on Droplets and Droplet-based services from SGP to the EU region. 
We are also seeing App Platform health checks fail as a result of this issue.
Our Engineering team is investigating any possible mitigations to work around this upstream issue. We will provide an update as soon as further information is available.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>DigitalOcean Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>