<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2023-01-24T00:23:34.515Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2023-01-24T00:23:34.515Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Issues Creating New Frontline Instances on Twilio Accounts]]></title>
        <id>https://status.twilio.com/incidents/673qn9qzys69</id>
        <link href="https://status.twilio.com/incidents/673qn9qzys69"/>
        <updated>2023-01-24T00:13:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jan 23, 16:13 PST
Resolved - New account creation for Frontline in Twilio console is operating normally at this time. This incident is resolved.
Jan 23, 15:47 PST
Monitoring - New account creation for Frontline in Twilio console is now operating normally. We will continue to monitor for system stability. We'll provide another update in 30 minutes or as soon as more information becomes available.
Jan 23, 14:39 PST
Identified - Our engineers have identified the issue causing problems creating new Frontline instances on Twilio Accounts and are working to deploy a fix. 
Current workaround to create new Frontline instances is to use the following URL:
https://console.twilio.com/us1/develop/frontline?frameUrl=%2Fconsole%2Ffrontline%2Foverview%3Fx-target-region%3Dus1. 
We expect to provide another update in 2 hours or as soon as more information becomes available.
Jan 23, 13:40 PST
Update - We are continuing to investigate customer reports of issues creating new Frontline instances on Twilio accounts. We expect to provide another update in 1 hour or as soon as more information becomes available.
While we investigate, a workaround to create new Frontline instances is to use the following URL:
https://console.twilio.com/us1/develop/frontline?frameUrl=%2Fconsole%2Ffrontline%2Foverview%3Fx-target-region%3Dus1
Jan 23, 13:24 PST
Update - We are investigating customer reports of issues creating new Frontline instances on Twilio accounts. We expect to provide another update in 30 minutes or as soon as more information becomes available.
Jan 23, 13:14 PST
Investigating - We've become aware of a potential issue with creation of new accounts in console. Our engineering team has been alerted and is actively investigating. We will update as soon as we have more information.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Twilio Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Russia SMS Carrier Maintenance - Megafon]]></title>
        <id>https://status.twilio.com/incidents/7g55lf667clf</id>
        <link href="https://status.twilio.com/incidents/7g55lf667clf"/>
        <updated>2023-01-24T00:00:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jan 23, 16:00 PST
Completed - The scheduled maintenance has been completed.
Jan 23, 12:03 PST
In progress - Scheduled maintenance is currently in progress. We will provide updates as necessary.
Jan 19, 01:39 PST
Scheduled - The Megafon network in Russia is conducting a planned maintenance from 23 January 2023 at 12:00 PST until 23 January 2023 at 16:00 PST. During the maintenance window, there could be intermittent delays delivering SMS to and from Megafon Russia handsets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Twilio Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident: Some users may be experiencing issues with workflows]]></title>
        <id>https://status.slack.com//2023-01/9090b27a5ea06bce</id>
        <link href="https://status.slack.com//2023-01/9090b27a5ea06bce"/>
        <updated>2023-01-23T23:12:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We feel confident that affected users should no longer experience issues with workflows. Thank you for your patience while we looked into this.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Slack System Status</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident: A small percentage of users may see a delayed response when loading channels and threads]]></title>
        <id>https://status.slack.com//2023-01/bd2fc67bb1474e78</id>
        <link href="https://status.slack.com//2023-01/bd2fc67bb1474e78"/>
        <updated>2023-01-23T23:06:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We're seeing signs of recovery and feel confident that this issue is now resolved. Affected users should be see normal rates of responsiveness when loading channels and threads. Thank you for your patience while we looked into this.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Slack System Status</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Inbound Call Failures to a Subset of Twilio Argentina Phone Numbers]]></title>
        <id>https://status.twilio.com/incidents/nvd9z317snx5</id>
        <link href="https://status.twilio.com/incidents/nvd9z317snx5"/>
        <updated>2023-01-23T22:08:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jan 23, 14:08 PST
Update - We are continuing to observe a subset of call failures to Twilio Argentina phone numbers. We are currently working with our carrier partner to resolve the issue. We expect to provide another update in 4 hours or as soon as more information becomes available.
Jan 23, 12:11 PST
Update - We are continuing to observe a subset of call failures to Twilio Argentina phone numbers. We are currently working with our carrier partner to resolve the issue. We expect to provide another update in 2 hours or as soon as more information becomes available.
Jan 23, 11:13 PST
Investigating - We are observing a subset of call failures to Twilio Argentina phone numbers. We are currently working with our carrier partner to resolve the issue. We expect to provide another update in 1 hour or as soon as more information becomes available.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Twilio Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[France SMS Carrier Maintenance - Bouygues Telecom]]></title>
        <id>https://status.twilio.com/incidents/lj5wljh7jsh3</id>
        <link href="https://status.twilio.com/incidents/lj5wljh7jsh3"/>
        <updated>2023-01-23T22:00:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jan 23, 14:00 PST
In progress - Scheduled maintenance is currently in progress. We will provide updates as necessary.
Dec 23, 21:27 PST
Scheduled - The Bouygues Telecom network in France is conducting a planned maintenance from 23 January 2023 at 14:00 PST until 23 January 2023 at 21:00 PST. During the maintenance window, there could be intermittent delays delivering SMS to and from Bouygues Telecom handsets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Twilio Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[On Call Engineers are Investigating Issues With Creation of New Accounts]]></title>
        <id>https://status.twilio.com/incidents/7m2cr5ylx4jg</id>
        <link href="https://status.twilio.com/incidents/7m2cr5ylx4jg"/>
        <updated>2023-01-23T21:10:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jan 23, 13:10 PST
Resolved - Our monitoring systems have detected a potential issue with New Account creation. Our engineering team has been alerted and is actively investigating. We will update as soon as we have more information.
**************************Please delete before using************************
Do your best to associate a component (in Operational state) and include the affected product or problem symptom in the alerted posting. This way we can ensure that customers get meaningful updates/notifications from us. 
**************************Please delete before using************************]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Twilio Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[United Arab Emirates SMS Carrier Maintenance - Etisalat]]></title>
        <id>https://status.twilio.com/incidents/4fxbr0807kdl</id>
        <link href="https://status.twilio.com/incidents/4fxbr0807kdl"/>
        <updated>2023-01-23T20:02:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jan 23, 12:02 PST
In progress - Scheduled maintenance is currently in progress. We will provide updates as necessary.
Jan 17, 00:20 PST
Scheduled - The Etisalat network in United Arab Emirates is conducting a planned maintenance from 23 January 2023 at 12:00 PST until 23 January 2023 at 18:00 PST. During the maintenance window, there could be intermittent delays delivering SMS to and from United Arab Emirates handsets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Twilio Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SMS Delivery Receipt Delays To XL network in Indonesia over Registered Sender ID]]></title>
        <id>https://status.twilio.com/incidents/tvr3v0wt5j77</id>
        <link href="https://status.twilio.com/incidents/tvr3v0wt5j77"/>
        <updated>2023-01-23T17:16:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jan 23, 09:16 PST
Resolved - We are no longer experiencing SMS delivery delays when sending messages to XL network in Indonesia. This incident has been resolved.
Jan 23, 06:59 PST
Monitoring - We are observing recovery in SMS delivery delays when sending messages to XL network in Indonesia. We will continue monitoring the service to ensure a full recovery. We will provide another update in 2 hours or as soon as more information becomes available
Jan 23, 06:18 PST
Investigating - After a couple of minutes monitoring, we are still experiencing SMS delivery delays when sending messages XL network in Indonesia. Our engineers are working with our carrier partner to resolve the issue. We expect to provide another update in 1 hour or as soon as more information becomes available.
Jan 23, 06:01 PST
Monitoring - We are experiencing SMS delivery delays when sending messages XL network in Indonesia. Our engineers are working with our carrier partner to resolve the issue. We will provide another update in 2 hours or as soon as more information becomes available.
Jan 23, 05:42 PST
Investigating - We are experiencing SMS delivery delays when sending messages XL network in Indonesia. Our engineers are working with our carrier partner to resolve the issue. We will provide another update in 1 hour or as soon as more information becomes available.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Twilio Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unable to Preserve Sender ID to All networks in Chile resulting to Inbound SMS failures to a Subset of Twilio Chile Phone Numbers]]></title>
        <id>https://status.twilio.com/incidents/cnrhythqf4sz</id>
        <link href="https://status.twilio.com/incidents/cnrhythqf4sz"/>
        <updated>2023-01-23T16:32:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jan 23, 08:32 PST
Resolved - The issue affecting inbound SMS delivery delays when sending messages to a subset of Chile phone numbers has been resolved, and the service is functioning normally at this time.
Jan 23, 06:20 PST
Monitoring - We are observing recovery in inbound SMS delivery delays when sending messages to a subset of Chile phone numbers. We will continue monitoring the service to ensure a full recovery. We will provide another update in 2 hours or as soon as more information becomes available.
Jan 22, 23:15 PST
Update - We currently observe an issue in preserving sender IDs when sending SMS to all networks in Chile from a subset of Twilio Chile phone numbers resulting to Inbound SMS failures. Our engineers are working with our carrier partner to resolve the issue. We will prov…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Twilio Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[List your properties on maeva.com and get more bookings !]]></title>
        <id>255657</id>
        <link href="https://changelog.bookingsync.com/list-your-properties-on-maeva-com-and-get-more-bookings-!-255657"/>
        <updated>2023-01-23T09:36:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Partners
  
We are today happy to announce our new partnership with a big French company : maeva !
We have been working closely to the maeva team to offer a new direct integration to our Smily clients. Therefore, you can easily push your properties to the maeva websites and promote your listings to millions of French guests using this channel !

About maeva.com
maeva.com is a tour operator specialized in vacation rentals which promotes properties in leisure and tourist areas.
Acquired by the Pierre et Vacances group in 2001, maeva.com is now appreciated by French travelers for its general vacation rental site presenting more than 50,000 properties and having hosted more than 200,000 travelers in the summer of 2022.
Their offer was initially including tourist residences mainly but they now …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Audrey, Partnerships Development</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Notion page loading]]></title>
        <id>https://status.notion.so/incidents/kxnjf4xw20ty</id>
        <link href="https://status.notion.so/incidents/kxnjf4xw20ty"/>
        <updated>2023-01-20T00:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jan 19, 16:30 PST
Resolved - From approximately 4:45 PM to 6:00 PM Pacific time today, approximately 1% of users were unable to load Notion pages. This issue has been resolved and we are monitoring.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Notion Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident with Actions, Git Operations and Pages]]></title>
        <id>https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/n18j5g7wpg0s</id>
        <link href="https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/n18j5g7wpg0s"/>
        <updated>2023-01-19T20:51:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jan 19, 20:51 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Jan 19, 20:11 UTC
Update - We have applied a mitigation that has reduced impact to Actions, but error rates are still elevated. We continue to work with our dependency team on additional mitigations.
Jan 19, 19:31 UTC
Update - We are aware of an issue that impacts Actions, resulting in slow or failed jobs. Root cause in a dependency is understood and we are working with that team on a mitigation.
Jan 19, 18:49 UTC
Update - We are aware of an issue that impacts Actions, resulting in slow or failed jobs. Root cause in a dependency is understood and we are working with that team on a mitigation.
Jan 19, 18:07 UTC
Update - We are aware of an issue that impacts Actions, resulting in slow or failed jobs. Root cause in a dependency is understood and we are working with that team on a mitigation.
Jan 19, 17:27 UTC
Update - We are aware of an issue that impacts Actions artifact uploads and downloads, causing slow or failed jobs. We are investigating the root cause and will provide updates as we learn more.
Jan 19, 16:54 UTC
Update - We are observing an issue that impacts Actions artifact uploads and downloads, causing slow or failed jobs. We are investigating the root cause and will provide updates as we learn more.
Jan 19, 16:52 UTC
Update - Actions is experiencing degraded performance. We are continuing to investigate.
Jan 19, 16:49 UTC
Update - Git Operations is operating normally.
Jan 19, 16:09 UTC
Update - Pages is experiencing degraded performance. We are continuing to investigate.
Jan 19, 15:57 UTC
Investigating - We are investigating reports of degraded performance for Git Operations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GitHub Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident: Some customers may be missing channels and DMs in their sidebar]]></title>
        <id>https://status.slack.com//2023-01/e7a6c99fb49d6b09</id>
        <link href="https://status.slack.com//2023-01/e7a6c99fb49d6b09"/>
        <updated>2023-01-19T14:35:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Issue summary: 

From January 18th, 2023 7:45AM to 8:46PM PST some users experienced issues with missing channels and DMs in their sidebar. This affected only users of free teams.


This was due to a feature rollout which was rolled back and the issue is now resolved.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Slack System Status</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident with Actions and Pages]]></title>
        <id>https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/z2j6pjg527p6</id>
        <link href="https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/z2j6pjg527p6"/>
        <updated>2023-01-19T02:21:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jan 19, 02:21 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Jan 19, 01:54 UTC
Update - Actions is experiencing degraded performance. We are continuing to investigate.
Jan 19, 01:48 UTC
Investigating - We are investigating reports of degraded performance for Pages.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GitHub Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident with Copilot]]></title>
        <id>https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/tyk95n0z3pql</id>
        <link href="https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/tyk95n0z3pql"/>
        <updated>2023-01-18T20:16:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jan 18, 20:16 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Jan 18, 19:50 UTC
Update - We are investigating reports of issues with service(s): Copilot. We see authentication failures for a small percentage of users. We are investigating the root cause and will update as we learn more.
Jan 18, 19:00 UTC
Update - We are investigating reports of issues with service(s): Copilot. We see authentication failures for a small percentage of users. We are investigating the root cause and will update as we learn more.
Jan 18, 18:16 UTC
Investigating - We are investigating reports of degraded performance for Copilot.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GitHub Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RESOLVED: We're investigating reports of an issue with Google Meet. We will provide more information shortly. The affected users are able to access Google Meet, but are seeing error messages, high latency, and/or other unexpected behavior.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.google.com/appsstatus/dashboard/incidents/3U9C1tA43Nd5E3nWhDDY</id>
        <link href="https://www.google.com/appsstatus/dashboard/incidents/3U9C1tA43Nd5E3nWhDDY"/>
        <updated>2023-01-18T19:03:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p> Incident began at <strong>2023-01-18 07:45</strong> and ended at <strong>2023-01-18 14:35</strong> <span>(times are in <strong>Coordinated Universal Time (UTC)</strong>).</span></p><div class="cBIRi14aVDP__status-update-text"><h1>Mini Incident Report</h1>
<p>We apologize for the inconvenience this service disruption may have caused. We would like to provide some information about this incident below. Please note, this information is based on our best knowledge at the time of posting and is subject to change as our investigation continues. If you have experienced impact outside of what is listed below, please reach out to Google Cloud Support using <a href="https://cloud.google.com/support">https://cloud.google.com/support</a>  or to Google Workspace Support using help article <a href="https://support.google.com/a/answer/1047213">https://support.google.com/a/answer/1047213</a>.</p>
<p>(All Times US/Pacific)</p>
<p><strong>Incident Start:</strong> 17 January 2023 23:45</p>
<p><strong>Incident End:</strong> 18 January 2023 06:35</p>
<p><strong>Duration:</strong> 6 hours, 50 minutes</p>
<p><strong>Affected Services and Features:</strong></p>
<p>Google Meet - Live stream</p>
<p><strong>Regions/Zones:</strong> Global</p>
<p><strong>Description:</strong></p>
<p>Google Meet experienced an issue in which users trying to watch livestreams received errors for 6 hours and 50 minutes. From preliminary analysis, the root cause of the issue was identified as a recent rollout to the live stream player. Google will be completing a full IR in the following days that will provide a full root cause.</p>
<p><strong>Customer Impact:</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Users who accessed Meet livestreams from clients other than iOS, Android, or Safari received an error “This video format is not supported” instead of a stream.</li>
</ul>
</div><hr><p>Affected products: Google Meet</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Workspace Status Dashboard Updates</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Some users are receiving incorrect block and member limit warnings]]></title>
        <id>https://status.notion.so/incidents/g2jhynfpdlxj</id>
        <link href="https://status.notion.so/incidents/g2jhynfpdlxj"/>
        <updated>2023-01-18T01:25:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jan 17, 17:25 PST
Resolved - We have implemented a fix and confirmed the issue is resolved. Users should no longer be receiving incorrect member and block limit warnings. You may need to refresh Notion to see the fixed version.
Jan 17, 16:29 PST
Update - We are continuing to work on a fix for this issue.
Jan 17, 16:29 PST
Identified - There is currently an issue where some users are incorrectly receiving block and member limit warnings. We have identified the root cause and a fix is in progress.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Notion Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident: Users may experience issues accessing or loading Slack, have trouble creating posts, and using Workflow Builder.]]></title>
        <id>https://status.slack.com//2023-01/592b7776e9a7fdfa</id>
        <link href="https://status.slack.com//2023-01/592b7776e9a7fdfa"/>
        <updated>2023-01-17T23:06:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Issue summary:

From January 16th, 2023 04:59 to 08:38 AM PST, some users experienced issues creating Posts, using workflows, and trouble accessing Slack.  


We traced this back to an issue with our internal DNS configuration. Once this was identified and resolved, functionality was restored to all impacted users.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Slack System Status</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident: Some Android users may be experiencing issues when trying to access a workspace]]></title>
        <id>https://status.slack.com//2023-01/61694d1ccb108116</id>
        <link href="https://status.slack.com//2023-01/61694d1ccb108116"/>
        <updated>2023-01-17T09:55:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Issue summary:

From January 10th 04:11 AM PST to January 16th 07:54 PM PST, some of our fellow Slack colleagues were unable to access their workspaces on Android. We're happy to share that this issue was specifically related to our internal testing app, having no impact on the Slack production app nor our Customers.


This issue has been resolved and will have no impact on our future Android app releases.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Slack System Status</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TS-2023-001]]></title>
        <id>https://tailscale.com/security-bulletins/#ts-2023-001/</id>
        <link href="https://tailscale.com/security-bulletins/#ts-2023-001/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-17T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Description: An issue in the Tailscale coordination server allowed a malicious individual to share nodes from other tailnets to themselves, if they knew the node ID of the target.
What happened?
A bug in Tailscale’s node sharing logic allowed the creation of sharing invitations by unauthorized users. A malicious individual who knew a target node’s database ID could generate and accept a sharing invite for that node without being an admin of the target node’s tailnet.
This was possible for any node in any tailnet, as long as the individual knew the target’s node ID. The node ID is an integer used in the admin panel’s database, and is not related to the node “StableID” that is visible to Tailscale clients. A node’s ID is only visible in the API or admin console, by admins of either the node’s tailnet or a tailnet to which that node has already been shared. IDs are random 64-bit numbers that are not sequential or otherwise easily guessable.
The bug was introduced on 2022-09-14, reported to us on 2023-01-11, and remediated on 2023-01-12.
Who is affected?
All tailnets with nodes are affected.
What is the impact?
This vulnerability was not triggered or exploited. Analysis of tailnet logs shows that no unauthorized shares were created or accepted while the vulnerability was present, except as part of the proof of concept from the individual who reported the vulnerability.
Admins of a tailnet can review nodes that are shared out of their tailnet in the admin console. Sharing invites are logged as events in configuration audit logs. Admins can also review invites created and accepted in their configuration audit logs in the admin console.
What do I need to do?
No action is required. Tailscale has deployed a fix to the coordination server as of 2023-01-12, and verified that the vulnerability was not exploited.
Credits
We would like to thank Benjamin Roberts (tsujamin) for reporting this issue.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Security Bulletins on Tailscale</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Servers down]]></title>
        <id>https://status.notion.so/incidents/l3glrt4dhc6p</id>
        <link href="https://status.notion.so/incidents/l3glrt4dhc6p"/>
        <updated>2023-01-16T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jan 16, 09:00 PST
Resolved - Notion was down between 8:56 - 9:12 AM PT. Service is now recovered.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Notion Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident with Actions]]></title>
        <id>https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/f3kthhhjt9ss</id>
        <link href="https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/f3kthhhjt9ss"/>
        <updated>2023-01-16T16:43:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jan 16, 16:43 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Jan 16, 16:31 UTC
Update - We found an issue that caused high database replication lag, leading to issues visible in multiple services. We have resolved this issue and are expecting services to become healthy once queues drain.
Jan 16, 15:51 UTC
Investigating - We are investigating reports of degraded performance for Actions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GitHub Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident: Some customers may be unable to complete SSO configuration]]></title>
        <id>https://status.slack.com//2023-01/86830b419c5578aa</id>
        <link href="https://status.slack.com//2023-01/86830b419c5578aa"/>
        <updated>2023-01-16T09:47:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[From January 6th at 8:42 AM PST to January 15th at 10:00 PM PST, some users were running into issues when completing their SSO configuration. In the SSO settings the "Test Configuration" button led to an error message page.

We identified a recent code change as the cause of the issue and a fix was launched to correct it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Slack System Status</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident with Codespaces]]></title>
        <id>https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/hzgtxb033mym</id>
        <link href="https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/hzgtxb033mym"/>
        <updated>2023-01-14T16:58:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jan 14, 16:58 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Jan 14, 16:09 UTC
Update - We are investigating issues with Codespaces port forwarding. Users may be able to use the desktop client as a workaround.
Jan 14, 15:13 UTC
Investigating - We are investigating reports of degraded performance for Codespaces.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GitHub Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident with Copilot]]></title>
        <id>https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/n6wxc7xwrk1z</id>
        <link href="https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/n6wxc7xwrk1z"/>
        <updated>2023-01-12T04:55:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jan 12, 04:55 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Jan 12, 04:51 UTC
Update - Some Copilot plans were impacted by a recent backend change causing those users to see an error that access has ended.  We have applied a change to correct this and are seeing full recovery.
Jan 12, 03:59 UTC
Investigating - We are investigating reports of degraded performance for Copilot.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GitHub Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Make intermittent login issues]]></title>
        <id>https://status.make.com/incidents/0zz20hbhy112</id>
        <link href="https://status.make.com/incidents/0zz20hbhy112"/>
        <updated>2023-01-11T16:36:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jan 11, 17:36 CET
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Jan 11, 12:00 CET
Monitoring - The root cause of the issue has been identified and a remedy is already in place . Some users might have experienced troubles with logging in to the platform whilst we can confirm that there was no impact on running scenarios . We are actively monitoring the situation .
Jan 11, 11:37 CET
Investigating - We are currently experiencing intermittent issues when logging in to make zones . We are actively investigating the issue and working on a solution.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Make Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident with Actions and Git Operations]]></title>
        <id>https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/00km0kwpz23b</id>
        <link href="https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/00km0kwpz23b"/>
        <updated>2023-01-10T18:14:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jan 10, 18:14 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Jan 10, 17:54 UTC
Update - Some action hosted runners are experiencing longer than normal run times.
Jan 10, 17:22 UTC
Update - Actions is experiencing degraded performance. We are still investigating and will provide an update when we have one.
Jan 10, 17:04 UTC
Investigating - We are investigating reports of degraded performance for Git Operations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GitHub Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[500 Errors Across Multiple Endpoints]]></title>
        <id>https://airbnbapi.statuspage.io/incidents/dz7fk8vqftbf</id>
        <link href="https://airbnbapi.statuspage.io/incidents/dz7fk8vqftbf"/>
        <updated>2023-01-09T23:10:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jan  9, 15:10 PST
Resolved - From 14:00-15:00 Pacific Time (PT), we saw increased 500 errors for multiple API endpoints, including reservations, listings and threads. The issue is now identified and resolved, please retry any failed requests during this time. Apologies for the inconvenience caused due to this incident and thank you for your patience and understanding.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Airbnb API Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident with Actions]]></title>
        <id>https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/ffwkvn9j77d1</id>
        <link href="https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/ffwkvn9j77d1"/>
        <updated>2023-01-07T23:30:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jan  7, 23:30 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Jan  7, 23:25 UTC
Update - We are investigating reports of timeouts with Actions. We will continue to keep users updated on progress towards mitigation.
Jan  7, 22:50 UTC
Investigating - We are investigating reports of degraded performance for Actions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GitHub Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Delay in email delivery due to third-party outage]]></title>
        <id>https://status.rippling.com/incidents/mbk89dt1vc41</id>
        <link href="https://status.rippling.com/incidents/mbk89dt1vc41"/>
        <updated>2023-01-05T15:49:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jan  5, 15:49 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Jan  5, 02:25 UTC
Monitoring - A fix has been implemented and we are monitoring the results.
Jan  5, 01:45 UTC
Update - We are continuing to monitor our third-party service provider for updates. Service has not been restored by the third-party email provider. Once service is restored, the majority of emails that were not sent during the outage will be resent.
Jan  5, 01:14 UTC
Update - We are continuing to monitor our third-party service provider for updates. Service has not been restored by the third-party email provider. Once service is restored, the majority of emails that were not sent during the outage will be resent.
Jan  5, 00:38 UTC
Update - Service has not been restored by the third-party email provider. Once service is restored, the majority of emails that were not sent during the outage will be resent.
Jan  5, 00:17 UTC
Identified - A fix has been implemented by the third-party service. We are working to confirm service has been restored.
Jan  4, 23:31 UTC
Investigating - Our third-party email delivery provider has been experiencing an outage since Jan 4th, 2:10 PM PST, causing a delay in notification delivery for all Rippling emails (including password resets). We are investigating this issue with the third-party provider.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rippling Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Issues completing a MFA authenticator challenge]]></title>
        <id>https://status.rippling.com/incidents/zgg7pyzjl7tr</id>
        <link href="https://status.rippling.com/incidents/zgg7pyzjl7tr"/>
        <updated>2023-01-03T23:07:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jan  3, 23:07 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Jan  3, 21:33 UTC
Monitoring - A fix has been implemented and we are monitoring the results.
Jan  3, 20:35 UTC
Identified - The issue has been identified and a fix is being implemented.
Jan  3, 20:27 UTC
Investigating - Users asked to complete an MFA challenge are unable to advance past the page. We are investigating this issue]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rippling Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident with Codespaces]]></title>
        <id>https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/srn4b1fjxp8h</id>
        <link href="https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/srn4b1fjxp8h"/>
        <updated>2023-01-01T18:28:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jan  1, 18:28 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Jan  1, 17:28 UTC
Update - We have identified the issue and are deploying a fix. We will update our status when the fix is fully deployed.
Jan  1, 16:44 UTC
Update - Codespaces is experiencing issues with web connectivity from GitHub.com. The desktop client can still be used to launch or connect to codespaces."
Jan  1, 16:33 UTC
Investigating - We are investigating reports of degraded performance for Codespaces.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GitHub Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident with Codespaces]]></title>
        <id>https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/1whd66ydswnx</id>
        <link href="https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/1whd66ydswnx"/>
        <updated>2022-12-31T01:47:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dec 31, 01:47 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Dec 31, 01:39 UTC
Update - We are continuing mitigation for an issue impacting some Codespaces customers. We will keep you updated on progress.
Dec 31, 01:12 UTC
Update - We are continuing to work on mitigation for an issue impacting some Codespaces customers. We will continue to keep you updated on progress.
Dec 31, 00:39 UTC
Update - We identified an issue that impacts some Codespaces customers and are working on mitigation.We will continue to keep you updated on progress.
Dec 31, 00:07 UTC
Investigating - We are investigating reports of degraded performance for Codespaces.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GitHub Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>