<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2023-06-28T00:26:31.013Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2023-06-28T00:26:31.013Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scheduled infrastructure maintenance]]></title>
        <id>https://status.make.com/incidents/xg8t6gl5shmp</id>
        <link href="https://status.make.com/incidents/xg8t6gl5shmp"/>
        <updated>2023-06-28T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[THIS IS A SCHEDULED EVENT Jun 28, 09:00 - 11:00 CEST
Jun 22, 17:01 CEST
Scheduled - Please note that we will be undergoing scheduled infrastructure maintenance on Wednesday June 28th between 09:00 AM and 11:00 AM CEST on European zones. During this maintenance you can expect few short service interruptions.
During the maintenance the us1.make.celonis.com, us1.make.com websites login might be temporarily affected.
Some webhooks and shared hooks processed at that time might be temporarily affected as well.
There will be no impact on eu1.make.com, eu2.make.com and eu1.make.celonis.com.
We do not expect any data loss.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Make Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Canada Account Security Service Partner Maintenance]]></title>
        <id>https://status.twilio.com/incidents/rhffd4zj5s2k</id>
        <link href="https://status.twilio.com/incidents/rhffd4zj5s2k"/>
        <updated>2023-06-28T06:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[THIS IS A SCHEDULED EVENT Jun 27, 23:00 PDT  -  Jun 28, 03:00 PDT
Jun 22, 05:32 PDT
Scheduled - Our Service Partner is conducting a planned maintenance from 27 June 2023 at 23:00 PDT until 28 June 2023 at 03:00 PDT. During the maintenance window, there could be intermittent API request failures for the following destination: Canada
Impacted Products: Silent Network Authentication (SNA), Lookup SIM Swap, Identity Match]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Twilio Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scheduled infrastructure maintenance]]></title>
        <id>https://status.make.com/incidents/jq61fcn60dfm</id>
        <link href="https://status.make.com/incidents/jq61fcn60dfm"/>
        <updated>2023-06-28T03:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[THIS IS A SCHEDULED EVENT Jun 28, 05:00 - 07:00 CEST
Jun 22, 16:59 CEST
Scheduled - Please note that we will be undergoing scheduled infrastructure maintenance on Wednesday June 28th between 05:00 AM and 07:00 AM CEST on European zones. During this maintenance you can expect few short service interruptions.
During the maintenance the eu1.make.celonis.com, eu1.make.com and eu2.make.com websites login might be temporarily affected.
Some webhooks and shared hooks processed at that time might be temporarily affected as well.
There will be no impact on us1.make.com and us1.make.celonis.com.
We do not expect any data loss.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Make Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ireland Voice Carrier Partner Maintenance]]></title>
        <id>https://status.twilio.com/incidents/gl3c2wd3sq6g</id>
        <link href="https://status.twilio.com/incidents/gl3c2wd3sq6g"/>
        <updated>2023-06-27T23:00:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jun 27, 16:00 PDT
Completed - The scheduled maintenance has been completed.
Jun 27, 15:01 PDT
In progress - Scheduled maintenance is currently in progress. We will provide updates as necessary.
Jun 20, 10:02 PDT
Update - Our Voice carrier partner is conducting a planned maintenance from 27 June 2023 at 15:00 PDT until 27 June 2023 at 16:00 PDT. During the maintenance window, there could be intermittent call disconnects and failures for calls to and from a subset of Twilio Ireland phone numbers.
Jun 20, 10:00 PDT
Update - We will be undergoing scheduled maintenance during this time.
Jun 20, 09:56 PDT
Scheduled - Our Voice carrier partner is conducting a planned maintenance from 27 June 2023 at 15:00 PDT until 27 June 2023 at 16:00 PDT. During the maintenance window, there could be intermittent call disconnects and failures for calls to and from a subset of Twilio Ireland phone numbers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Twilio Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident: Some users may be experiencing issues loading threads or connecting to Slack.]]></title>
        <id>https://status.slack.com//2023-06/511f645055892966</id>
        <link href="https://status.slack.com//2023-06/511f645055892966"/>
        <updated>2023-06-27T22:55:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Issue Summary:


From 12:49pm PDT on Tuesday June 27th 2023 to 13:20 PDT on Tuesday, June 27th, 2023, approximately 1% of users were seeing issues loading Slack.


The issue was caused by Slack not allocating resources effectively in our backend database. Once resources were reallocated, the issue was resolved. Our engineering team is taking a look at the cause to make sure it does not occur in the future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Slack System Status</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[United Kingdom Account Security Carrier Partner Maintenance]]></title>
        <id>https://status.twilio.com/incidents/m3lh8wb7bcvn</id>
        <link href="https://status.twilio.com/incidents/m3lh8wb7bcvn"/>
        <updated>2023-06-27T22:01:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jun 27, 15:01 PDT
In progress - Scheduled maintenance is currently in progress. We will provide updates as necessary.
Jun 22, 00:01 PDT
Scheduled - Our Carrier Partner EE UK is conducting a planned maintenance from 27 June 2023 at 15:00 PDT until 28 June 2023 at 00:00 PDT. During the maintenance window, there could be intermittent API request failures for EE UK customers.
Impacted Products: SNA, Lookup SIM Swap and Identity Match]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Twilio Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident: Users unable to create user groups]]></title>
        <id>https://status.slack.com//2023-06/e9d38ae3f06e5cfe</id>
        <link href="https://status.slack.com//2023-06/e9d38ae3f06e5cfe"/>
        <updated>2023-06-27T20:50:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Issue Summary:

From June 26, 2023 at 8:23 AM PDT to June 27, 2023 2:03 AM PDT, some users encountered an error message when creating user groups.


This issue was a result of a change to the user group creation flow. Once this change was reverted, the ability to create user groups was restored for all impacted users.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Slack System Status</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident: Issues sending messages with files]]></title>
        <id>https://status.slack.com//2023-06/40f7ccc7ae160447</id>
        <link href="https://status.slack.com//2023-06/40f7ccc7ae160447"/>
        <updated>2023-06-27T20:42:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Issue Summary:

From 00:00 AM PDT on Saturday, June 24th, 2023 to Monday, June 26th, 2023 10:18 AM PDT, some users on the desktop and browser apps encountered a 'failed to send' error message when trying to send messages with files attached. 


The issue was caused by a recent change to how file permissions are read when files are shared. This change was reverted, which resolved the problem for impacted users. 


Our team is making efforts to prevent issues like this from reoccurring in the future. Thank you for your patience while we sorted out this issue.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Slack System Status</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Issues When Opening the Verify Service Settings in the Twilio Console]]></title>
        <id>https://status.twilio.com/incidents/rmnr0pkhbl68</id>
        <link href="https://status.twilio.com/incidents/rmnr0pkhbl68"/>
        <updated>2023-06-27T19:43:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jun 27, 12:43 PDT
Resolved - Verify service settings in the Twilio Console has been resolved and is operating normally at this time.
Jun 27, 12:15 PDT
Monitoring - Opening the Verify service settings in the Twilio Console is now operating normally. We will continue to monitor for system stability. We'll provide another update in 30 minutes or as soon as more information becomes available.
Jun 27, 11:43 PDT
Update - We are investigating an issue when opening the Verify service settings in the Twilio Console. We expect to provide another update in 1 hour or as soon as more information becomes available
Jun 27, 11:29 PDT
Investigating - Our monitoring systems have detected a potential issue with the Verify settings in the Twilio Console. Our engineering team has been alerted and is actively investigating. We will update as soon as we have more information.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Twilio Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vietnam SMS Carrier Maintenance - Vietnamobile]]></title>
        <id>https://status.twilio.com/incidents/hpm2gr6j6464</id>
        <link href="https://status.twilio.com/incidents/hpm2gr6j6464"/>
        <updated>2023-06-27T19:00:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jun 27, 12:00 PDT
Completed - The scheduled maintenance has been completed.
Jun 27, 10:02 PDT
In progress - Scheduled maintenance is currently in progress. We will provide updates as necessary.
Jun 26, 08:05 PDT
Scheduled - The Vietnamobile network in Vietnam is conducting an emergency maintenance from 27 June 2023 at 10:00 PDT until 27 June 2023 at 12:00 PDT. During the maintenance window, there could be intermittent delays delivering SMS to and from Vietnamobile Vietnam handsets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Twilio Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SMS Delivery Delays to AIS Network in Thailand]]></title>
        <id>https://status.twilio.com/incidents/rwmb53pg5l4r</id>
        <link href="https://status.twilio.com/incidents/rwmb53pg5l4r"/>
        <updated>2023-06-27T16:29:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jun 27, 09:29 PDT
Resolved - We are no longer experiencing SMS delivery delays when sending messages to AIS network in Thailand. This incident has been resolved.
Jun 27, 07:29 PDT
Monitoring - We are observing recovery in SMS delivery delays when sending messages to AIS network in Thailand. We will continue monitoring the service to ensure a full recovery. We will provide another update in 2 hours or as soon as more information becomes available.
Jun 27, 06:12 PDT
Update - We continue experiencing SMS delivery delays when sending messages to AIS network in Thailand. Our engineers are working with our carrier partner to resolve the issue. We will provide another update in 2 hours or as soon as more information becomes available.
Jun 27, 05:12 PDT
Investigating - We are experiencing SMS delivery delays when sending messages to AIS network in Thailand. Our engineers are working with our carrier partner to resolve the issue. We will provide another update in 1 hour or as soon as more information becomes available.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Twilio Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SMS Delivery Delays to MCI Network in Iran]]></title>
        <id>https://status.twilio.com/incidents/jqt3zlym769x</id>
        <link href="https://status.twilio.com/incidents/jqt3zlym769x"/>
        <updated>2023-06-27T14:05:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jun 27, 07:05 PDT
Resolved - We are no longer experiencing SMS delivery delays when sending messages to MCI network in Iran. This incident has been resolved.
Jun 27, 05:11 PDT
Monitoring - We are observing successful SMS delivery delays when sending messages to MCI network in Iran. We will continue to monitor to ensure full service recovery. We expect to provide another update in 2 hours or as soon as more information becomes available.
Jun 27, 03:55 PDT
Update - We are continuing to experience SMS delivery delays when sending messages to MCI network in Iran. Our engineers are working with our carrier partner to resolve the issue. We will provide another update in 2 hours or as soon as more information becomes available.
Jun 27, 02:55 PDT
Investigating - We are experiencing SMS delivery delays when sending messages to MCI network in Iran. Our engineers are working with our carrier partner to resolve the issue. We will provide another update in 1 hours or as soon as more information becomes available.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Twilio Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Connectivity Lost on ~5% of Super SIM Devices on AT&T]]></title>
        <id>https://status.twilio.com/incidents/l61mssxxscyh</id>
        <link href="https://status.twilio.com/incidents/l61mssxxscyh"/>
        <updated>2023-06-27T08:29:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jun 27, 01:29 PDT
Resolved - Between 7:30 AM UTC and 8:00 AM UTC we observed ~5%  of active data sessions on Super SIM being dropped and quickly reconnected. Devices that attempted to reconnect immediately after losing connectivity should have been able to successfully reconnect to the redundant instances while the impacted one recovered. However, we kindly suggest that customers reset the connectivity through the console if they notice that some of their SIM cards are still experiencing issues. This can often help re-establish a stable connection for the affected devices.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Twilio Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing Google Analytics 4 ⚡]]></title>
        <id>268097</id>
        <link href="https://changelog.bookingsync.com/introducing-google-analytics-4-268097"/>
        <updated>2023-06-27T08:11:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Improvement
  
We would like to inform you that we have recently updated our data tracking system through our Website app to adjust to Google Analytics 4.
This new version offers improved features for tracking and analyzing the performance of your website.
However, for this update to be effective and to ensure your data’s tracking, we kindly ask you to replace the Google Analytics key in the preferences of your Website application.
This key is essential for your website data to be properly collected and analyzed.
What should I do to update my key?
We invite you to follow the instructions below to make this update:
Log in to your Google Analytics account.
Go to the “Admin” section of your account.
Select the property of your website.
Click on “Data Stream” and then open the window to get your Google Analytics 4 key code.
Copy the new Google Analytics 4 key and replace the old key in the Preferences of your Website application.
If needed, you can access the video instructions here.
Thank you for your cooperation in this important update. For your information, your GA3 key is still valid until the 1st of July 2023.
If you have any questions or need any help, please do not hesitate to contact us via this form.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ella, Head of Customer Care and OnBoarding team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SMS Carrier Partner Maintenance]]></title>
        <id>https://status.twilio.com/incidents/773bjtfg4pz9</id>
        <link href="https://status.twilio.com/incidents/773bjtfg4pz9"/>
        <updated>2023-06-27T04:00:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jun 26, 21:00 PDT
Completed - The scheduled maintenance has been completed.
Jun 26, 20:01 PDT
In progress - Scheduled maintenance is currently in progress. We will provide updates as necessary.
Jun 22, 15:59 PDT
Scheduled - Our SMS carrier partner in Italy and Greece is conducting a planned maintenance from 26 June 2023 at 20:00 PDT until 26 June 2023 at 21:00 PDT. During the maintenance window, there could be intermittent delays delivering SMS to and from Greece and Italy handsets]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Twilio Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Russia SMS Carrier Maintenance - K-Telecom]]></title>
        <id>https://status.twilio.com/incidents/t1z9yq1rz3h7</id>
        <link href="https://status.twilio.com/incidents/t1z9yq1rz3h7"/>
        <updated>2023-06-27T03:01:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jun 26, 20:01 PDT
Completed - The scheduled maintenance has been completed.
Jun 26, 16:00 PDT
In progress - Scheduled maintenance is currently in progress. We will provide updates as necessary.
Jun 26, 07:17 PDT
Scheduled - The K-Telecom network in Russia is conducting an emergency maintenance from 26 June 2023 at 16:00 PDT until 26 June 2023 at 20:00 PDT. During the maintenance window, there could be intermittent delays delivering SMS to and from K-Telecom Russia handsets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Twilio Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bulgaria SMS Carrier Maintenance - Yettel]]></title>
        <id>https://status.twilio.com/incidents/ryc2fb9x4qyj</id>
        <link href="https://status.twilio.com/incidents/ryc2fb9x4qyj"/>
        <updated>2023-06-27T03:00:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jun 26, 20:00 PDT
Completed - The scheduled maintenance has been completed.
Jun 26, 14:00 PDT
In progress - Scheduled maintenance is currently in progress. We will provide updates as necessary.
Jun 26, 04:32 PDT
Scheduled - The Yettel network in Bulgaria is conducting an emergency maintenance from 26 June 2023 at 14:00 PDT until 26 June 2023 at 20:00 PDT. During the maintenance window, there could be intermittent delays delivering SMS to and from Yettel Bulgaria handsets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Twilio Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RESOLVED: We're aware of a problem with Google Sheets affecting a majority of users. We will provide an update by Jun 13, 2023, 2:00 PM UTC detailing when we expect to resolve the problem. Please note that this resolution time is an estimate and may change. The affected users are able to access Google Sheets, but are seeing error messages, high latency, and/or other unexpected behavior.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.google.com/appsstatus/dashboard/incidents/bRkLdn3pfJQz2LbdanpR</id>
        <link href="https://www.google.com/appsstatus/dashboard/incidents/bRkLdn3pfJQz2LbdanpR"/>
        <updated>2023-06-26T16:45:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p> Incident began at <strong>2023-06-07 20:00</strong> and ended at <strong>2023-06-13 17:50</strong> <span>(times are in <strong>Coordinated Universal Time (UTC)</strong>).</span></p><div class="cBIRi14aVDP__status-update-text"><h1>Incident Report</h1>
<h2>Summary</h2>
<p>From 7 June 2023 at 13:00 to 13 June 2023 at 10:50 US/Pacific, Google Sheets users experienced issues fetching finance data using the built-in GOOGLEFINANCE() function. The total impact duration lasted 5 days, 21 hours, 50 minutes.</p>
<h2>Root Cause</h2>
<p>Google engineers identified a configuration change that unintentionally triggered this issue during a recent rollout. The change caused requests to return an “N/A” value, which ultimately impacted Sheets end users&#39; ability to fetch data using the built-in function.</p>
<h2>Remediation and Prevention</h2>
<p>An internal user alerted Google engineers to the issue on 13 June 2023 at 03:35 US/Pacific. Google engineers quickly identified the change that was deployed to a backend component. To mitigate the issue, engineers rolled back the change, and services were fully restored 13 June 2023 at 10:50 US/Pacific.</p>
<p>Google is committed to preventing a repeat of this issue in the future and is completing the following actions:</p>
<ul>
<li>Extend our monitoring capabilities to identify similar issues faster.</li>
<li>Optimize our debugging tools to enable us to investigate similar issues faster.</li>
<li>Validate our test suite to ensure similar issues are eliminated before being deployed to production systems.</li>
</ul>
</div><hr><p>Affected products: Google Sheets</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Workspace Status Dashboard Updates</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v2021.12.31 Webhook Migration Enforcement - Phase 3]]></title>
        <id>https://airbnbapi.statuspage.io/incidents/3f2h5b7dp3vj</id>
        <link href="https://airbnbapi.statuspage.io/incidents/3f2h5b7dp3vj"/>
        <updated>2023-06-26T07:00:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jun 26, 00:00 PDT
In progress - Scheduled maintenance is currently in progress. We will provide updates as necessary.
Jun 23, 08:32 PDT
Scheduled - The deprecation date for API Webhook Version 2021.12.31 was May 31, 2023. Any applications that have not fully migrated webhooks will be automatically migrated to a newer version, which can result in application breakage.
Automatic webhook migration will occur in phases as detailed in https://developer.airbnb.com/docs/versioning-enforcement
Phase 3 will occur during the week of June 26th, 2023 and will automatically migrate all Critical booking sync check webhooks:
- check_availability
- make_reservation
- update_reservation]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Airbnb API Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Network Connectivity in AMS3]]></title>
        <id>https://status.digitalocean.com/incidents/506776wyjn35</id>
        <link href="https://status.digitalocean.com/incidents/506776wyjn35"/>
        <updated>2023-06-25T18:12:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jun 25, 18:12 UTC
Resolved - As of 15:31 UTC our Engineering team has confirmed that the issue impacting Networking in AMS3 region has been fully resolved.
From 07:40 UTC to 15:31 UTC, Users may have experienced network timeouts, packet loss, and/or increased latency interacting with the resources in the AMS3 region. The impact has been completely subsided and the network connectivity is back to normal for all the services in AMS3 region. 
If you continue to experience problems, please open a ticket with our Support team. Thank you for your patience and we apologize for the inconvenience.
Jun 25, 15:51 UTC
Monitoring - The network issues affecting our AMS3 region have been mitigated. Users should no longer experience packet loss/latency, timeouts, and related issues with Droplet-based services in those regions, including Droplets, Managed Kubernetes, and Managed Database. 
We will continue to monitor network conditions for a period of time to establish a return to pre-incident conditions.
Jun 25, 15:18 UTC
Investigating - Our Engineering team is investigating an issue impacting the networking in our AMS3 region. During this time, a subset of users may experience intermittent packet loss or increased latency while interacting with the resources in AMS3 region.
At the moment, all the droplet-based services appear to be impacted and the users can expect to see brief connectivity issues and interrupted traffic flows. This will also be impacting services including Spaces, Managed Kubernetes and Managed Databases as well. 
We apologize for the inconvenience and will share an update once we have more information.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>DigitalOcean Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident with Actions and Pull Requests]]></title>
        <id>https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/tcp7119jvq7y</id>
        <link href="https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/tcp7119jvq7y"/>
        <updated>2023-06-25T07:01:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jun 25, 07:01 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Jun 25, 06:41 UTC
Update - Actions is experiencing degraded performance. We are continuing to investigate.
Jun 25, 06:40 UTC
Investigating - We are investigating reports of degraded performance for Pull Requests.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GitHub Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v2021.12.31 Webhook Migration Enforcement - Phase 2]]></title>
        <id>https://airbnbapi.statuspage.io/incidents/vl5ppdvchsjb</id>
        <link href="https://airbnbapi.statuspage.io/incidents/vl5ppdvchsjb"/>
        <updated>2023-06-24T07:00:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jun 24, 00:00 PDT
Completed - The scheduled maintenance has been completed.
Jun 19, 00:00 PDT
In progress - Scheduled maintenance is currently in progress. We will provide updates as necessary.
Jun 16, 14:55 PDT
Scheduled - The deprecation date for API Webhook Version 2021.12.31 was May 31, 2023. Any applications that have not fully migrated webhooks will be automatically migrated to a newer version, which can result in application breakage.
Automatic webhook migration will occur in phases as detailed in https://developer.airbnb.com/docs/versioning-enforcement
Phase 2 will occur during the week of June 19th, 2023 and will automatically migrate all Messaging, Reviews, and Reservations webhooks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Airbnb API Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Event Processing in AMS3]]></title>
        <id>https://status.digitalocean.com/incidents/vyk14zgrg3kd</id>
        <link href="https://status.digitalocean.com/incidents/vyk14zgrg3kd"/>
        <updated>2023-06-24T01:36:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jun 24, 01:36 UTC
Resolved - As of 01:30 UTC, our Engineering team has confirmed full resolution of the issue with processing events in AMS3 region. All impacted events have been marked as failed and users should now be able to process events normally for Droplets and Droplet-based services like Load Balancers, Kubernetes or Database clusters, etc.
If you continue to experience problems, please open a ticket with our support team from your Cloud Control Panel.
Thank you for your patience and we apologize for any inconvenience.
Jun 24, 01:06 UTC
Monitoring - From 23:50 UTC to 00:30 UTC, our Engineering team observed an issue with processing events in our AMS3 region. 
Users may have experienced delays or errors while creating and deleting Droplets and Droplet-based products like Load Balancers, Kubernetes or Database clusters, etc. From 00:30 UTC, Users can try performing events/tasks that were failing earlier. 
At this time, our Engineering team is monitoring this incident. We will post an update as soon as we have further information.
Jun 24, 00:28 UTC
Investigating - Beginning 23:50 UTC, our Engineering team is investigating an issue with processing events in our AMS3 region. During this time users may experience delays or errors while creating and deleting Droplets and Droplet-based products like Load Balancers, Kubernetes, or Database clusters, etc.
As soon as we have further information to share, we'll post an update.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>DigitalOcean Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident: Users may be experiencing increased loading time or delays when switching between channels]]></title>
        <id>https://status.slack.com//2023-06/a8931305c8cbcf0e</id>
        <link href="https://status.slack.com//2023-06/a8931305c8cbcf0e"/>
        <updated>2023-06-24T00:09:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We have released a fix at this time, and customers should no longer be experiencing delays when loading channels, conversation history, or when switching between channels. Please send a note to feedback@slack.com if you continue to have any trouble.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Slack System Status</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Issues with sending commands to macOS devices]]></title>
        <id>https://status.rippling.com/incidents/psdc4zd8pnqd</id>
        <link href="https://status.rippling.com/incidents/psdc4zd8pnqd"/>
        <updated>2023-06-23T21:46:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jun 23, 21:46 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Jun 23, 21:20 UTC
Monitoring - A fix has been implemented and we are monitoring the results.
Jun 23, 18:57 UTC
Identified - The issue has been identified and a fix is being implemented.
Jun 23, 18:53 UTC
Investigating - When installing new Rippling MDM Enrollment profiles there maybe a delay in establishing a connection to the MDM server.  This may also cause issues for new installations of the Rippling agent.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rippling Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[500 Errors Across Multiple Endpoints]]></title>
        <id>https://airbnbapi.statuspage.io/incidents/l1v69r4fm1jx</id>
        <link href="https://airbnbapi.statuspage.io/incidents/l1v69r4fm1jx"/>
        <updated>2023-06-23T20:08:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jun 23, 13:08 PDT
Resolved - We are actively investigating an increased number of 500 errors across multiple endpoints. These errors started today (June 23, 2023) around 01:00 PM PDT. Our engineering teams are working to get everything up and running again and we will update you with the latest information as soon as possible.
The issue has been mitigated at 1:25PM PDT. Please apply any failed requests during the incident.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Airbnb API Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[500 Errors Across Multiple Endpoints]]></title>
        <id>https://airbnbapi.statuspage.io/incidents/tx6z0zm2rfmg</id>
        <link href="https://airbnbapi.statuspage.io/incidents/tx6z0zm2rfmg"/>
        <updated>2023-06-22T22:09:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jun 22, 15:09 PDT
Resolved - This incident has been mitigated. Please apply any failed requests that were made during the incident time.
Jun 22, 13:26 PDT
Investigating - We are actively investigating an increased number of 500 errors across multiple endpoints. These errors started today (June 22, 2023) around 12:30 PM PDT. Our engineering teams are working to get everything up and running again and we will update you with the latest information as soon as possible.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Airbnb API Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Degraded Functions Service]]></title>
        <id>https://status.digitalocean.com/incidents/9hwth0p75c6y</id>
        <link href="https://status.digitalocean.com/incidents/9hwth0p75c6y"/>
        <updated>2023-06-21T18:05:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jun 21, 18:05 UTC
Resolved - Our Engineering team has confirmed that the issue impacting our Functions service has been fully resolved. If you continue to experience any issues in relation to this incident please open a ticket with our support team. Thank you for your patience.
Jun 21, 17:11 UTC
Monitoring - Functions in BLR1 region are now restored to normal service. As of 17:00 UTC, all impact has been mitigated and users should no longer experience any issues with the Functions. We are monitoring the situation and will post an update once the incident is completely resolved.
Thank you for your patience and we apologize for the inconvenience.
Jun 21, 16:50 UTC
Update - Functions in FRA1 and LON1 are now restored to normal service. We continue work to remediate BLR1.
Our Engineering team has discovered that some Function invocations were duplicated, so a subset of users may have experienced that during the course of this incident.
We will post an update once the last region has returned to normal service.
Jun 21, 16:01 UTC
Identified - Our Engineering team has been working in order to restore the Functions service. At this time, normal service has been restored in most of the regions including AMS3, SGP1, TOR1, and SYD1.
We’re now working to fully remediate the remaining regions: BLR1, FRA1, and LON1. We will post an update as soon as that has completed. Thank you for your patience!
Jun 21, 15:43 UTC
Investigating - Beginning 14:37 UTC, our Engineering team has identified an issue impacting Functions in AMS3, BLR1, FRA1, LON1, SGP1, SYD1, and TOR1. During this time, users with standalone Functions or Functions deployed through Apps may experience performance degradation, leading to delays in Functions invocations and/or Functions working more slowly than normal.
Our team is working to mitigate the issue and we will provide an update as soon as possible.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>DigitalOcean Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Network Connectivity in European Regions]]></title>
        <id>https://status.digitalocean.com/incidents/bclmy32d12p0</id>
        <link href="https://status.digitalocean.com/incidents/bclmy32d12p0"/>
        <updated>2023-06-21T14:31:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jun 21, 14:31 UTC
Resolved - From 12:00 - 13:40 UTC our Engineering team observed an issue with network connectivity to US-EAST-1 and US-EAST-2 (AWS) from European datacenter regions including DigitalOcean's AMS, FRA & LON datatancers. During this time, a subset of users might have experienced high latency or errors while connecting to  services, including Droplets and Droplet-based products. We also received reports of issues in pushing/pulling images to and from DigitalOcean Container Registries. 
As of 13:40 UTC the impact has been subsided and users should no longer be facing network connectivity issues. We apologize for the inconcenience and if you are still experiencing issues or have any additional questions then please open a support ticket from within your account.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>DigitalOcean Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Issue affecting listings bedrooms, bathrooms and beds]]></title>
        <id>https://airbnbapi.statuspage.io/incidents/620bns7c4y3p</id>
        <link href="https://airbnbapi.statuspage.io/incidents/620bns7c4y3p"/>
        <updated>2023-06-20T21:10:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jun 20, 14:10 PDT
Resolved - This incident has been resolved. We have restored the correct bedroom, bathroom and bed count on the Listings API.
Jun 15, 20:37 PDT
Update - We have implemented a fix to restore the correct bedrooms, bathrooms and bed values on the Listings API and will continue to monitor this incident.
We apologize for any inconvenience this may cause and appreciate your understanding as we resolve this issue.
Jun 15, 14:38 PDT
Monitoring - We are currently addressing a bug that affects the bedroom, bathroom, and bed count on our Listings API. Due to a change in behavior of how bedrooms, bathrooms and beds interact with the Listing Rooms API, you might come across the following issues:
* On the Listings API, some listings might have the fields `bedrooms`,`bathrooms` and/or `beds` set to 0.
* On the Listings Rooms API, some rooms might have been created/deleted.
As of today, we have reverted the problematic behavior and are working diligently to restore the correct bedrooms, bathrooms, and beds values on the Listings API. To ensure that your Listing Rooms are accurately set, we kindly ask you to re-sync your data.
We apologize for any inconvenience this may cause and appreciate your understanding as we resolve this issue.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Airbnb API Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident with Actions]]></title>
        <id>https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/22qm4j1kvn0h</id>
        <link href="https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/22qm4j1kvn0h"/>
        <updated>2023-06-19T23:09:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jun 19, 23:09 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Jun 19, 22:47 UTC
Investigating - We are investigating reports of degraded performance for Actions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GitHub Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Issues Affecting Guest Name Parameters in Webhooks]]></title>
        <id>https://airbnbapi.statuspage.io/incidents/qn4kgtck381x</id>
        <link href="https://airbnbapi.statuspage.io/incidents/qn4kgtck381x"/>
        <updated>2023-06-19T14:46:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jun 19, 07:46 PDT
Resolved - This incident has been resolved. However, there remains a minor possibility that reservation acceptance confirmation webhooks may be sent without the guest's last name due to an Airbnb race condition. In case you encounter this issue, please  you can retrieve the missing information with the GET Reservations API.
We apologize for the inconvenience this may have caused and don't hesitate to reach out if you have any questions, or require further assistance.
Jun 14, 16:46 PDT
Identified - Unfortunately, the mitigation did not resolve the issue and we are still seeing reservation acceptance confirmation webhooks missing the guest last name. Please know our engineering teams are working to get this issue resolved, and we will update you with the latest information as soon as possible. Meanwhile, please use the GET reservations API for any reservations that did not include the guest last name within the webhooks. We apologize for the inconvenience.
Jun 12, 08:41 PDT
Monitoring - We have implemented a fix for this issue and are monitoring the results. Apologies for the inconvenience caused.
Jun  9, 00:12 PDT
Identified - The issue has been identified and we are working on a fix.
Meanwhile, please attempt GET reservations requests for any reservations that did not include the guest names in full within the webhooks.
Jun  8, 19:36 PDT
Investigating - We are currently investigating an issue where guest names are not returned in full within webhooks - namely the reservation acceptance confirmation webhooks. This is not a widespread issue and is only affecting a small percentage of webhooks.
Alternatively, you may be able to retrieve the details with GET reservations requests.
We will post updates as soon as we know more.
Apologies for the inconvenience caused and thank you for your understanding.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Airbnb API Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v2021.12.31 Webhook Migration Enforcement - Phase 1]]></title>
        <id>https://airbnbapi.statuspage.io/incidents/bf02v30139sd</id>
        <link href="https://airbnbapi.statuspage.io/incidents/bf02v30139sd"/>
        <updated>2023-06-17T07:00:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jun 17, 00:00 PDT
Completed - The scheduled maintenance has been completed.
Jun 13, 00:00 PDT
In progress - Scheduled maintenance is currently in progress. We will provide updates as necessary.
Jun 12, 11:00 PDT
Scheduled - The deprecation date for API Webhook Version 2021.12.31 was May 31, 2023. Any applications that have not fully migrated webhooks will be automatically migrated to a newer version, which can result in application breakage.
Automatic webhook migration will occur in phases as detailed in https://developer.airbnb.com/docs/versioning-enforcement
Phase 1 will occur during the week of June 12th, 2023 and will automatically migrate all async webhooks (except Messaging, Reviews and Reservations).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Airbnb API Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[500 Errors Across Multiple Endpoints]]></title>
        <id>https://airbnbapi.statuspage.io/incidents/l4t3crp7lr61</id>
        <link href="https://airbnbapi.statuspage.io/incidents/l4t3crp7lr61"/>
        <updated>2023-06-17T01:52:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jun 16, 18:52 PDT
Resolved - This incident has now been resolved.
Jun 16, 16:38 PDT
Monitoring - An issue has been deployed and we are monitoring the results - the 500 error rate has significantly dropped.
Jun 16, 15:44 PDT
Identified - We are actively investigating an increased number of 500 errors and an increase in latency across multiple endpoints. These errors started today (June 16, 2023) around 14:20 PDT. If your API requests fail with a 500, please retry them. Our engineering teams are working to get everything up and running again and we will update you with the latest information as soon as possible.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Airbnb API Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Investigating reports of degraded performance.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/psdymfgt6p7q</id>
        <link href="https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/psdymfgt6p7q"/>
        <updated>2023-06-16T23:59:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jun 16, 23:59 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Jun 16, 23:46 UTC
Update - Users may be unable to access org-owned resources in GitHub-owned client apps such as VS Code, GitHub Desktop, GitHub Mobile, and the CLI. We are working on reverting a change that is causing this
Jun 16, 23:46 UTC
Investigating - We are currently investigating this issue.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GitHub Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elevated Error Rate for Volumes and Snapshots]]></title>
        <id>https://status.digitalocean.com/incidents/7dgq9yz9ch1n</id>
        <link href="https://status.digitalocean.com/incidents/7dgq9yz9ch1n"/>
        <updated>2023-06-16T19:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jun 16, 19:00 UTC
Resolved - From 19:12 - 19:40 UTC, we experienced an issue with Volumes and Snapshots endpoints. During that time, we saw elevated 500 errors and a subset of users experienced latency or errors while loading the Volumes or Images tab in the Cloud Control Panel. A subset of users also experienced errors in both the Cloud Control Panel and the API for CRUD (create, read, update, and delete) operations on Volumes and Snapshots. 
Our Engineering team was able to identify the root cause and quickly deployed a configuration fix to resolve the situation.  
We apologize for the inconvenience. If you are still experiencing any problems or have additional questions, please open a support ticket within your account.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>DigitalOcean Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident: Trouble with Google Calendar and Outlook Calendar App]]></title>
        <id>https://status.slack.com//2023-06/4edd40b2f4290679</id>
        <link href="https://status.slack.com//2023-06/4edd40b2f4290679"/>
        <updated>2023-06-16T12:00:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Issue summary:

From June 13, 2023 at 12:30 PM PDT until June 15, 2023 at 2:30 AM PDT, some users may have experienced issues with statuses, reminders and agendas failing to sync from their Google Calendar and Outlook Calendar apps.


These issues were due to an outage from an upstream service provider which affected many services. The provider actively worked to remediate those issues, which then fully resolved the reported failures for impacted Slack users.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Slack System Status</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident: Some users may notice slow performance throughout Slack]]></title>
        <id>https://status.slack.com//2023-06/7363f55dbcde89c1</id>
        <link href="https://status.slack.com//2023-06/7363f55dbcde89c1"/>
        <updated>2023-06-15T23:28:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Issue summary:


On June 15, 2023 from 8:10 AM PDT to around 8:20 AM PDT, some users may have experienced slow performance and errors while loading conversations, sending messages and taking other actions in Slack.


We traced the issue to a recent code change which caused connection failures. We reverted this change and all affected functionality should be restored for users. Thank you for your patience while we resolved this issue.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Slack System Status</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident with Copilot]]></title>
        <id>https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/6tfr2b2s2073</id>
        <link href="https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/6tfr2b2s2073"/>
        <updated>2023-06-15T19:36:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jun 15, 19:36 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Jun 15, 19:22 UTC
Investigating - We are investigating reports of degraded performance for Copilot.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GitHub Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident: Trouble with workflows, loading channels and accessing Slack]]></title>
        <id>https://status.slack.com//2023-06/20df18536cc9524b</id>
        <link href="https://status.slack.com//2023-06/20df18536cc9524b"/>
        <updated>2023-06-15T18:31:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Issue Summary:

From June 14, 2023 at 3:44 PM PDT until June 15, 2023 at 4:30 AM PDT, some customers may have been unable to send messages, join Huddles, run workflows, and access Slack.


A recent code change caused some resources on our backend web hosting service to be temporarily exhausted. Due to this, users experienced errors when joining Huddles, sending messages, and may have had their connection to Slack reset. We identified the issue and reverted the change restoring full functionality to these features.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Slack System Status</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident with Pages]]></title>
        <id>https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/h3vqt1fvp9tc</id>
        <link href="https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/h3vqt1fvp9tc"/>
        <updated>2023-06-15T16:57:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jun 15, 16:57 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Jun 15, 16:47 UTC
Update - Due to an issue with Let's Encrypt, obtaining a new HTTPS certificate for Pages sites is delayed.
Jun 15, 16:34 UTC
Investigating - We are investigating reports of degraded performance for Pages.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GitHub Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Networking in Europe Datacenters (AMS, FRA, LON)]]></title>
        <id>https://status.digitalocean.com/incidents/1d5qv6pmsv6b</id>
        <link href="https://status.digitalocean.com/incidents/1d5qv6pmsv6b"/>
        <updated>2023-06-15T03:37:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jun 15, 03:37 UTC
Resolved - Our Engineering team has confirmed the full resolution of the issue impacting networking in our European regions.
From 16:40 UTC to 02:10 UTC, Users may have experienced network timeouts, packet loss, and/or increased latency interacting with the resources in these regions (AMS2/3, FRA1 & LON1).
If you continue to experience problems, please open a ticket with our Support team. Thank you for your patience and we apologize for the inconvenience.
Jun 15, 02:40 UTC
Monitoring - The network issues affecting our European regions have been mitigated. Users should no longer experience packet loss/latency, timeouts, and related issues with Droplet-based services in those regions, including Droplets, Managed Kubernetes, and Managed Database.
We will continue to monitor network conditions for a period of time to establish a return to pre-incident conditions.
Jun 15, 01:26 UTC
Update - Our engineering team continues to investigate the ongoing issues impacting the networking in our European data centres including AMS2/3, FRA1 & LON1 regions. During this time, you may experience intermittent packet loss or increased latency while interacting with the resources in these regions. We apologize for the inconvenience and will share an update once we have more information.
Jun 14, 20:06 UTC
Investigating - From 16:40 UTC our Engineering team is investigating an issue impacting the networking in our European data centers including AMS2/3, FRA1 & LON1 regions. During this time, you may experience intermittent packet loss or increased latency while interacting with the resources in these regions.
At the moment, all the droplet-based services appear to be impacted and the users can expect to see brief connectivity issues and interrupted traffic flows. This will also be impacting services including Spaces and Managed Databases. 
We apologize for the inconvenience and will share an update once we have more information.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>DigitalOcean Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scheduled Maintenance]]></title>
        <id>https://status.make.com/incidents/413nrl6rvmsx</id>
        <link href="https://status.make.com/incidents/413nrl6rvmsx"/>
        <updated>2023-06-14T11:00:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jun 14, 13:00 CEST
Completed - The scheduled maintenance has been completed.
Jun 14, 11:00 CEST
In progress - Scheduled maintenance is currently in progress. We will provide updates as necessary.
Jun 13, 15:02 CEST
Scheduled - We would like to inform you about a scheduled maintenance window that will be taking place on 14th June between 11:00 CEST - 13:00 CEST.
During this maintenance period, there will be a short interruption resulting in the unavailability of the login page and organisations page. 
If you experience a blank page , clearing your browser cache might resolve the issue . If not please reach out to our customer care team.
However, we assure you that there will be no data loss and all scenarios will continue running properly.
We apologize for any inconvenience caused and appreciate your understanding.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Make Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident: Trouble with workflows and clips transcripts]]></title>
        <id>https://status.slack.com//2023-06/a0c185e5ad5eac55</id>
        <link href="https://status.slack.com//2023-06/a0c185e5ad5eac55"/>
        <updated>2023-06-14T03:06:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Issue summary: 

On June 13, 2023 from 11:55 AM PDT to around 3:47 PM PDT, some users may have experienced failure with clips transcribing and transcoding, execution of workflows with custom functions, new deployments of apps with hosted functions, and some delay when using canvases in Slack. 


These issues were due to an outage from an upstream service provider which affected many services. The provider actively worked to remediate those issues, which then fully resolved the reported failures for impacted Slack users.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Slack System Status</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident with Actions and Pages]]></title>
        <id>https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/csnbwc85chp2</id>
        <link href="https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/csnbwc85chp2"/>
        <updated>2023-06-13T00:17:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jun 13, 00:17 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Jun 13, 00:09 UTC
Update - We have applied a mitigation and are seeing signs of recovery. We will post another update shortly.
Jun 12, 23:39 UTC
Update - We are investigating reports of degraded performance for Actions. We have identified the root cause and have begun applying a mitigation.
Jun 12, 22:48 UTC
Update - Pages is experiencing degraded performance. We are still investigating and will provide an update when we have one.
Jun 12, 22:43 UTC
Investigating - We are investigating reports of degraded performance for Actions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GitHub Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Container Registry in FRA1 and SGP1]]></title>
        <id>https://status.digitalocean.com/incidents/rptq6jh8ljd7</id>
        <link href="https://status.digitalocean.com/incidents/rptq6jh8ljd7"/>
        <updated>2023-06-12T17:44:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jun 12, 17:44 UTC
Resolved - From 04:30 to 09:30 UTC, our Engineering team observed issues with DigitalOcean Container Registry in SGP1 and FRA1 regions. During this time, users might have experienced errors while interacting with their registries in SGP1 and FRA1 regions. Users might also have experienced latency in pushing/pulling images to/from registries.
Our Engineering team has observed that the impact has been mitigated. As of 17:20 UTC, users should no longer experience any issues with pushing/pulling images to/from their registries in SGP1 and FRA1 regions. We apologize for the inconvenience. If you are still experiencing any problems or have additional questions, please open a support ticket within your account.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>DigitalOcean Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident: Small number of users might be experiencing connectivity issues]]></title>
        <id>https://status.slack.com//2023-06/1bd97a73cb7874f1</id>
        <link href="https://status.slack.com//2023-06/1bd97a73cb7874f1"/>
        <updated>2023-06-12T14:56:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On June 11, 2023 from 10:57 AM PDT to 12:10 PM PDT, some users may have experienced difficulties when trying to access Slack due to a database issue.


The underlying cause has since been determined and remediation steps were applied. This resolved the above for all impacted users.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Slack System Status</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident with Pull Requests]]></title>
        <id>https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/0csnqhwzxp1m</id>
        <link href="https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/0csnqhwzxp1m"/>
        <updated>2023-06-09T23:17:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jun  9, 23:17 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Jun  9, 22:46 UTC
Update - We are investigating elevated error rates on Pull Requests. We will continue to keep users updated on progress towards mitigation.
Jun  9, 22:18 UTC
Investigating - We are investigating reports of degraded performance for Pull Requests.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GitHub Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Modifying DNS records via Cloud Control Panel]]></title>
        <id>https://status.digitalocean.com/incidents/5jvv4xltnbk7</id>
        <link href="https://status.digitalocean.com/incidents/5jvv4xltnbk7"/>
        <updated>2023-06-08T22:53:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jun  8, 22:53 UTC
Resolved - Our Engineering team has confirmed that the issue impacting the modification of the DNS records for the existing domains via the Cloud Control Panel is fully resolved. 
If you continue to experience problems please open a ticket with our support team. Thank you for your patience and we apologize for the inconvenience.
Jun  8, 22:31 UTC
Monitoring - Our engineering team has implemented a fix to resolve the issue that affected the modification of the DNS records for the existing domains via the Cloud Control Panel. Users should now be able to modify or create new DNS records for the domains within their Cloud Control Panel.
We are monitoring the situation and will post another update once we confirm it is fully resolved.
Jun  8, 21:56 UTC
Investigating - Our Engineering team is investigating an issue with modifying or creating new DNS records in our Cloud Control Panel for the existing domains. 
During this time, some users may experience issues editing the DNS records from within the Cloud Control Panel and also when navigating through the tabs available in the domain section. Users should be able to modify or add new DNS records to the existing domains using the API.
We apologize for the inconvenience and will share an update once we have more information.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>DigitalOcean Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident with Pull Requests]]></title>
        <id>https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/17c40y7spfgl</id>
        <link href="https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/17c40y7spfgl"/>
        <updated>2023-06-08T12:55:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jun  8, 12:55 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Jun  8, 12:55 UTC
Update - Our team continues to mitigate the impacted search results however we are going to status to green due to impact on overall service. We will continue to post updates on the status page as we mitigate
Jun  8, 12:23 UTC
Update - We are aware search results for PRs are returning incomplete results in certain scenarios. This is impacting most users. No other search results are impacted. All other PR functionality is working.
Jun  8, 11:58 UTC
Investigating - We are investigating reports of degraded performance for Pull Requests.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GitHub Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NYC3 Network Maintenance 2023-06-08 04:00 UTC]]></title>
        <id>https://status.digitalocean.com/incidents/tw85s4rhwpqm</id>
        <link href="https://status.digitalocean.com/incidents/tw85s4rhwpqm"/>
        <updated>2023-06-08T08:00:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jun  8, 08:00 UTC
Completed - The scheduled maintenance has been completed.
Jun  8, 04:00 UTC
In progress - Scheduled maintenance is currently in progress. We will provide updates as necessary.
Jun  8, 03:08 UTC
Scheduled - Start time: 2023-06-08 04:00 UTC
End time: 2023-06-08 08:00 UTC
During the above window, our Networking team will be performing maintenance on core switches in our NYC3 datacenter as a part of network upgrades.
Expected Impact:
These upgrades are designed and tested to be seamless and we do not expect any impact to customer traffic due to this maintenance. If an unexpected issue arises, affected Droplets and Droplet-based services may experience a temporary loss of connectivity. We will endeavor to keep any such impact to a minimum.
If you have any questions or concerns regarding this maintenance, please reach out to us by opening up a ticket on your account via https://cloudsupport.digitalocean.com/s/createticket .]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>DigitalOcean Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scenarios using Custom Variables not working properly]]></title>
        <id>https://status.make.com/incidents/ts75knvtfm16</id>
        <link href="https://status.make.com/incidents/ts75knvtfm16"/>
        <updated>2023-06-07T22:47:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jun  8, 00:47 CEST
Resolved - This incident is now resolved.
Jun  7, 21:32 CEST
Update - We have applied a permanent fix on eu1.make.celonis.com and eu1.make.com, and based on our checks there are no issues and all scenarios are running as expected.
Jun  7, 21:18 CEST
Update - We are applying a fix for this issue.
Jun  7, 13:13 CEST
Update - We have applied a permanent fix on us1.make.celonis.com and us1.make.com, and based on our checks there are no issues and all scenarios are running as expected.
In regards to eu1.make.celonis.com and eu1.make.com, we are going to roll out the fix outside of business hours. 
Please use the workaround as needed, it was described in the previous update.
We will post another update once a full fix is applied.
Jun  6, 11:39 CEST
Identified - We're currently experiencing an issue that appears only in certain unique circumstances when a running scenario is not properly using the values of team or organization variables during executions.
Specific circumstances for the issue are:
- A team or organization variable is used as a filter condition OR there is more than one team or organization variable referenced within a single mapped field, OR the variable is used inside a function.
- AND the scenario was created / modified before March 8, 2023 
- AND the execution occurs after May 3, 2023
Workaround: 
Any user encountering this issue can open the affected scenario, make any change (move a module) and hit save. This will immediately resolve the issue for that scenario.
Complete resolution: 
The development team is actively working on a fix that will address any scenario where the issue still persists. Will post an update once we have more information around the permanent fix.
Jun  6, 09:09 CEST
Investigating - We're currently experiencing issues with Scenarios that use Custom Variables. Our engineering team is investigating the root cause.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Make Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident with Actions, Pull Requests and Webhooks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/1g1gkh0qpyvs</id>
        <link href="https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/1g1gkh0qpyvs"/>
        <updated>2023-06-07T18:39:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jun  7, 18:39 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Jun  7, 18:32 UTC
Update - Repository push workers are continuing to catch up with enqueued jobs.
Jun  7, 17:58 UTC
Update - We have mitigated the problem and are waiting for our repository push workers to catch up with enqueued jobs.
Jun  7, 17:42 UTC
Update - We have identified the cause of delayed processing for commits pushed to repositories and are actively working on mitigating this issue.
Jun  7, 17:31 UTC
Update - Webhooks is experiencing degraded performance. We are continuing to investigate.
Jun  7, 17:29 UTC
Update - Actions is experiencing degraded performance. We are still investigating and will provide an update when we have one.
Jun  7, 16:53 UTC
Update - Pushes to repositories may take longer for a significant number of customers. We are actively investigating.
Jun  7, 16:45 UTC
Investigating - We are investigating reports of degraded availability for Pull Requests.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GitHub Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Issues with the Google Workspace integration]]></title>
        <id>https://status.rippling.com/incidents/tvr7l7344y0y</id>
        <link href="https://status.rippling.com/incidents/tvr7l7344y0y"/>
        <updated>2023-06-07T13:43:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jun  7, 13:43 UTC
Resolved - This incident has been resolved.
Jun  6, 20:27 UTC
Update - We are continuing to monitor for any further issues.
Jun  6, 18:43 UTC
Monitoring - Google has implemented a fix and we are monitoring the results. Customers should be able to add new licenses and transfer subscriptions via the Google Workspace App in Rippling.
Jun  5, 22:07 UTC
Identified - We are continuing to work with Google to resolve an issue that is affecting our integration.
Jun  5, 17:32 UTC
Investigating - Customers are currently unable to add new licenses and transfer subscriptions via the Google Workspace App in Rippling. We are currently working with Google to resolve this issue.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rippling Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident: Some files may not be unfurling as expected]]></title>
        <id>https://status.slack.com//2023-06/6cb0bb4f227a82e8</id>
        <link href="https://status.slack.com//2023-06/6cb0bb4f227a82e8"/>
        <updated>2023-06-06T11:15:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Thank you for your patience while our team investigated this. All new file uploads are now expected to generate thumbnails for affected users and the issue has been resolved. Please note that previous attempts won't be retried, however new files should function as normal.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Slack System Status</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scheduled maintenance]]></title>
        <id>https://status.make.com/incidents/ms6hw0p562v8</id>
        <link href="https://status.make.com/incidents/ms6hw0p562v8"/>
        <updated>2023-06-06T08:00:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jun  6, 10:00 CEST
Completed - The scheduled maintenance has been completed.
Jun  6, 08:00 CEST
In progress - Scheduled maintenance is currently in progress. We will provide updates as necessary.
Jun  1, 15:57 CEST
Scheduled - We would like to inform you about a scheduled maintenance window that will be taking place on 6th June between 08:00 CEST - 10:00 CEST.
During this maintenance period, there will be a short interruption resulting in the unavailability of the login page and organizations page. 
However, we assure you that there will be no data loss and all scenarios will continue running properly.
We apologize for any inconvenience caused and appreciate your understanding.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Make Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Notion.so down]]></title>
        <id>https://status.notion.so/incidents/j5jk1f1ytyz1</id>
        <link href="https://status.notion.so/incidents/j5jk1f1ytyz1"/>
        <updated>2023-06-05T17:43:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jun  5, 10:43 PDT
Resolved - This has been resolved -- all users can access notion.so without issue again.
Jun  5, 09:53 PDT
Investigating - The notion.so site is down for some users, we are investigating. Users can still log in and access their workspaces at notion.so/login.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Notion Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Notion production outage]]></title>
        <id>https://status.notion.so/incidents/vpm90b50y09t</id>
        <link href="https://status.notion.so/incidents/vpm90b50y09t"/>
        <updated>2023-06-05T16:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jun  5, 09:30 PDT
Resolved - Notion was down from around 9:25am - 9:40am Pacific time.  We are still investigating an issue that may be preventing some users from accessing notion.so while not logged in.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Notion Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident: Issues with Workflow Builder]]></title>
        <id>https://status.slack.com//2023-06/f7c5d1e455e95466</id>
        <link href="https://status.slack.com//2023-06/f7c5d1e455e95466"/>
        <updated>2023-06-05T09:01:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Issue summary:


On June 02, 2023 from 3:28 PM PDT to around 5:29 PM PDT, some customers may have experienced large empty spaces in the Workflow Builder UI and issues with publishing/adding or editing steps in a workflow. 


We traced the issue to a recent code change which caused the channel selector to appear out of view, resulting in the inability to take certain actions while editing a workflow. 


We reverted the change which solved the issue for all customers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Slack System Status</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[500 Errors Across Multiple Endpoints]]></title>
        <id>https://airbnbapi.statuspage.io/incidents/xccq5r4gm6c5</id>
        <link href="https://airbnbapi.statuspage.io/incidents/xccq5r4gm6c5"/>
        <updated>2023-06-02T15:35:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jun  2, 08:35 PDT
Resolved - This issue is now resolved. The incident that occurred yesterday (June 1, 2023) resulted in an elevated amount of 500 errors across multiple endpoints, for approximately 1 hour. If you are still encountering a high volume of 500 errors, please reach out to us through the Support Portal so we can assist you further.
We apologize for any inconvenience this may have caused.
Jun  1, 13:34 PDT
Monitoring - We have implemented a fix for the issue, and the error rate has dropped significantly. We will continue to monitor the results
Jun  1, 12:51 PDT
Identified - We are actively investigating an increased number of 500 errors across multiple endpoints. These errors started today (June 1, 2023) around 12:20 PM PDT. Please know our engineering and operations teams are working hard to get everything up and running again, and we will update you with the latest information as soon as possible]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Airbnb API Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Notion.so down]]></title>
        <id>https://status.notion.so/incidents/crfw2mn48z7m</id>
        <link href="https://status.notion.so/incidents/crfw2mn48z7m"/>
        <updated>2023-06-02T12:26:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jun  2, 05:26 PDT
Resolved - The issue has been resolved, and notion.so is available to all users
Jun  2, 04:53 PDT
Investigating - The notion.so site is down for some users, we are investigating. Users can still log in and access their workspaces at notion.so/login.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Notion Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident: Some users are reporting issues triggering shortcut Workflows]]></title>
        <id>https://status.slack.com//2023-05/d3da25ad25333a58</id>
        <link href="https://status.slack.com//2023-05/d3da25ad25333a58"/>
        <updated>2023-06-01T18:00:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Issue summary:


From May 19, 2023 at 12:00 AM PDT until May 25, 2023 at 8:00 AM PDT, some users may have experienced issues triggering shortcut workflows.


We carried out our investigation and determined that cached data on the back end temporarily broke legacy workflows. In the process of determining our path to a resolution the issue resolved itself. We are taking the necessary steps to prevent similar issues in the future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Slack System Status</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident: Users reporting issues with keyboard shortcuts]]></title>
        <id>https://status.slack.com//2023-05/223e97529097de1c</id>
        <link href="https://status.slack.com//2023-05/223e97529097de1c"/>
        <updated>2023-06-01T05:57:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Issue summary:

On May 31, 2023 from 5:15 PM PDT to 7:12 PM PDT, some customers experienced issues with using keyboard shortcuts. 


We’ve traced that this issue was caused by a recent code change. We’ve rolled back this change, resolving the issue for all impacted customers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Slack System Status</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SFO2 Network Maintenance 2023-06-01 01:00 UTC Phase 2]]></title>
        <id>https://status.digitalocean.com/incidents/r8yz7801sh9w</id>
        <link href="https://status.digitalocean.com/incidents/r8yz7801sh9w"/>
        <updated>2023-06-01T03:01:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jun  1, 03:01 UTC
Completed - The scheduled maintenance has been completed.
Jun  1, 01:00 UTC
In progress - Scheduled maintenance is currently in progress. We will provide updates as necessary.
May 31, 23:11 UTC
Scheduled - Start: 2023-06-01 01:00 UTC
End: 2023-06-01 05:00 UTC
During the above window, our Networking team will be making changes to our core networking infrastructure to improve performance and scalability in the SFO2 region. This will be the second of the two maintenance activities performed by our team in the region on consecutive days.
Expected Impact:
These upgrades are designed and tested to be seamless and we do not expect any impact to customer traffic due to this maintenance. If an unexpected issue arises, affected Droplets and Droplet-based services may experience a temporary loss of private connectivity between VPCs. We will endeavor to keep any such impact to a minimum.
If you have any questions or concerns regarding this maintenance, please reach out to us by opening up a ticket on your account via https://cloudsupport.digitalocean.com/s/createticket .]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>DigitalOcean Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident: Autocomplete results ranking in search degraded]]></title>
        <id>https://status.slack.com//2023-05/aa025f4aef896b16</id>
        <link href="https://status.slack.com//2023-05/aa025f4aef896b16"/>
        <updated>2023-05-31T23:27:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Issue summary:

From May 30th, 2023 at 8:02 AM PDT until 11:18 AM PDT, some users experienced unexpected behavior with autocomplete suggestions, including incorrect rankings & incomplete results when conducting searches.


We traced the source of the issue back to an error that occurred in our autocomplete cache. A fix was rolled out to our search logic which began to show the correct results.


Users can refresh their Slack client (by pressing Cmd/Ctrl + Shift + R) if they are still experiencing issues. We apologize for any interruption.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Slack System Status</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident: Reacji Channeler app is failing for some users]]></title>
        <id>https://status.slack.com//2023-05/0848cba206ef2188</id>
        <link href="https://status.slack.com//2023-05/0848cba206ef2188"/>
        <updated>2023-05-31T23:04:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Issue summary:

From May 30th, 2023 at around 8:00 PM PDT until May 31st, 2023 at 9:20 AM PDT, users with the Reacji Channeler app installed in their workspace experienced some issues where the app would not execute.


The issue was traced back to a recent change that occurred for one of our app databases. This caused the app to accept new requests even though it was unable to connect to the database, resulting in timeout errors. 


We reverted the change and restarted the backend processes which allowed the app to connect to the database again, resolving the issue for impacted users. We apologize for any disruptions to your day.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Slack System Status</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scheduled maintenance]]></title>
        <id>https://status.make.com/incidents/2vlc5cz18jbn</id>
        <link href="https://status.make.com/incidents/2vlc5cz18jbn"/>
        <updated>2023-05-31T08:00:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[May 31, 10:00 CEST
Completed - The scheduled maintenance has been completed.
May 31, 08:02 CEST
In progress - Scheduled maintenance is currently in progress. We will provide updates as necessary.
May 29, 15:34 CEST
Scheduled - We would like to inform you about a scheduled maintenance window that will be taking place on 31st May between 08:00 CEST - 10:00 CEST.
During this maintenance period, there will be a short interruption resulting in the unavailability of the login page and organizations page. 
However, we assure you that there will be no data loss and all scenarios will continue running properly.
We apologize for any inconvenience caused and appreciate your understanding.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Make Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SFO2 Network Maintenance]]></title>
        <id>https://status.digitalocean.com/incidents/4rf2j2dmc382</id>
        <link href="https://status.digitalocean.com/incidents/4rf2j2dmc382"/>
        <updated>2023-05-31T04:04:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[May 31, 04:04 UTC
Completed - The scheduled maintenance has been completed.
May 31, 01:30 UTC
In progress - Scheduled maintenance is currently in progress. We will provide updates as necessary.
May 31, 01:26 UTC
Scheduled - Start: 2023-05-31 01:00 UTC
End: 2023-05-31 05:00 UTC

During the above window, our Networking team will be making changes to our core networking infrastructure to improve performance and scalability in the SFO2 region. This maintenance will occur in two parts on consecutive days and we will send another maintenance notice for the second phase. 
Expected Impact:
These upgrades are designed and tested to be seamless and we do not expect any impact to customer traffic due to this maintenance. If an unexpected issue arises, affected Droplets and Droplet-based services may experience a temporary loss of private connectivity between VPCs. We will endeavor to keep any such impact to a minimum.
If you have any questions or concerns regarding this maintenance, please reach out to us by opening up a ticket on your account via https://cloudsupport.digitalocean.com/s/createticket .]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>DigitalOcean Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spaces API Availability in NYC3]]></title>
        <id>https://status.digitalocean.com/incidents/vmxnj2vv4k9k</id>
        <link href="https://status.digitalocean.com/incidents/vmxnj2vv4k9k"/>
        <updated>2023-05-31T02:25:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[May 31, 02:25 UTC
Resolved - Our Engineering team has confirmed the full resolution of the issue impacting Spaces performance and availability in our NYC3 region.
From 00:20 to 00:57 UTC, users may have experienced slowness or timeouts when trying to access or manage their Spaces resources in NYC3, static site assets in NYC, or App Platform bandwidth insights.
Spaces should now be operating normally. If you continue to experience problems, please open a ticket with our support team from within your Cloud Control Panel. We apologize for any inconvenience.
May 31, 01:47 UTC
Monitoring - Our Engineering team has observed recovery of availability for Spaces in our NYC3 region. 
Availability returned to 100% at 00:57 UTC and since then, users should not be experiencing any issues with Spaces or App Platform. 
We'll now monitor the situation for a period of time and post a final update once we confirm the incident is resolved.
May 31, 01:05 UTC
Investigating - Our Engineering team is investigating a drop in availability for Spaces in our NYC region. During this time, some users may experience errors with API or object requests, be unable to create new buckets in NYC3, and/or see issues with loading Spaces in the Cloud Control Panel. 
Additionally, users of App Platform will be unable to see bandwidth insights in their dashboards and static site users may notice errors fetching assets from Spaces buckets in NYC3. 
We apologize for the inconvenience and will share an update once we have more information.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>DigitalOcean Status - Incident History</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>